<gameList>
<game id="38532" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Alchemist Marie &amp; Elie - Futari no Atelier (Japan).zip</path>
	<name>Alchemist Marie &amp; Elie: Futari no Atelier</name>
	<desc>In the city of Salburg, there has always been a long tradition of alchemy - a magical science that dealt with combining various materials and turning metals into gold. You play as two young girls, Marlone and Elvira, who have to study at the Academy of alchemy, make powerful items, and prove to their masters they are worthy to be real alchemists.

The game is a combination of role-playing and simulation. You have to read books and talk to people in order to learn more about items, and then to buy these items or to to find them somewhere. You must combine powerful items in order to impress your teachers. You also develop your characters in a standard RPG fashion. You can equip weapons and armor on them, and fight random enemies in wilderness areas. You gain levels and become stronger the more enemies you fight. The battles are automatic, and you can only assign a general strategy to your characters.</desc>
	<image>./boxart/Alchemist Marie &amp; Elie - Futari no Atelier (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Alchemist Marie &amp; Elie - Futari no Atelier (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Alchemist Marie &amp; Elie - Futari no Atelier (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Gust Co., Ltd.</developer>
	<publisher>Gust Co., Ltd.</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="46274" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Another Heaven - Memory of those Days (Japan).zip</path>
	<name>Another Heaven - Memory of those Days</name>
	<desc>Another Heaven: Memory of Those Days is an Adventure game, developed and published by Omega Micott, which was released in Japan in 2000.</desc>
	<image>./boxart/Another Heaven - Memory of those Days (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Another Heaven - Memory of those Days (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Another Heaven - Memory of those Days (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer/>
	<publisher/>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="38533" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Arc the Lad - Kishin Fukkatsu (Japan).zip</path>
	<name>Arc the Lad: Kijin Fukkatsu</name>
	<desc>Two generations ago, there was a great battle between the humans and the machines. Led by their evil god, the machines were eventually able to win the battle and to take control over the world. You play the role of Elc, the hero of  Arc the Lad 2. As always, Elc is a freelance mercenary who gets assignments from his guild. He encounters Finia, a girl who belonged to a resistance group and whose mother was killed by the machines. With the help of other friends, the heroes must save the humanity and restore the world to normal.

This is a side-story in Arc the Lad series, set in a futuristic environment. As in the classic Arc the Lad games, the entire dungeon navigation is perceived as a series of continuous battles. You move your heroes in turn-based mode, and enemies use their turn to perform their moves. You can attack once an enemy is on a square near you, and also use a variety of special techniques.</desc>
	<image>./boxart/Arc the Lad - Kishin Fukkatsu (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Arc the Lad - Kishin Fukkatsu (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Arc the Lad - Kishin Fukkatsu (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Bandai Co., Ltd.</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai Co., Ltd.</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="38538" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Battle Spirit - Digimon Frontier (Japan).zip</path>
	<name>Digimon: Battle Spirit</name>
	<desc>In 2001, an unknown digimon (digital monster) appeared. He was immensely powerful and could delete any other digimon by touching him. Very soon he gained control over the entire Digiworld. But some digimons organized a resistance group consisting of seven most venerable members. Now those digital monsters must test their powers in order to finally be able to defeat the unknown evil digimon.

This is a platform fighting game based on the Digimon manga/animé series. You can fight against computer AI or in two-player mode. There are seven digimons to choose as playable characters; all are popular digimon characters from the original series, each associated with a human tamer. The battles take place on a system of platform. You can freely move around, jump, and perform a variety of melee and long-ranged attacks. Oppoenents can also inflict status ailments on each other. In each location there are random events happening, which influence the performance of the combatants.</desc>
	<image>./boxart/Battle Spirit - Digimon Frontier (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Battle Spirit - Digimon Frontier (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Battle Spirit - Digimon Frontier (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Dimps Corporation</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai Co., Ltd.</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="38534" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Blue Wing Blitz (Japan).zip</path>
	<name>Blue Wing Blitz</name>
	<desc>There are six nations living in the world of floating islands. The most powerful one is the Ordia Empire, possessing the best aircrafts in the world. But its leaders were hungry for even more power, and planned to invade and to occupy the other five nations. The other nations tried to maintain diplomatic relationship with the Empire as long as possible. But one of those countries, the Esk Republic, decided to send a special strike team of skillful pilots, attempting to initiate a secret rebellion against the Empire. A young pilot named Keid, guided by his senior partner, the girl Payer, is the one who was chosen for this mission.

"Blue Wing Blitz" is a turn-based strategy RPG with a twist: instead of fighters or soldier units, you command aircrafts. You navigate your planes over a battle field, which consists of airspaces, in round-based fashion. Once you land on a space occupied by an enemy plane, a battle follows. During those battles you have control over your aircraft, performing various attacks or defending. After several turns, the battle stops, but will resume if the enemy planes are still standing on the same space.</desc>
	<image>./boxart/Blue Wing Blitz (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Blue Wing Blitz (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Blue Wing Blitz (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Square Co., Ltd.</developer>
	<publisher>Square Co., Ltd.</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="46275" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Dark Eyes - Battle Gate (Japan).zip</path>
	<name>Dark Eyes - Battle Gate</name>
	<desc>Dark Eyes ~ Battle Gate tells the story of a battle between two races on a pioneer planet.  This Strategy RPG also supports the WonderGate, allowing additional features to be downloaded with a cellular phone</desc>
	<image>./boxart/Dark Eyes - Battle Gate (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Dark Eyes - Battle Gate (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Dark Eyes - Battle Gate (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer/>
	<publisher/>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="38535" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Dicing Knight. (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<name>Dicing Knight.</name>
	<desc>Dicing Knight. follows the journey of a nameless knight fighting through a series of randomly generated dungeons.  The game will start on the floor of a dungeon, your goal being to find the floors key to progress to the next floor. Eventually you will reach a dungeon boss, after you beat it youll be allowed access to a new more difficult dungeon. Dungeons are timed by a Food Gauge which when depleted will force you to exit the dungeon.

The dungeons are named:

1. Lindwurm - German term for dragon, meant to establish the mythic setting. This dungeon has a heavenly aura.
2. Shootingstar - A fiery land that will start to test your knowledge of the controls from Lindwurm.
3. Jabberwock - A whimsical land that is bathed in night. When the night shall end is unknown.
4. Quetzalcoatl - The area named for the Aztec sky god and creator. The entire map can no longer be seen.
5. Jörmungandr - The serpent that shall kill Thor. This stage is a mythic earthy setting.

The A button swings your sword and the B rings up your shield, the key items of any knight. Slashing your foes with your sword and devouring projectiles with your shield will increase your special meter, which when filled will allow you to perform a deadly special attack Shining Sword or "Blazing Sword".

One interesting features of Dicing Knight is the dicing every time you attack an enemy dice will pop out of it and roll, youll deal damage to the foe based on the rolls you get. Likewise when you are hit dice also roll to determine youre damaged. 

The Y buttons will be mapped to four different items, which can be found inside your foes. A variety of items are included in the game such as an item that will predict or alter dice rolls, a variety of stat altering potions, invincibility items, and a drill that will let you progress through dungeon wall to avoid monster filled rooms. Various orbs are also obtainable, via a lottery system, which will improve your abilities. 

After you beat the game on Knight Mode youll obtain a, Fortuner Mode, which will alter the game play, keeping the dungeon crawling style but giving you the ability to shoot to you and more of the monsters. The A button will be transformed into a double pistol, and the B will lob grenades. As well as two new specials that allow you to absorb enemy bullets or do a powerful shock attack. A new stage with a fitting title will also appear:

1. Ouroboros - The snake eating its own tail, an alchemical symbol of immortality, this dungeon rests betwixt time, eternal, and waiting.</desc>
	<image>./boxart/Dicing Knight. (Japan) (Translated En).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Dicing Knight. (Japan) (Translated En).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Dicing Knight. (Japan) (Translated En).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Platine Dispositif</developer>
	<publisher>Qute</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="38537" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Digimon - Anode Tamer &amp; Cathode Tamer (Asia).zip</path>
	<name>Digimon Anode &amp; Cathode Tamer</name>
	<desc>This release contains the first  Digimon Adventure, both  Anode Tamer and  Cathode Tamer versions. The game is based on the manga and animé series Digimon. You play as an ordinary Japanese boy named Ryou who gets sucked into the mysterious digital world and has to help the digital monster Agumon and his friends to recruit digital monsters and send them into battles against evil ones.
</desc>
	<image>./boxart/Digimon - Anode Tamer &amp; Cathode Tamer (Asia).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Digimon - Anode Tamer &amp; Cathode Tamer (Asia).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Digimon - Anode Tamer &amp; Cathode Tamer (Asia).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Bandai Co., Ltd.</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai Co., Ltd.</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="38536" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Digimon Adventure 02 - D1 Tamers (Japan).zip</path>
	<name>Digimon Adventure 02: D1 Tamers</name>
	<desc>This is a sequel to  Digimon Adventure 02: Tag Tamers, set in the world of digital monsters based on the popular manga series. After having defeated the evil Millenniumon, our hero Ryou thought that would be his last travel to the Digiworld. However, the four sacred Digimons summon him once again, to participate in the D1 monster fighting tournament. But that is not all: it appears that Millenniumon is still alive, and is looking for revenge! Now Ryou has to win the tournament and defeat his archenemy once again.

The gameplay is nearly identical to that of the previous game. You travel through top-down and isometric locations, fighting monsters with your own monster team, and then recruiting new monsters and assembling a collection. The battles are turn-based and are viewed from an isometric perspective. The monsters have various kinds of attacks in their disposal. Each attack is shown as a short animated sequence.</desc>
	<image>./boxart/Digimon Adventure 02 - D1 Tamers (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Digimon Adventure 02 - D1 Tamers (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Digimon Adventure 02 - D1 Tamers (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>SIMS Co., Ltd.</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai Co., Ltd.</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87632" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Digimon Tamers - Battle Spirit (Japan).zip</path>
	<name>Digimon Tamers - Battle Spirit</name>
	<desc/>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Dimps Corporation</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players>1-2</players>
</game>
<game id="38538" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Digimon Tamers - Battle Spirit Ver. 1.5 (Japan).zip</path>
	<name>Digimon: Battle Spirit</name>
	<desc>In 2001, an unknown digimon (digital monster) appeared. He was immensely powerful and could delete any other digimon by touching him. Very soon he gained control over the entire Digiworld. But some digimons organized a resistance group consisting of seven most venerable members. Now those digital monsters must test their powers in order to finally be able to defeat the unknown evil digimon.

This is a platform fighting game based on the Digimon manga/animé series. You can fight against computer AI or in two-player mode. There are seven digimons to choose as playable characters; all are popular digimon characters from the original series, each associated with a human tamer. The battles take place on a system of platform. You can freely move around, jump, and perform a variety of melee and long-ranged attacks. Oppoenents can also inflict status ailments on each other. In each location there are random events happening, which influence the performance of the combatants.</desc>
	<image>./boxart/Digimon Tamers - Battle Spirit Ver. 1.5 (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Digimon Tamers - Battle Spirit Ver. 1.5 (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Digimon Tamers - Battle Spirit Ver. 1.5 (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Dimps Corporation</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai Co., Ltd.</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="38539" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Digimon Tamers - Brave Tamer (Japan).zip</path>
	<name>Digimon Tamers: Brave Tamer</name>
	<desc>Based on the popular Digimon manga, this is a sequel to  Digimon Adventure 02: D1 Tamers. The game picks up directly where the previous one ended. After yet another ultimate battle against the evil Millenniumon, during which he revealed to the hero Ryou a terrifying secret, there was a great explosion. Ryou comes to his senses in an unknown place. The only digital monster there explains to him that the explosion send Millenniumon to the future, while Ryou ended up in the past. And now Millenniumon is trying to take control over the main computer in the Digiworld, and it is Ryou's task to stop him once and for all, and to finally find the truth about his and his archenemy's identities.

The gameplay is similar to that of the predecessors: you navigate your hero over the top-down view, descend into dungeons, fight monsters in turn-based combat, recruit them into your party, and send the new teams to fight new enemies. The battle are not isometric any more, but viewed entirely as animé-style pictures. Attacks are also depicted as animated sequences.</desc>
	<image>./boxart/Digimon Tamers - Brave Tamer (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Digimon Tamers - Brave Tamer (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Digimon Tamers - Brave Tamer (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>SIMS Co., Ltd.</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai Co., Ltd.</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="38540" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Digimon Tamers - Digimon Medley (Japan).zip</path>
	<name>Digimon Tamers: Digimon Medley</name>
	<desc>"Digimon Medley" is based on the popular manga and and animé series Digimon, in which ordinary Japanese children find a way into a digital world, where they help good digital monsters fight against evil ones. The game is not directly plot-related to  Digimon Adventure or Digimon Tamers: Brave Tamer games. Instead, it follows more closely the actual episodes of the series. You play as various characters, such as the main hero Taichi and his friend Yamato from the first episodes, as well as heroes from the Digimon Tamers sub-series: Takato, Ruki, and Lee. The game is divided into short episodes, each one of which revives one of the battles in the series. You start with Digimon Tamers, as they venture into the DigiWorld, only to meet the enigmatic digimon named Impmon, who is up to some mischief. 

Each episode can be played as one of several available characters. Each character also has his/her own digimon who fights all the battles. The battles are random and occur while you are navigating your heroes through top-down dungeons. The attacks are displayed as short animé-style sequences. During your turn, you must press the A button repeatedly to increase the power of your attack. The enemy attacks simultaneously, and you have to invest enough power in your attack in order for it to connect.</desc>
	<image>./boxart/Digimon Tamers - Digimon Medley (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Digimon Tamers - Digimon Medley (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Digimon Tamers - Digimon Medley (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Shade, Inc.</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai Co., Ltd.</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="46276" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Digital Monster - D-Project (Japan).zip</path>
	<name>Digital Monster - D-Project</name>
	<desc>In this, the newest Digimon RPG game for the Wonderswan Color/Crystal, you're once again cast as a kid who's sent to the Digital World to save it (what else?), armed with nothing else but your partner digimon, your tamer know-how, and a machine that someh</desc>
	<image>./boxart/Digital Monster - D-Project (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Digital Monster - D-Project (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Digital Monster - D-Project (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer/>
	<publisher/>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="46277" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Digital Monster Card Game - Ver. WonderSwan Color (Japan).zip</path>
	<name>Digital Monster Card Game - Ver. WonderSwan Color</name>
	<desc>Digimon Card Game: Ver. WonderSwan Color is the popular card game based on the anime series for the WonderSwan Color.  As you start the game, you'll talk with Takato. After the card game tutorial (or if you just skip it ), you' ll be in a menu with a list</desc>
	<image>./boxart/Digital Monster Card Game - Ver. WonderSwan Color (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Digital Monster Card Game - Ver. WonderSwan Color (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Digital Monster Card Game - Ver. WonderSwan Color (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer/>
	<publisher/>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="38541" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Dokodemo Hamster 3 - Odekake Saffron (Japan).zip</path>
	<name>Dokodemo Hamster 3: O-Dekake Safuran</name>
	<desc>This is the third in Bandai's "hamster simulation" series. In this game, you are the "master" of a hamster. The game flows in real time, but you can interfere and perform various actions. The hamster has its own room in a house, with a table and a wheel. There are many things you can do with the hamster. You can take in to a stroll in the forest, go shopping with it, make it play with a ball, and so on. You can also perform actions unrelated to the hamster, like re-decorating the house or writing and painting on a piece of paper. The game features a point-and-click interface: you move your cursor over an object (such as hamster or calendar), which brings up an action menu.</desc>
	<image>./boxart/Dokodemo Hamster 3 - Odekake Saffron (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Dokodemo Hamster 3 - Odekake Saffron (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Dokodemo Hamster 3 - Odekake Saffron (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>BEC Co., Ltd.</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai Co., Ltd.</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="46278" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Dragon Ball (Japan).zip</path>
	<name>Dragon Ball</name>
	<desc>The game is based on the famous Dragon Ball manga series, starring Son Goku, and spans a long time period of the hero's life. It begins with Son Goku being a mere child and meeting the mysterious Bulma who asks him to add her on her quest to find seven Dr</desc>
	<image>./boxart/Dragon Ball (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Dragon Ball (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Dragon Ball (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>TOSE</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="38543" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Final Fantasy (Japan).zip</path>
	<name>Final Fantasy</name>
	<desc>Hironobu Sakaguchi's Final Fantasy... the first of one of the longest role-playing game series known to mankind. Final Fantasy is the game for the NES console that started it all.

The world is veiled in darkness. Winds don't blow, the seas are stormy, and the earth rots. All people can hope for is that the ancient prophecy will be finally fulfilled. "When the world is veiled in darkness, four warriors will come..." And indeed, they come - the four characters you have previously chosen. Their first quest is to free a princess from the evil Garland, and then the real journey begins...

Final Fantasy is played with an adventuring party rather than with a single character. Before the game starts, the player chooses four characters from six different classes: Fighter, Thief, Black Belt, White Mage, Red Mage, and Black Mage. Which four classes the player chooses for his characters is entirely up to him. He also gives the characters names. 

In the game, the party walks around in a top-down world, visits cities, caves, palaces and other places to buy equipment, rest and get hints and new quests, and fights baddies when they are encountered. Final Fantasy uses a turn-based combat system; the ATB (active-time battle) system from the later installments is not used. In battle, the player gives each character in order a command (attack a particular enemy, cast a spell, use an item, or try to run.) Then the characters and the enemies act in a random order. Attacked enemies and party members lose hit points, dying when they reach zero HP. When all the enemies are defeated, living party members receive experience, eventually gaining a level and improving their stats when enough experience is accumulated. Slain party members can be revived in towns for a price. 

Spells are bought in cities in special shops. The spells are divided into two categories - white magic and black magic. White Mages can only use white magic, Black Mages can only use black magic, and Red Mages can use both. Casting spells in battle uses up magic points, which, like hit points, can be restored by resting in inns.</desc>
	<image>./boxart/Final Fantasy (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Final Fantasy (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Final Fantasy (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Square Co., Ltd.</developer>
	<publisher>Square Co., Ltd.</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="38544" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Final Fantasy II (Japan).zip</path>
	<name>Final Fantasy II</name>
	<desc>This is the fourth entry in the  Final Fantasy series. It was known as Final Fantasy II internationally, because the  second and third games were never released outside of Japan.

The military country of Baron is one of the strongest in the land, with a proud army and a majestic air force known as the Red Wings. But, while their armies are kind and loyal, the recent actions of the King are anything but. The young Captain of the Red Wings, Cecil, is ordered to steal a crystal from a village of innocent magicians, and when he questions the actions of his King, Cecil is immediately thrown out of the country and sent off to kill strange monsters. Little does he realize the price the King's actions will pay, and what the true secret of the crystals, and their powers, truly is...

This is the first Final Fantasy game that introduced the famous ATB (active-time battle) system: during the battles, you have a time indicator for each party member that tells you when this character is able to act. If it takes you too long to select a command for this character, the enemy will act without waiting for your turn. The game abandons the job system that was implemented in the first and the third game in favor of pre-set character classes (paladin, white mage, ninja, etc.) assigned to each party member.

The PlayStation version adds a new rendered intro and ending.</desc>
	<image>./boxart/Final Fantasy II (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Final Fantasy II (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Final Fantasy II (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Square Co., Ltd.</developer>
	<publisher>Square Co., Ltd.</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87635" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Final Fantasy IV (Japan).zip</path>
	<name>Final Fantasy IV</name>
	<desc/>
	<image>./boxart/Final Fantasy IV (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Final Fantasy IV (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Final Fantasy IV (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Square Co., Ltd.</developer>
	<publisher>Square Co., Ltd.</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87637" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Final Lap Special - GT &amp; Formula Machine (Japan).zip</path>
	<name>Final Lap Special - GT &amp; Formula Machine</name>
	<desc> For each mode, GT and Formula, you can only race as those cars in its respective tournaments whi</desc>
	<image>./boxart/Final Lap Special - GT &amp; Formula Machine (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Final Lap Special - GT &amp; Formula Machine (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Final Lap Special - GT &amp; Formula Machine (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Bandai</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87638" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Flash Koibito-kun (Japan).zip</path>
	<name>Flash Koibito-kun</name>
	<desc/>
	<image>./boxart/Flash Koibito-kun (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Flash Koibito-kun (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Flash Koibito-kun (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Koto Laboratory</developer>
	<publisher>Kobunsha</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87665" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./From TV Animation One Piece - Chopper no Daibouken (Japan).zip</path>
	<name>From TV Animation One Piece - Chopper no Daibouken</name>
	<desc>After the long intro has set the plot the player is given control of Chopper who's initial aim is to return to the group after unfo</desc>
	<image>./boxart/From TV Animation One Piece - Chopper no Daibouken (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/From TV Animation One Piece - Chopper no Daibouken (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/From TV Animation One Piece - Chopper no Daibouken (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Bandai</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87666" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./From TV Animation One Piece - Grand Battle Swan Colosseum (Japan).zip</path>
	<name>From TV Animation One Piece - Grand Battle Swan Co</name>
	<desc> A real high point in the WonderSwan One Piece series </desc>
	<image>./boxart/From TV Animation One Piece - Grand Battle Swan Colosseum (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/From TV Animation One Piece - Grand Battle Swan Colosseum (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/From TV Animation One Piece - Grand Battle Swan Colosseum (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Bandai</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87667" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./From TV Animation One Piece - Niji no Shima Densetsu (Japan).zip</path>
	<name>From TV Animation One Piece - Niji no Shima Denset</name>
	<desc/>
	<image>./boxart/From TV Animation One Piece - Niji no Shima Densetsu (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/From TV Animation One Piece - Niji no Shima Densetsu (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/From TV Animation One Piece - Niji no Shima Densetsu (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Bandai</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87668" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./From TV Animation One Piece - Treasure Wars (Japan).zip</path>
	<name>From TV Animation One Piece - Treasure Wars</name>
	<desc/>
	<image>./boxart/From TV Animation One Piece - Treasure Wars (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/From TV Animation One Piece - Treasure Wars (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/From TV Animation One Piece - Treasure Wars (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Bandai</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87669" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./From TV Animation One Piece - Treasure Wars 2 - Buggy Land e Youkoso (Japan).zip</path>
	<name>From TV Animation One Piece - Treasure Wars 2 - Bu</name>
	<desc>That's not to say Treasure Wars 2 is any less enjoyable just little changed; still "choose your character and att</desc>
	<image>./boxart/From TV Animation One Piece - Treasure Wars 2 - Buggy Land e Youkoso (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/From TV Animation One Piece - Treasure Wars 2 - Buggy Land e Youkoso (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/From TV Animation One Piece - Treasure Wars 2 - Buggy Land e Youkoso (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Bandai</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="38546" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Front Mission (Japan).zip</path>
	<name>Front Mission</name>
	<desc>In the future, many military forces are dependent on huge mech robots, called Wanzers (Walking Panzers) for combat. At Huffman Island, located in the the pacific ocean, wanzers are deployed by both the USN (United States of the New Continent) and the OCU (Oceana Community Union), who dispute ownership over the island.  One night, the OCU forces stage a covert recon mission on a facility located in Larcus, a USN-held territory and weapons facility. Lead by a soldier named Roid, this mission was entirely unofficial and violated the peace treaty. During the mission, USN forces lead by Commander Driscoll appeared and ambushed the OCU soldiers. During the combat, Roid's fiance, Karen is killed and the USN facility is blown up; placing the blame on the OCU. This became known as the &amp;quot;Larcus Incident&amp;quot; and the OCU denied all knowledge of it's soldiers actions. Ultimately it would be a leading cause to the second Huffman War. 

One year later, the war is underway and Huffman island is under provisional control of the OCU, but with a weakened military unable to defend against USN attacks. The soldiers involved involved in the Larcus Incident have all been discharged and disgraced. Roid spends his time fighting as a gladiator in the Wanzer fighting arena before being approached by a mysterious man. Colonel Olson has found out about Roid's history and wants him to command a mercenary unit he is assembling on behalf of the OCU, dubbed &amp;quot;Carrion Crow&amp;quot;. Convincing Roid that Driscoll is still out there on the island, Roid agrees.

Front Mission is a turn-based strategy RPG played from an isometric perspective. Players progress in the story through large strategic battles involving multiple units and cutscenes between them. At certain places, usually towns, the player can visit multiple locations including bars and shops, and talk to people. Shops are also found to purchase new weaponry, parts and make repairs. In combat, each Wanzer robot is a seperate unit and, has a large variety of weapons and attack styles depending on what's equipped. Units get experience for defeating enemies and also for using various techniques. The more an attack is used, the more powerful it becomes.</desc>
	<image>./boxart/Front Mission (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Front Mission (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Front Mission (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>G-Craft</developer>
	<publisher>Square Co., Ltd.</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87639" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Gekitou! Crash Gear Turbo - Gear Champion League (Japan).zip</path>
	<name>Gekitou! Crash Gear Turbo - Gear Champion League</name>
	<desc/>
	<image>./boxart/Gekitou! Crash Gear Turbo - Gear Champion League (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Gekitou! Crash Gear Turbo - Gear Champion League (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Gekitou! Crash Gear Turbo - Gear Champion League (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Bandai</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87640" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Gensou Maden Saiyuuki Retribution - Hi no Ataru Basho de (Japan).zip</path>
	<name>Gensou Maden Saiyuuki Retribution - Hi no Ataru Ba</name>
	<desc/>
	<image>./boxart/Gensou Maden Saiyuuki Retribution - Hi no Ataru Basho de (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Gensou Maden Saiyuuki Retribution - Hi no Ataru Basho de (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Gensou Maden Saiyuuki Retribution - Hi no Ataru Basho de (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>PicPac-Airreal</developer>
	<publisher>Mubik</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="38547" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Golden Axe (Japan).zip</path>
	<name>Golden Axe</name>
	<desc>Sega's classic arcade beat-'em-up game, Golden Axe puts in the shoes of one of three heroes, each with his own reason for trying to overthrow the evil rule of Death-Adder, who - along with his forces of darkness - kidnapped and imprisoned the King and his daughter and stole the legendary Golden Axe.

This is a horizontal fighting game, where you basically take one of the three characters (a warrior, a dwarf or an amazon) and bash everything which stands between you and Death Adder himself.</desc>
	<image>./boxart/Golden Axe (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Golden Axe (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Golden Axe (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>SEGA Enterprises Ltd.</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai Co., Ltd.</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87641" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Gransta Chronicle (Japan).zip</path>
	<name>Gransta Chronicle</name>
	<desc>The combat adopts the simulation battle method. Because the friend or foe is disordered on the wide field, let's challenge it by making good use of the weapons, magic, and all items. The items and monsters can be </desc>
	<image>./boxart/Gransta Chronicle (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Gransta Chronicle (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Gransta Chronicle (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Tom Create Co., Ltd.</developer>
	<publisher>Omega Micott Inc.</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="38548" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Guilty Gear Petit (Japan).zip</path>
	<name>Guilty Gear Petit</name>
	<desc>The game takes place in 22th century. Scientists developed a new technique that allowed them to merge the DNA of humans and animals, producing powerful creatures known as "gears". The characters of the game participate in a tournament, the winner of which would face a gear who went out of control and is threatening to lead a gear rebellion against the humans. The game allows you to play as familiar characters from Guilty Gear series, such as the main hero Sol Badguy, who has a certain connection to the gears, and his rival, the leader of the Holy Knights named Ky Kiske. It also introduces a new character, the nurse Fanny, who fights with a syringe and has a mysterious connection to the genius surgeon, and later serial murderer, Dr. Baldhead. 

"Guilty Gear Petit" is a 2D fighting game. The story mode lets you pick a character and take him/her through a series of fights, while in time attack mode you can choose your opponents freely. The graphics are done in "super-deformed" style. The game retains key ingredients of Guilty Gear gameplay, such as building tension in order to execute powerful attacks, combo moves, etc.</desc>
	<image>./boxart/Guilty Gear Petit (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Guilty Gear Petit (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Guilty Gear Petit (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Arc System Works Co., Ltd.</developer>
	<publisher>Sammy Corporation</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="38549" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Guilty Gear Petit 2 (Japan).zip</path>
	<name>Guilty Gear Petit 2</name>
	<desc>In 22th century, scientists found a way to create artificial beings whom they called "gears". These gears were very powerful, but did not have wills of their own, and were completely obedient to the humans. However, a gear named Justice was able to free himself from the control and led a rebellion against the humans. Since then, the humanity lived in fear that the gears will one day gain the power on the Earth. For that purpose, the Sacred Order of the Holy Knights organized fighting tournaments to find out who is strong enough to face the renegade gears.

"Guilty Gear Petit 2" is very similar to its predecessor, having the same "super-deformed" graphical style, battle moves (including the tension system to accumulate power and combo attacks), as well as backgrounds for battles. Several new characters appear in "Guilty Gear Petit 2", such as Zato-1, the former head of the assassin guild, the pirate captain Johnny, the time traveler Axl Lou from the 20th century, the mysterious Faust, and others.</desc>
	<image>./boxart/Guilty Gear Petit 2 (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Guilty Gear Petit 2 (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Guilty Gear Petit 2 (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Arc System Works Co., Ltd.</developer>
	<publisher>Sammy Corporation</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="38550" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./GunPey EX (Japan).zip</path>
	<name>Gunpey EX</name>
	<desc>Direct sequel to the original Gunpey on the WonderSwan, Gunpey EX adds a number of new elements to the classic; most notably, color.

In addition to earning points for completing a line across the field you will now earn points if those lines are of a matching color. Previously only gray lines were possible now red, blue, and green lines appear.

Gunpey EX has the same modes as the previous game, except a story mode. Time Attack mode where one has to eliminate as many tiles as possible in two of five minutes. Endless mode give the player unlimited time to crank out whatever score they desire. Stage mode presents a set number of tiles to remove in a given time. Puzzle mode puts the player in the situation of having to remove a certain group of tiles, the player can change the color of the lines here when they swap their tiles positions.

A link mode is available to play against another human with a WonderSwan and Gunpey EX. 

This game could access the internet through a wireless phone and the WonderGate where it was able to interact with an online high score board.</desc>
	<image>./boxart/GunPey EX (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/GunPey EX (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/GunPey EX (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Koto Laboratory</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai Co., Ltd.</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87642" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Hanjuku Hero - Ah, Sekai yo Hanjuku Nare...!! (Japan).zip</path>
	<name>Hanjuku Hero - Ah, Sekai yo Hanjuku Nare...!!</name>
	<desc/>
	<image>./boxart/Hanjuku Hero - Ah, Sekai yo Hanjuku Nare...!! (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Hanjuku Hero - Ah, Sekai yo Hanjuku Nare...!! (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Hanjuku Hero - Ah, Sekai yo Hanjuku Nare...!! (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Square Co., Ltd.</developer>
	<publisher>Square Co., Ltd.</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87643" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Hataraku Chocobo (Japan).zip</path>
	<name>Hataraku Chocobo</name>
	<desc>A sim featuring Square's mascot released on the WonderSwan Color in Japan only.</desc>
	<image>./boxart/Hataraku Chocobo (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Hataraku Chocobo (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Hataraku Chocobo (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Square Co., Ltd.</developer>
	<publisher>Square Co., Ltd.</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87644" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Hunter X Hunter - Greed Island (Japan).zip</path>
	<name>Hunter X Hunter - Greed Island</name>
	<desc>When you encounter the enemy, you rush into a command selection type turn system battle on a 8x3 field mas</desc>
	<image>./boxart/Hunter X Hunter - Greed Island (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Hunter X Hunter - Greed Island (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Hunter X Hunter - Greed Island (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Bandai</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87645" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Hunter X Hunter - Michibikareshi Mono (Japan).zip</path>
	<name>Hunter X Hunter - Michibikareshi Mono</name>
	<desc/>
	<image>./boxart/Hunter X Hunter - Michibikareshi Mono (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Hunter X Hunter - Michibikareshi Mono (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Hunter X Hunter - Michibikareshi Mono (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Bandai</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87646" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Hunter X Hunter - Sorezore no Ketsui (Japan).zip</path>
	<name>Hunter X Hunter - Sorezore no Ketsui</name>
	<desc>The story of Hunter X Hunter focuses on a young boy named Gon Freecss, who one day discovers that the father he had always been told was dead was ali</desc>
	<image>./boxart/Hunter X Hunter - Sorezore no Ketsui (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Hunter X Hunter - Sorezore no Ketsui (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Hunter X Hunter - Sorezore no Ketsui (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Bandai</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87648" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Inuyasha - Fuuun Emaki (Japan).zip</path>
	<name>Inuyasha - Fuuun Emaki</name>
	<desc/>
	<image>./boxart/Inuyasha - Fuuun Emaki (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Inuyasha - Fuuun Emaki (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Inuyasha - Fuuun Emaki (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Bandai</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87649" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Inuyasha - Kagome no Sengoku Nikki (Japan).zip</path>
	<name>Inuyasha - Kagome no Sengoku Nikki</name>
	<desc/>
	<image>./boxart/Inuyasha - Kagome no Sengoku Nikki (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Inuyasha - Kagome no Sengoku Nikki (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Inuyasha - Kagome no Sengoku Nikki (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Bandai</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87650" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Inuyasha - Kagome no Yume Nikki (Japan).zip</path>
	<name>Inuyasha - Kagome no Yume Nikki</name>
	<desc/>
	<image>./boxart/Inuyasha - Kagome no Yume Nikki (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Inuyasha - Kagome no Yume Nikki (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Inuyasha - Kagome no Yume Nikki (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Bandai</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87651" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Judgement Silversword - Rebirth Edition (Japan).zip</path>
	<name>Judgement Silversword - Rebirth Edition</name>
	<desc/>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>M-KAI</developer>
	<publisher>Qute</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players>1</players>
</game>
<game id="87658" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Kidou Senshi Gundam - Giren no Yabou - Tokubetsu Hen - Aoki Hoshi no Hasha (Japan).zip</path>
	<name>Kidou Senshi Gundam - Giren no Yabou - Tokubetsu H</name>
	<desc/>
	<image>./boxart/Kidou Senshi Gundam - Giren no Yabou - Tokubetsu Hen - Aoki Hoshi no Hasha (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Kidou Senshi Gundam - Giren no Yabou - Tokubetsu Hen - Aoki Hoshi no Hasha (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Kidou Senshi Gundam - Giren no Yabou - Tokubetsu Hen - Aoki Hoshi no Hasha (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Bandai</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87659" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Kidou Senshi Gundam Seed (Japan).zip</path>
	<name>Kidou Senshi Gundam Seed</name>
	<desc/>
	<image>./boxart/Kidou Senshi Gundam Seed (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Kidou Senshi Gundam Seed (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Kidou Senshi Gundam Seed (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Bandai</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87660" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Kidou Senshi Gundam Vol. 1 - Side 7 (Japan).zip</path>
	<name>Kidou Senshi Gundam Vol. 1 - Side 7</name>
	<desc/>
	<image>./boxart/Kidou Senshi Gundam Vol. 1 - Side 7 (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Kidou Senshi Gundam Vol. 1 - Side 7 (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Kidou Senshi Gundam Vol. 1 - Side 7 (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Bandai</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87661" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Kidou Senshi Gundam Vol. 2 - Jaburo (Japan).zip</path>
	<name>Kidou Senshi Gundam Vol. 2 - Jaburo</name>
	<desc/>
	<image>./boxart/Kidou Senshi Gundam Vol. 2 - Jaburo (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Kidou Senshi Gundam Vol. 2 - Jaburo (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Kidou Senshi Gundam Vol. 2 - Jaburo (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Bandai</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87662" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Kidou Senshi Gundam Vol. 3 - A Baoa Qu (Japan).zip</path>
	<name>Kidou Senshi Gundam Vol. 3 - A Baoa Qu</name>
	<desc/>
	<image>./boxart/Kidou Senshi Gundam Vol. 3 - A Baoa Qu (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Kidou Senshi Gundam Vol. 3 - A Baoa Qu (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Kidou Senshi Gundam Vol. 3 - A Baoa Qu (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Bandai</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87652" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Kinnikuman IIsei - Choujin Seisenshi (Japan).zip</path>
	<name>Kinnikuman IIsei - Choujin Seisenshi</name>
	<desc/>
	<image>./boxart/Kinnikuman IIsei - Choujin Seisenshi (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Kinnikuman IIsei - Choujin Seisenshi (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Kinnikuman IIsei - Choujin Seisenshi (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Bandai</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87653" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Kinnikuman IIsei - Dream Tag Match (Japan).zip</path>
	<name>Kinnikuman IIsei - Dream Tag Match</name>
	<desc>The gameplay in this game is really simple, and you don't even have to understand Japanese in order </desc>
	<image>./boxart/Kinnikuman IIsei - Dream Tag Match (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Kinnikuman IIsei - Dream Tag Match (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Kinnikuman IIsei - Dream Tag Match (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Tose. Co. Ltd.</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87654" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Kurupara! (Japan).zip</path>
	<name>Kurupara!</name>
	<desc/>
	<image>./boxart/Kurupara! (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Kurupara! (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Kurupara! (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Tomcreate</developer>
	<publisher>Tomcreate</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87655" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Last Alive (Japan).zip</path>
	<name>Last Alive</name>
	<desc>Perhaps not the most 'Adventureous" adventure game.</desc>
	<image>./boxart/Last Alive (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Last Alive (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Last Alive (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Bandai</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87636" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Makai Toushi SaGa (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<name>Makai Toushi Sa-Ga</name>
	<desc/>
	<image>./boxart/Makai Toushi SaGa (Japan) (Translated En).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Makai Toushi SaGa (Japan) (Translated En).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Makai Toushi SaGa (Japan) (Translated En).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Square Co., Ltd.</developer>
	<publisher>Square Co., Ltd.</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87630" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Meitantei Conan - Yuugure no Koujo (Japan).zip</path>
	<name>Meitantei Conan - Yuugure no Koujo</name>
	<desc/>
	<image>./boxart/Meitantei Conan - Yuugure no Koujo (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Meitantei Conan - Yuugure no Koujo (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Meitantei Conan - Yuugure no Koujo (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Bandai</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87656" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Memories Off - Festa (Japan).zip</path>
	<name>Memories Off - Festa</name>
	<desc/>
	<image>./boxart/Memories Off - Festa (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Memories Off - Festa (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Memories Off - Festa (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>KID Corp.</developer>
	<publisher>KID Corp.</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87657" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Mikeneko Holmes - Ghost Panic (Japan).zip</path>
	<name>Mikeneko Holmes - Ghost Panic</name>
	<desc/>
	<image>./boxart/Mikeneko Holmes - Ghost Panic (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Mikeneko Holmes - Ghost Panic (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Mikeneko Holmes - Ghost Panic (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>MintJulep</developer>
	<publisher>Kobunsha</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="38554" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Mr. Driller (Japan).zip</path>
	<name>Mr. Driller</name>
	<desc>Mr Driller's world has been covered with mysterious blocks. Armed with only a mighty drill, you'll have to dig your way down to safety before his air supply runs out!

Mr Driller is a real-time puzzle game that relies solely on quick-thinking and a bit of planning. Gameplay is a combination of Tetris and Boulder Dash: You have to drill down through multi-colored blocks to reach the bottom while avoiding the consequences of reckless drilling (blocks may fall on you and crush you).</desc>
	<image>./boxart/Mr. Driller (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Mr. Driller (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Mr. Driller (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Namco Limited</developer>
	<publisher>Namco Limited</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87663" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Namco Super Wars (Japan).zip</path>
	<name>Namco Super Wars</name>
	<desc/>
	<image>./boxart/Namco Super Wars (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Namco Super Wars (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Namco Super Wars (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Namco Limited</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87664" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Naruto - Konoha Ninpouchou (Japan).zip</path>
	<name>Naruto - Konoha Ninpouchou</name>
	<desc/>
	<image>./boxart/Naruto - Konoha Ninpouchou (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Naruto - Konoha Ninpouchou (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Naruto - Konoha Ninpouchou (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Bandai</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87634" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Pocket no Naka no Doraemon (Japan).zip</path>
	<name>Pocket no Naka no Doraemon</name>
	<desc/>
	<image>./boxart/Pocket no Naka no Doraemon (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Pocket no Naka no Doraemon (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Pocket no Naka no Doraemon (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Bandai</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87670" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Raku Jongg (Japan).zip</path>
	<name>Raku Jongg</name>
	<desc>Imagine Puyo Puyo or Panic Bomber, but with Mahjong tiles instead.</desc>
	<image>./boxart/Raku Jongg (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Raku Jongg (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Raku Jongg (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Enterbrain</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="38555" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Rhyme Rider Kerorican (Japan).zip</path>
	<name>Rhyme Rider Kerorican</name>
	<desc>You play as the rhyme rider Kerorcian, a vivacious space girl with a large frog helmet, as she skips to the music through the games four stages. The games music is largely comprised of jazzy techno pieces.

Kerorcian skips down a set line while randomly placed enemies and obstacles appear before her. Various button combos will avoid certain obstacles, although a "one-button" easy mode is available. When you avoid an obstacle a note will sound, clearing long chains of obstacles will result in funky melodies popping up inside the song that is playing. This gameplay is reminiscent of the studios earlier game Vib Ribbon. 

Some of the obstacles are interactive, such as a rocket one can jump on and ride a short distance, others can merely be kicked out of the way or jumped over.

Occasionally a crown will appear over an obstacle, if you successfully clear it you will briefly soar over the stage avoiding anything that might have been in your path. This is especially common before obstacles that might require outlandish button combos.</desc>
	<image>./boxart/Rhyme Rider Kerorican (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Rhyme Rider Kerorican (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Rhyme Rider Kerorican (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>NanaOn-Sha Co., Ltd.</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai Co., Ltd.</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87671" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Riviera - Yakusoku no Chi Riviera (Japan).zip</path>
	<name>Riviera - Yakusoku no Chi Riviera</name>
	<desc/>
	<image>./boxart/Riviera - Yakusoku no Chi Riviera (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Riviera - Yakusoku no Chi Riviera (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Riviera - Yakusoku no Chi Riviera (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Sting</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87672" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Rockman EXE - N1 Battle (Japan).zip</path>
	<name>Rockman EXE - N1 Battle</name>
	<desc/>
	<image>./boxart/Rockman EXE - N1 Battle (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Rockman EXE - N1 Battle (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Rockman EXE - N1 Battle (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Capcom Co., Ltd.</developer>
	<publisher>Capcom Co., Ltd.</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87673" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Rockman EXE WS (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<name>Rockman EXE WS</name>
	<desc/>
	<image>./boxart/Rockman EXE WS (Japan) (Translated En).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Rockman EXE WS (Japan) (Translated En).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Rockman EXE WS (Japan) (Translated En).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Capcom Co., Ltd.</developer>
	<publisher>Capcom Co., Ltd.</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="38557" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Romancing SaGa (Japan).zip</path>
	<name>Romancing SaGa</name>
	<desc>Once upon a time, three evil gods fought against the holy gods, and the holy God-Father chose a human warrior to help them. Finally, after a prolonged, terrible war, the leader of the three evil gods - Death, the eldest of them - surrendered. The youngest evil god, Schirach, became a human and has lost her powers. The middle one, Saruin, was sealed away in the dark world. Now, after thousand years have passed, and the seal of Saruin has weakened, it is time for you, the hero of the new generation, to defeat him.

Romancing SaGa is the fourth installment in the long SaGa series - non-linear role-playing games with several main heroes. It is the first of three Super Nintendo entries. The first three games in the series were on the Gameboy and were known as "Final Fantasy Legend" outside of Japan. In this game, you play the stories of eight characters, which will later unite to face the ultimate evil. The eight characters belong to different classes and have different abilities. There are four male characters (noble son, thief, adventurer, and pirate), and four female ones (nomad, ranger, dancer, and savage). The combat is turn-based, with enemies visible on screen. Taking a cue from Final Fantasy II on the NES, instead of "Leveling" your character as a whole you level specific abilities such as a type of weapon or magic, as well as, stats such as HP and Strength and Intelligence. New to this entry abilities are randomly unlocked during battle as a light-bulb appears over the characters head and the new ability is unleashed to the surprise of friend and foe. This serendipitous element of gameplay along with the multiple heroes to choose from greatly enhance the replay value as no two playthroughs are alike. Which is good considering the steep learning curve of the SaGa games which require multiple playthroughs to truly master the system.

"Romancing SaGa" was never released outside of Japan until the Playstation 2 remake "Romancing SaGa: Minstrel Song"</desc>
	<image>./boxart/Romancing SaGa (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Romancing SaGa (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Romancing SaGa (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Square Co., Ltd.</developer>
	<publisher>Square Co., Ltd.</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87675" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./RUN=DIM - Return to Earth (Japan).zip</path>
	<name>RUN=DIM - Return to Earth</name>
	<desc/>
	<image>./boxart/RUN=DIM - Return to Earth (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/RUN=DIM - Return to Earth (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/RUN=DIM - Return to Earth (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Digital Dream Inc.</developer>
	<publisher>Digital Dream Inc.</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87676" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Saint Seiya - Ougon Densetsuhen Perfect Edition (Japan).zip</path>
	<name>Saint Seiya - Ougon Densetsu Hen - Perfect Edition</name>
	<desc/>
	<image>./boxart/Saint Seiya - Ougon Densetsuhen Perfect Edition (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Saint Seiya - Ougon Densetsuhen Perfect Edition (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Saint Seiya - Ougon Densetsuhen Perfect Edition (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Bandai</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87680" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./SD Gundam - Operation U.C. (Japan).zip</path>
	<name>SD Gundam - Operation U.C.</name>
	<desc>When you start playing the game and reach the main menu, you will have some things which you can cho</desc>
	<image>./boxart/SD Gundam - Operation U.C. (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/SD Gundam - Operation U.C. (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/SD Gundam - Operation U.C. (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Bandai</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87679" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./SD Gundam Eiyuuden - Kishi Densetsu (Japan).zip</path>
	<name>SD Gundam Eiyuuden - Kishi Densetsu</name>
	<desc/>
	<image>./boxart/SD Gundam Eiyuuden - Kishi Densetsu (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/SD Gundam Eiyuuden - Kishi Densetsu (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/SD Gundam Eiyuuden - Kishi Densetsu (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Bandai</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87681" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./SD Gundam Eiyuuden - Musha Densetsu (Japan).zip</path>
	<name>SD Gundam Eiyuuden - Musha Densetsu</name>
	<desc/>
	<image>./boxart/SD Gundam Eiyuuden - Musha Densetsu (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/SD Gundam Eiyuuden - Musha Densetsu (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/SD Gundam Eiyuuden - Musha Densetsu (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Bandai</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87677" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./SD Gundam G-Generation - Gather Beat 2 (Japan).zip</path>
	<name>SD Gundam G-Generation - Gather Beat 2</name>
	<desc/>
	<image>./boxart/SD Gundam G-Generation - Gather Beat 2 (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/SD Gundam G-Generation - Gather Beat 2 (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/SD Gundam G-Generation - Gather Beat 2 (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Bandai</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87678" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./SD Gundam G-Generation - Mono-Eye Gundams (Japan).zip</path>
	<name>SD Gundam G-Generation - Mono-Eye Gundams</name>
	<desc/>
	<image>./boxart/SD Gundam G-Generation - Mono-Eye Gundams (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/SD Gundam G-Generation - Mono-Eye Gundams (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/SD Gundam G-Generation - Mono-Eye Gundams (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Bandai</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87684" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Senkaiden Ni - TV Animation Senkaiden Houshin Engi Yori (Japan).zip</path>
	<name>Senkaiden Ni - TV Animation Senkaiden Houshin Engi</name>
	<desc>A beautiful female fox spirit named Dakki is controlling the emperor Chu-o and the ruling In dynasty, and is using her power over him to do evil in the nation. An immortal-in-training named Taikobo is chosen by the gr</desc>
	<image>./boxart/Senkaiden Ni - TV Animation Senkaiden Houshin Engi Yori (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Senkaiden Ni - TV Animation Senkaiden Houshin Engi Yori (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Senkaiden Ni - TV Animation Senkaiden Houshin Engi Yori (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Bandai</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87682" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Shaman King - Asu e no Ishi (Japan).zip</path>
	<name>Shaman King - Asu heno Ishi</name>
	<desc/>
	<image>./boxart/Shaman King - Asu e no Ishi (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Shaman King - Asu e no Ishi (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Shaman King - Asu e no Ishi (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Bandai</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87683" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Soroban Gu (Japan).zip</path>
	<name>Sorobang</name>
	<desc/>
	<image>./boxart/Soroban Gu (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Soroban Gu (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Soroban Gu (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Mechanic Arms</developer>
	<publisher>Naxat Soft</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87686" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Star Hearts - Hoshi to Daichi no Shisha (Japan).zip</path>
	<name>Star Hearts - Hoshi to Daichi no Shisha</name>
	<desc/>
	<image>./boxart/Star Hearts - Hoshi to Daichi no Shisha (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Star Hearts - Hoshi to Daichi no Shisha (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Star Hearts - Hoshi to Daichi no Shisha (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Bandai</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87689" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Super Robot Taisen Compact 3 (Japan).zip</path>
	<name>Super Robot Taisen Compact 3</name>
	<desc>As in most games of this type, you will mainly be playing in a story mode. As you progress through it, you will receive new a</desc>
	<image>./boxart/Super Robot Taisen Compact 3 (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Super Robot Taisen Compact 3 (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Super Robot Taisen Compact 3 (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Banpresto</developer>
	<publisher>Banpresto</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87688" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Super Robot Taisen Compact for WonderSwan Color (Japan).zip</path>
	<name>Super Robot Taisen Compact for WonderSwan Color</name>
	<desc>During battle, the player chooses a unit and takes an action by the commands available, such as movement, attacking, forming squads an</desc>
	<image>./boxart/Super Robot Taisen Compact for WonderSwan Color (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Super Robot Taisen Compact for WonderSwan Color (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Super Robot Taisen Compact for WonderSwan Color (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Banpresto</developer>
	<publisher>Banpresto</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="38558" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Terrors 2 (Japan).zip</path>
	<name>Terrors 2</name>
	<desc>Terrors 2 is a interactive text-based story with accompanying images that feature the following Japanese pop stars: Risa Goto, Kaori Manabe, Erika Yamakawa, Nami Ichinohe, Yumi Uehara. The games story is one of horror slowly sneaking into a Japanese school. The plot is revealed through four scenarios. The choices you make in the story will affect the path it takes, as such there are numerous alternate ending to encourage multiple playthroughs. 

Terrors 2 could connect to the internet with the WonderGate so that ingame events would take place at the same time of day that the player was experiencing.</desc>
	<image>./boxart/Terrors 2 (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Terrors 2 (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Terrors 2 (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Terrors 2 Project</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai Co., Ltd.</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87690" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Tetris (Japan).zip</path>
	<name>Tetris</name>
	<desc> Geometric shapes fall from the top of a playfield to rest on the bottom; fit the pieces together, and the line they form disappears. If the pieces don't form lin</desc>
	<image>./boxart/Tetris (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Tetris (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Tetris (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Elorg</developer>
	<publisher>Vanguard Works</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87691" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Tonpuusou (Japan).zip</path>
	<name>Tonpuusou</name>
	<desc>Standard play mechanics, though an understanding of Japanese is an advantage.</desc>
	<image>./boxart/Tonpuusou (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Tonpuusou (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Tonpuusou (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Bandai</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87685" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Uchuu Senkan Yamato (Japan).zip</path>
	<name>Uchuu Senkan Yamato</name>
	<desc>Yamato is a flying naval ship and also the believed to be the essence of the Japanese spirit. The ga</desc>
	<image>./boxart/Uchuu Senkan Yamato (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Uchuu Senkan Yamato (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Uchuu Senkan Yamato (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Tom Create Co., Ltd.</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87692" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Ultraman - Hikari no Kuni no Shisha (Japan).zip</path>
	<name>Ultraman - Hikari no Kuni no Shisha</name>
	<desc>Sinister aliens and giant monsters are constantly threatening civilization. The only Earth organization equipped to handle these disasters is the Science Special Search Party (SSSP), a special police force with br</desc>
	<image>./boxart/Ultraman - Hikari no Kuni no Shisha (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Ultraman - Hikari no Kuni no Shisha (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Ultraman - Hikari no Kuni no Shisha (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Bandai</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="38559" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Wild Card (Japan).zip</path>
	<name>Wild Card</name>
	<desc>Although made by  Square, the famous Japanese RPG developer, "Wild Card" is a game that is very different from classic Asian RPGs. Most importantly, it is not story-driven. The game is based entirely on quests which are not connected by a story arc. You play a nameless character with no background and there is no plot information or development beside your own progress with the quests. The gameplay consists entirely of playing cards. In the beginning of the game, an enigmatic woman named Maria asks you a series of questions, to determine the cards you get. After that, your character begins an adventure in a town. Locations, other characters, inventory, your movement - everything appears in form of cards. To get quests, you must choose your correspondent cards when encountering different people. You can buy weapons and equipment, and also fight enemies in turn-based combat by choosing the cards from your deck. You gain levels and become stronger in a traditional RPG fashion.</desc>
	<image>./boxart/Wild Card (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Wild Card (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Wild Card (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Square Co., Ltd.</developer>
	<publisher>Square Co., Ltd.</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="38560" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./With You - Mitsumete Itai (Japan).zip</path>
	<name>With You: Mitsumete Itai</name>
	<desc>With You is an adventure game with static graphics, in which the game advances as you choose what to do from a list of possible actions. Long time ago, a man and a woman made a promise, stating that although they were destined to be lonely souls, they should always remain together. But by a cruel joke of fate, they were separated and sealed into two jewels that were hidden for generations. Manami, who left the country 6 years before, has found one of the jewels while traveling. He will return to Japan to meet with their friends from childhood. This will entail a meeting of the two jewels again, for the second jewel seems to be owned by his father.</desc>
	<image>./boxart/With You - Mitsumete Itai (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/With You - Mitsumete Itai (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/With You - Mitsumete Itai (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Cocktail Soft</developer>
	<publisher>Shall Luck</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87694" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Wizardry Scenario 1 - Proving Grounds of the Mad Overlord (Japan).zip</path>
	<name>Wizardry Scenario 1 - Proving Grounds of the Mad O</name>
	<desc>You generate and control a party of up to six different adventurers and send them into a 3D</desc>
	<image>./boxart/Wizardry Scenario 1 - Proving Grounds of the Mad Overlord (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Wizardry Scenario 1 - Proving Grounds of the Mad Overlord (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Wizardry Scenario 1 - Proving Grounds of the Mad Overlord (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Sir-Tech Software</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="38562" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Wonder Classic (Japan).zip</path>
	<name>Wonder Classic</name>
	<desc>Wonder Classic is a golfing game where you will use different characters with specific abilities to your advantage. For example the character, Reiko Nagase nullifies the effects of wind, most others have certain benefits to certain types of shot. There are two starting characters and twenty-two unlockable and downloadable characters.

The game consists of the following modes:

1. Training: play whatever field you like as long as you like.

2. Character Get: you'll challenge your way through ten golfers, after you beat them you'll be able to play as them elsewhere in the game

3. Stroke: play against the score

4. Match: play by hole, each time golfer gets a hole he will go "1UP" while his opponent will go "1DOWN". Whoever is "UP" in the end wins. If the "DOWN" player cannot win given the number of remaining holes then the game will end.

5. Mini Battle: Driving Contest: a match contest where the golfers will only drive.

6. Mini Battle: Near-Pin: a match contest that will involve only shots near the pin.

7. Mini Course: you play on a 3-par 9 hole course, you may play against a computer if you so wish.

8. Tour: 32 contestants enter the tour, who will win? You'll have to hone your Wonder Classic golfing skills to best this. Winning in tour mode will unlock new courses.

9. Net Tour: this mode will allow you the download the best 32 Tour scores that have been uploaded via the WonderGate. And then play a tour against those people, not the real people but against their scores, in a tour. You can also upload you own scores to compare them online.

The gameplay of Wonder Classic includes the ability to use the Y-buttons to augment just how your club will come in contact with the ball, to subtlety alter its trajectory. You'll also have six "Power Shots" which will have to be carefully conserved in each match.

Using the WonderGate you could get new clubs as well as stat altering equipment, such as gloves. You also could get new characters and courses through the WonderGate as well. This feature also allowed you to see your score as part of a "global" ranking.</desc>
	<image>./boxart/Wonder Classic (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Wonder Classic (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Wonder Classic (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Namco Limited</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai Co., Ltd.</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87695" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./X - Card of Fate (Japan).zip</path>
	<name>X - Card of Fate</name>
	<desc>This is Tokyo - the keystone that keeps Earth from falling into ruin.</desc>
	<image>./boxart/X - Card of Fate (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/X - Card of Fate (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/X - Card of Fate (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Access Software</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87696" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./XI (Sai) Little (Japan).zip</path>
	<name>XI [sai] Little</name>
	<desc>"Roll the dice game will be off the edge. I know that someone you know is a famous game. Chain can not be perplexed in the beginning, when man used to enjoy! Highly addictive puzzle. I </desc>
	<image>./boxart/XI (Sai) Little (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/XI (Sai) Little (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/XI (Sai) Little (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>MBI Limited</developer>
	<publisher>Namco Limited</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="38532" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Alchemist Marie &amp; Elie - Futari no Atelier (Japan).wsc</path>
	<name>Alchemist Marie &amp; Elie: Futari no Atelier</name>
	<desc>In the city of Salburg, there has always been a long tradition of alchemy - a magical science that dealt with combining various materials and turning metals into gold. You play as two young girls, Marlone and Elvira, who have to study at the Academy of alchemy, make powerful items, and prove to their masters they are worthy to be real alchemists.

The game is a combination of role-playing and simulation. You have to read books and talk to people in order to learn more about items, and then to buy these items or to to find them somewhere. You must combine powerful items in order to impress your teachers. You also develop your characters in a standard RPG fashion. You can equip weapons and armor on them, and fight random enemies in wilderness areas. You gain levels and become stronger the more enemies you fight. The battles are automatic, and you can only assign a general strategy to your characters.</desc>
	<image>./boxart/Alchemist Marie &amp; Elie - Futari no Atelier (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Alchemist Marie &amp; Elie - Futari no Atelier (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Alchemist Marie &amp; Elie - Futari no Atelier (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Gust Co., Ltd.</developer>
	<publisher>Gust Co., Ltd.</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="46274" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Another Heaven - Memory of those Days (Japan).wsc</path>
	<name>Another Heaven - Memory of those Days</name>
	<desc>Another Heaven: Memory of Those Days is an Adventure game, developed and published by Omega Micott, which was released in Japan in 2000.</desc>
	<image>./boxart/Another Heaven - Memory of those Days (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Another Heaven - Memory of those Days (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Another Heaven - Memory of those Days (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer/>
	<publisher/>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="38533" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Arc the Lad - Kishin Fukkatsu (Japan).wsc</path>
	<name>Arc the Lad: Kijin Fukkatsu</name>
	<desc>Two generations ago, there was a great battle between the humans and the machines. Led by their evil god, the machines were eventually able to win the battle and to take control over the world. You play the role of Elc, the hero of  Arc the Lad 2. As always, Elc is a freelance mercenary who gets assignments from his guild. He encounters Finia, a girl who belonged to a resistance group and whose mother was killed by the machines. With the help of other friends, the heroes must save the humanity and restore the world to normal.

This is a side-story in Arc the Lad series, set in a futuristic environment. As in the classic Arc the Lad games, the entire dungeon navigation is perceived as a series of continuous battles. You move your heroes in turn-based mode, and enemies use their turn to perform their moves. You can attack once an enemy is on a square near you, and also use a variety of special techniques.</desc>
	<image>./boxart/Arc the Lad - Kishin Fukkatsu (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Arc the Lad - Kishin Fukkatsu (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Arc the Lad - Kishin Fukkatsu (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Bandai Co., Ltd.</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai Co., Ltd.</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="38538" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Battle Spirit - Digimon Frontier (Japan).wsc</path>
	<name>Digimon: Battle Spirit</name>
	<desc>In 2001, an unknown digimon (digital monster) appeared. He was immensely powerful and could delete any other digimon by touching him. Very soon he gained control over the entire Digiworld. But some digimons organized a resistance group consisting of seven most venerable members. Now those digital monsters must test their powers in order to finally be able to defeat the unknown evil digimon.

This is a platform fighting game based on the Digimon manga/animé series. You can fight against computer AI or in two-player mode. There are seven digimons to choose as playable characters; all are popular digimon characters from the original series, each associated with a human tamer. The battles take place on a system of platform. You can freely move around, jump, and perform a variety of melee and long-ranged attacks. Oppoenents can also inflict status ailments on each other. In each location there are random events happening, which influence the performance of the combatants.</desc>
	<image>./boxart/Battle Spirit - Digimon Frontier (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Battle Spirit - Digimon Frontier (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Battle Spirit - Digimon Frontier (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Dimps Corporation</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai Co., Ltd.</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="38534" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Blue Wing Blitz (Japan).wsc</path>
	<name>Blue Wing Blitz</name>
	<desc>There are six nations living in the world of floating islands. The most powerful one is the Ordia Empire, possessing the best aircrafts in the world. But its leaders were hungry for even more power, and planned to invade and to occupy the other five nations. The other nations tried to maintain diplomatic relationship with the Empire as long as possible. But one of those countries, the Esk Republic, decided to send a special strike team of skillful pilots, attempting to initiate a secret rebellion against the Empire. A young pilot named Keid, guided by his senior partner, the girl Payer, is the one who was chosen for this mission.

"Blue Wing Blitz" is a turn-based strategy RPG with a twist: instead of fighters or soldier units, you command aircrafts. You navigate your planes over a battle field, which consists of airspaces, in round-based fashion. Once you land on a space occupied by an enemy plane, a battle follows. During those battles you have control over your aircraft, performing various attacks or defending. After several turns, the battle stops, but will resume if the enemy planes are still standing on the same space.</desc>
	<image>./boxart/Blue Wing Blitz (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Blue Wing Blitz (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Blue Wing Blitz (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Square Co., Ltd.</developer>
	<publisher>Square Co., Ltd.</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="46275" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Dark Eyes - Battle Gate (Japan).wsc</path>
	<name>Dark Eyes - Battle Gate</name>
	<desc>Dark Eyes ~ Battle Gate tells the story of a battle between two races on a pioneer planet.  This Strategy RPG also supports the WonderGate, allowing additional features to be downloaded with a cellular phone</desc>
	<image>./boxart/Dark Eyes - Battle Gate (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Dark Eyes - Battle Gate (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Dark Eyes - Battle Gate (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer/>
	<publisher/>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="38535" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Dicing Knight. (Japan) (Translated En).wsc</path>
	<name>Dicing Knight.</name>
	<desc>Dicing Knight. follows the journey of a nameless knight fighting through a series of randomly generated dungeons.  The game will start on the floor of a dungeon, your goal being to find the floors key to progress to the next floor. Eventually you will reach a dungeon boss, after you beat it youll be allowed access to a new more difficult dungeon. Dungeons are timed by a Food Gauge which when depleted will force you to exit the dungeon.

The dungeons are named:

1. Lindwurm - German term for dragon, meant to establish the mythic setting. This dungeon has a heavenly aura.
2. Shootingstar - A fiery land that will start to test your knowledge of the controls from Lindwurm.
3. Jabberwock - A whimsical land that is bathed in night. When the night shall end is unknown.
4. Quetzalcoatl - The area named for the Aztec sky god and creator. The entire map can no longer be seen.
5. Jörmungandr - The serpent that shall kill Thor. This stage is a mythic earthy setting.

The A button swings your sword and the B rings up your shield, the key items of any knight. Slashing your foes with your sword and devouring projectiles with your shield will increase your special meter, which when filled will allow you to perform a deadly special attack Shining Sword or "Blazing Sword".

One interesting features of Dicing Knight is the dicing every time you attack an enemy dice will pop out of it and roll, youll deal damage to the foe based on the rolls you get. Likewise when you are hit dice also roll to determine youre damaged. 

The Y buttons will be mapped to four different items, which can be found inside your foes. A variety of items are included in the game such as an item that will predict or alter dice rolls, a variety of stat altering potions, invincibility items, and a drill that will let you progress through dungeon wall to avoid monster filled rooms. Various orbs are also obtainable, via a lottery system, which will improve your abilities. 

After you beat the game on Knight Mode youll obtain a, Fortuner Mode, which will alter the game play, keeping the dungeon crawling style but giving you the ability to shoot to you and more of the monsters. The A button will be transformed into a double pistol, and the B will lob grenades. As well as two new specials that allow you to absorb enemy bullets or do a powerful shock attack. A new stage with a fitting title will also appear:

1. Ouroboros - The snake eating its own tail, an alchemical symbol of immortality, this dungeon rests betwixt time, eternal, and waiting.</desc>
	<image>./boxart/Dicing Knight. (Japan) (Translated En).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Dicing Knight. (Japan) (Translated En).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Dicing Knight. (Japan) (Translated En).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Platine Dispositif</developer>
	<publisher>Qute</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="38537" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Digimon - Anode Tamer &amp; Cathode Tamer (Asia).wsc</path>
	<name>Digimon Anode &amp; Cathode Tamer</name>
	<desc>This release contains the first  Digimon Adventure, both  Anode Tamer and  Cathode Tamer versions. The game is based on the manga and animé series Digimon. You play as an ordinary Japanese boy named Ryou who gets sucked into the mysterious digital world and has to help the digital monster Agumon and his friends to recruit digital monsters and send them into battles against evil ones.
</desc>
	<image>./boxart/Digimon - Anode Tamer &amp; Cathode Tamer (Asia).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Digimon - Anode Tamer &amp; Cathode Tamer (Asia).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Digimon - Anode Tamer &amp; Cathode Tamer (Asia).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Bandai Co., Ltd.</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai Co., Ltd.</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="38536" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Digimon Adventure 02 - D1 Tamers (Japan).wsc</path>
	<name>Digimon Adventure 02: D1 Tamers</name>
	<desc>This is a sequel to  Digimon Adventure 02: Tag Tamers, set in the world of digital monsters based on the popular manga series. After having defeated the evil Millenniumon, our hero Ryou thought that would be his last travel to the Digiworld. However, the four sacred Digimons summon him once again, to participate in the D1 monster fighting tournament. But that is not all: it appears that Millenniumon is still alive, and is looking for revenge! Now Ryou has to win the tournament and defeat his archenemy once again.

The gameplay is nearly identical to that of the previous game. You travel through top-down and isometric locations, fighting monsters with your own monster team, and then recruiting new monsters and assembling a collection. The battles are turn-based and are viewed from an isometric perspective. The monsters have various kinds of attacks in their disposal. Each attack is shown as a short animated sequence.</desc>
	<image>./boxart/Digimon Adventure 02 - D1 Tamers (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Digimon Adventure 02 - D1 Tamers (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Digimon Adventure 02 - D1 Tamers (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>SIMS Co., Ltd.</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai Co., Ltd.</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87632" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Digimon Tamers - Battle Spirit (Japan).wsc</path>
	<name>Digimon Tamers - Battle Spirit</name>
	<desc/>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Dimps Corporation</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players>1-2</players>
</game>
<game id="38538" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Digimon Tamers - Battle Spirit Ver. 1.5 (Japan).wsc</path>
	<name>Digimon: Battle Spirit</name>
	<desc>In 2001, an unknown digimon (digital monster) appeared. He was immensely powerful and could delete any other digimon by touching him. Very soon he gained control over the entire Digiworld. But some digimons organized a resistance group consisting of seven most venerable members. Now those digital monsters must test their powers in order to finally be able to defeat the unknown evil digimon.

This is a platform fighting game based on the Digimon manga/animé series. You can fight against computer AI or in two-player mode. There are seven digimons to choose as playable characters; all are popular digimon characters from the original series, each associated with a human tamer. The battles take place on a system of platform. You can freely move around, jump, and perform a variety of melee and long-ranged attacks. Oppoenents can also inflict status ailments on each other. In each location there are random events happening, which influence the performance of the combatants.</desc>
	<image>./boxart/Digimon Tamers - Battle Spirit Ver. 1.5 (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Digimon Tamers - Battle Spirit Ver. 1.5 (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Digimon Tamers - Battle Spirit Ver. 1.5 (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Dimps Corporation</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai Co., Ltd.</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="38539" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Digimon Tamers - Brave Tamer (Japan).wsc</path>
	<name>Digimon Tamers: Brave Tamer</name>
	<desc>Based on the popular Digimon manga, this is a sequel to  Digimon Adventure 02: D1 Tamers. The game picks up directly where the previous one ended. After yet another ultimate battle against the evil Millenniumon, during which he revealed to the hero Ryou a terrifying secret, there was a great explosion. Ryou comes to his senses in an unknown place. The only digital monster there explains to him that the explosion send Millenniumon to the future, while Ryou ended up in the past. And now Millenniumon is trying to take control over the main computer in the Digiworld, and it is Ryou's task to stop him once and for all, and to finally find the truth about his and his archenemy's identities.

The gameplay is similar to that of the predecessors: you navigate your hero over the top-down view, descend into dungeons, fight monsters in turn-based combat, recruit them into your party, and send the new teams to fight new enemies. The battle are not isometric any more, but viewed entirely as animé-style pictures. Attacks are also depicted as animated sequences.</desc>
	<image>./boxart/Digimon Tamers - Brave Tamer (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Digimon Tamers - Brave Tamer (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Digimon Tamers - Brave Tamer (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>SIMS Co., Ltd.</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai Co., Ltd.</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="38540" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Digimon Tamers - Digimon Medley (Japan).wsc</path>
	<name>Digimon Tamers: Digimon Medley</name>
	<desc>"Digimon Medley" is based on the popular manga and and animé series Digimon, in which ordinary Japanese children find a way into a digital world, where they help good digital monsters fight against evil ones. The game is not directly plot-related to  Digimon Adventure or Digimon Tamers: Brave Tamer games. Instead, it follows more closely the actual episodes of the series. You play as various characters, such as the main hero Taichi and his friend Yamato from the first episodes, as well as heroes from the Digimon Tamers sub-series: Takato, Ruki, and Lee. The game is divided into short episodes, each one of which revives one of the battles in the series. You start with Digimon Tamers, as they venture into the DigiWorld, only to meet the enigmatic digimon named Impmon, who is up to some mischief. 

Each episode can be played as one of several available characters. Each character also has his/her own digimon who fights all the battles. The battles are random and occur while you are navigating your heroes through top-down dungeons. The attacks are displayed as short animé-style sequences. During your turn, you must press the A button repeatedly to increase the power of your attack. The enemy attacks simultaneously, and you have to invest enough power in your attack in order for it to connect.</desc>
	<image>./boxart/Digimon Tamers - Digimon Medley (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Digimon Tamers - Digimon Medley (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Digimon Tamers - Digimon Medley (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Shade, Inc.</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai Co., Ltd.</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="46276" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Digital Monster - D-Project (Japan).wsc</path>
	<name>Digital Monster - D-Project</name>
	<desc>In this, the newest Digimon RPG game for the Wonderswan Color/Crystal, you're once again cast as a kid who's sent to the Digital World to save it (what else?), armed with nothing else but your partner digimon, your tamer know-how, and a machine that someh</desc>
	<image>./boxart/Digital Monster - D-Project (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Digital Monster - D-Project (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Digital Monster - D-Project (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer/>
	<publisher/>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="46277" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Digital Monster Card Game - Ver. WonderSwan Color (Japan).wsc</path>
	<name>Digital Monster Card Game - Ver. WonderSwan Color</name>
	<desc>Digimon Card Game: Ver. WonderSwan Color is the popular card game based on the anime series for the WonderSwan Color.  As you start the game, you'll talk with Takato. After the card game tutorial (or if you just skip it ), you' ll be in a menu with a list</desc>
	<image>./boxart/Digital Monster Card Game - Ver. WonderSwan Color (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Digital Monster Card Game - Ver. WonderSwan Color (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Digital Monster Card Game - Ver. WonderSwan Color (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer/>
	<publisher/>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="38541" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Dokodemo Hamster 3 - Odekake Saffron (Japan).wsc</path>
	<name>Dokodemo Hamster 3: O-Dekake Safuran</name>
	<desc>This is the third in Bandai's "hamster simulation" series. In this game, you are the "master" of a hamster. The game flows in real time, but you can interfere and perform various actions. The hamster has its own room in a house, with a table and a wheel. There are many things you can do with the hamster. You can take in to a stroll in the forest, go shopping with it, make it play with a ball, and so on. You can also perform actions unrelated to the hamster, like re-decorating the house or writing and painting on a piece of paper. The game features a point-and-click interface: you move your cursor over an object (such as hamster or calendar), which brings up an action menu.</desc>
	<image>./boxart/Dokodemo Hamster 3 - Odekake Saffron (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Dokodemo Hamster 3 - Odekake Saffron (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Dokodemo Hamster 3 - Odekake Saffron (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>BEC Co., Ltd.</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai Co., Ltd.</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="46278" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Dragon Ball (Japan).wsc</path>
	<name>Dragon Ball</name>
	<desc>The game is based on the famous Dragon Ball manga series, starring Son Goku, and spans a long time period of the hero's life. It begins with Son Goku being a mere child and meeting the mysterious Bulma who asks him to add her on her quest to find seven Dr</desc>
	<image>./boxart/Dragon Ball (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Dragon Ball (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Dragon Ball (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>TOSE</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="38543" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Final Fantasy (Japan).wsc</path>
	<name>Final Fantasy</name>
	<desc>Hironobu Sakaguchi's Final Fantasy... the first of one of the longest role-playing game series known to mankind. Final Fantasy is the game for the NES console that started it all.

The world is veiled in darkness. Winds don't blow, the seas are stormy, and the earth rots. All people can hope for is that the ancient prophecy will be finally fulfilled. "When the world is veiled in darkness, four warriors will come..." And indeed, they come - the four characters you have previously chosen. Their first quest is to free a princess from the evil Garland, and then the real journey begins...

Final Fantasy is played with an adventuring party rather than with a single character. Before the game starts, the player chooses four characters from six different classes: Fighter, Thief, Black Belt, White Mage, Red Mage, and Black Mage. Which four classes the player chooses for his characters is entirely up to him. He also gives the characters names. 

In the game, the party walks around in a top-down world, visits cities, caves, palaces and other places to buy equipment, rest and get hints and new quests, and fights baddies when they are encountered. Final Fantasy uses a turn-based combat system; the ATB (active-time battle) system from the later installments is not used. In battle, the player gives each character in order a command (attack a particular enemy, cast a spell, use an item, or try to run.) Then the characters and the enemies act in a random order. Attacked enemies and party members lose hit points, dying when they reach zero HP. When all the enemies are defeated, living party members receive experience, eventually gaining a level and improving their stats when enough experience is accumulated. Slain party members can be revived in towns for a price. 

Spells are bought in cities in special shops. The spells are divided into two categories - white magic and black magic. White Mages can only use white magic, Black Mages can only use black magic, and Red Mages can use both. Casting spells in battle uses up magic points, which, like hit points, can be restored by resting in inns.</desc>
	<image>./boxart/Final Fantasy (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Final Fantasy (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Final Fantasy (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Square Co., Ltd.</developer>
	<publisher>Square Co., Ltd.</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="38544" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Final Fantasy II (Japan).wsc</path>
	<name>Final Fantasy II</name>
	<desc>This is the fourth entry in the  Final Fantasy series. It was known as Final Fantasy II internationally, because the  second and third games were never released outside of Japan.

The military country of Baron is one of the strongest in the land, with a proud army and a majestic air force known as the Red Wings. But, while their armies are kind and loyal, the recent actions of the King are anything but. The young Captain of the Red Wings, Cecil, is ordered to steal a crystal from a village of innocent magicians, and when he questions the actions of his King, Cecil is immediately thrown out of the country and sent off to kill strange monsters. Little does he realize the price the King's actions will pay, and what the true secret of the crystals, and their powers, truly is...

This is the first Final Fantasy game that introduced the famous ATB (active-time battle) system: during the battles, you have a time indicator for each party member that tells you when this character is able to act. If it takes you too long to select a command for this character, the enemy will act without waiting for your turn. The game abandons the job system that was implemented in the first and the third game in favor of pre-set character classes (paladin, white mage, ninja, etc.) assigned to each party member.

The PlayStation version adds a new rendered intro and ending.</desc>
	<image>./boxart/Final Fantasy II (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Final Fantasy II (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Final Fantasy II (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Square Co., Ltd.</developer>
	<publisher>Square Co., Ltd.</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87635" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Final Fantasy IV (Japan).wsc</path>
	<name>Final Fantasy IV</name>
	<desc/>
	<image>./boxart/Final Fantasy IV (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Final Fantasy IV (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Final Fantasy IV (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Square Co., Ltd.</developer>
	<publisher>Square Co., Ltd.</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87637" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Final Lap Special - GT &amp; Formula Machine (Japan).wsc</path>
	<name>Final Lap Special - GT &amp; Formula Machine</name>
	<desc> For each mode, GT and Formula, you can only race as those cars in its respective tournaments whi</desc>
	<image>./boxart/Final Lap Special - GT &amp; Formula Machine (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Final Lap Special - GT &amp; Formula Machine (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Final Lap Special - GT &amp; Formula Machine (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Bandai</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87638" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Flash Koibito-kun (Japan).wsc</path>
	<name>Flash Koibito-kun</name>
	<desc/>
	<image>./boxart/Flash Koibito-kun (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Flash Koibito-kun (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Flash Koibito-kun (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Koto Laboratory</developer>
	<publisher>Kobunsha</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87665" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./From TV Animation One Piece - Chopper no Daibouken (Japan).wsc</path>
	<name>From TV Animation One Piece - Chopper no Daibouken</name>
	<desc>After the long intro has set the plot the player is given control of Chopper who's initial aim is to return to the group after unfo</desc>
	<image>./boxart/From TV Animation One Piece - Chopper no Daibouken (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/From TV Animation One Piece - Chopper no Daibouken (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/From TV Animation One Piece - Chopper no Daibouken (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Bandai</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87666" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./From TV Animation One Piece - Grand Battle Swan Colosseum (Japan).wsc</path>
	<name>From TV Animation One Piece - Grand Battle Swan Co</name>
	<desc> A real high point in the WonderSwan One Piece series </desc>
	<image>./boxart/From TV Animation One Piece - Grand Battle Swan Colosseum (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/From TV Animation One Piece - Grand Battle Swan Colosseum (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/From TV Animation One Piece - Grand Battle Swan Colosseum (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Bandai</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87667" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./From TV Animation One Piece - Niji no Shima Densetsu (Japan).wsc</path>
	<name>From TV Animation One Piece - Niji no Shima Denset</name>
	<desc/>
	<image>./boxart/From TV Animation One Piece - Niji no Shima Densetsu (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/From TV Animation One Piece - Niji no Shima Densetsu (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/From TV Animation One Piece - Niji no Shima Densetsu (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Bandai</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87668" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./From TV Animation One Piece - Treasure Wars (Japan).wsc</path>
	<name>From TV Animation One Piece - Treasure Wars</name>
	<desc/>
	<image>./boxart/From TV Animation One Piece - Treasure Wars (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/From TV Animation One Piece - Treasure Wars (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/From TV Animation One Piece - Treasure Wars (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Bandai</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87669" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./From TV Animation One Piece - Treasure Wars 2 - Buggy Land e Youkoso (Japan).wsc</path>
	<name>From TV Animation One Piece - Treasure Wars 2 - Bu</name>
	<desc>That's not to say Treasure Wars 2 is any less enjoyable just little changed; still "choose your character and att</desc>
	<image>./boxart/From TV Animation One Piece - Treasure Wars 2 - Buggy Land e Youkoso (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/From TV Animation One Piece - Treasure Wars 2 - Buggy Land e Youkoso (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/From TV Animation One Piece - Treasure Wars 2 - Buggy Land e Youkoso (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Bandai</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="38546" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Front Mission (Japan).wsc</path>
	<name>Front Mission</name>
	<desc>In the future, many military forces are dependent on huge mech robots, called Wanzers (Walking Panzers) for combat. At Huffman Island, located in the the pacific ocean, wanzers are deployed by both the USN (United States of the New Continent) and the OCU (Oceana Community Union), who dispute ownership over the island.  One night, the OCU forces stage a covert recon mission on a facility located in Larcus, a USN-held territory and weapons facility. Lead by a soldier named Roid, this mission was entirely unofficial and violated the peace treaty. During the mission, USN forces lead by Commander Driscoll appeared and ambushed the OCU soldiers. During the combat, Roid's fiance, Karen is killed and the USN facility is blown up; placing the blame on the OCU. This became known as the &amp;quot;Larcus Incident&amp;quot; and the OCU denied all knowledge of it's soldiers actions. Ultimately it would be a leading cause to the second Huffman War. 

One year later, the war is underway and Huffman island is under provisional control of the OCU, but with a weakened military unable to defend against USN attacks. The soldiers involved involved in the Larcus Incident have all been discharged and disgraced. Roid spends his time fighting as a gladiator in the Wanzer fighting arena before being approached by a mysterious man. Colonel Olson has found out about Roid's history and wants him to command a mercenary unit he is assembling on behalf of the OCU, dubbed &amp;quot;Carrion Crow&amp;quot;. Convincing Roid that Driscoll is still out there on the island, Roid agrees.

Front Mission is a turn-based strategy RPG played from an isometric perspective. Players progress in the story through large strategic battles involving multiple units and cutscenes between them. At certain places, usually towns, the player can visit multiple locations including bars and shops, and talk to people. Shops are also found to purchase new weaponry, parts and make repairs. In combat, each Wanzer robot is a seperate unit and, has a large variety of weapons and attack styles depending on what's equipped. Units get experience for defeating enemies and also for using various techniques. The more an attack is used, the more powerful it becomes.</desc>
	<image>./boxart/Front Mission (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Front Mission (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Front Mission (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>G-Craft</developer>
	<publisher>Square Co., Ltd.</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87639" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Gekitou! Crash Gear Turbo - Gear Champion League (Japan).wsc</path>
	<name>Gekitou! Crash Gear Turbo - Gear Champion League</name>
	<desc/>
	<image>./boxart/Gekitou! Crash Gear Turbo - Gear Champion League (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Gekitou! Crash Gear Turbo - Gear Champion League (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Gekitou! Crash Gear Turbo - Gear Champion League (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Bandai</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87640" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Gensou Maden Saiyuuki Retribution - Hi no Ataru Basho de (Japan).wsc</path>
	<name>Gensou Maden Saiyuuki Retribution - Hi no Ataru Ba</name>
	<desc/>
	<image>./boxart/Gensou Maden Saiyuuki Retribution - Hi no Ataru Basho de (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Gensou Maden Saiyuuki Retribution - Hi no Ataru Basho de (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Gensou Maden Saiyuuki Retribution - Hi no Ataru Basho de (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>PicPac-Airreal</developer>
	<publisher>Mubik</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="38547" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Golden Axe (Japan).wsc</path>
	<name>Golden Axe</name>
	<desc>Sega's classic arcade beat-'em-up game, Golden Axe puts in the shoes of one of three heroes, each with his own reason for trying to overthrow the evil rule of Death-Adder, who - along with his forces of darkness - kidnapped and imprisoned the King and his daughter and stole the legendary Golden Axe.

This is a horizontal fighting game, where you basically take one of the three characters (a warrior, a dwarf or an amazon) and bash everything which stands between you and Death Adder himself.</desc>
	<image>./boxart/Golden Axe (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Golden Axe (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Golden Axe (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>SEGA Enterprises Ltd.</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai Co., Ltd.</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87641" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Gransta Chronicle (Japan).wsc</path>
	<name>Gransta Chronicle</name>
	<desc>The combat adopts the simulation battle method. Because the friend or foe is disordered on the wide field, let's challenge it by making good use of the weapons, magic, and all items. The items and monsters can be </desc>
	<image>./boxart/Gransta Chronicle (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Gransta Chronicle (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Gransta Chronicle (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Tom Create Co., Ltd.</developer>
	<publisher>Omega Micott Inc.</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="38548" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Guilty Gear Petit (Japan).wsc</path>
	<name>Guilty Gear Petit</name>
	<desc>The game takes place in 22th century. Scientists developed a new technique that allowed them to merge the DNA of humans and animals, producing powerful creatures known as "gears". The characters of the game participate in a tournament, the winner of which would face a gear who went out of control and is threatening to lead a gear rebellion against the humans. The game allows you to play as familiar characters from Guilty Gear series, such as the main hero Sol Badguy, who has a certain connection to the gears, and his rival, the leader of the Holy Knights named Ky Kiske. It also introduces a new character, the nurse Fanny, who fights with a syringe and has a mysterious connection to the genius surgeon, and later serial murderer, Dr. Baldhead. 

"Guilty Gear Petit" is a 2D fighting game. The story mode lets you pick a character and take him/her through a series of fights, while in time attack mode you can choose your opponents freely. The graphics are done in "super-deformed" style. The game retains key ingredients of Guilty Gear gameplay, such as building tension in order to execute powerful attacks, combo moves, etc.</desc>
	<image>./boxart/Guilty Gear Petit (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Guilty Gear Petit (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Guilty Gear Petit (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Arc System Works Co., Ltd.</developer>
	<publisher>Sammy Corporation</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="38549" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Guilty Gear Petit 2 (Japan).wsc</path>
	<name>Guilty Gear Petit 2</name>
	<desc>In 22th century, scientists found a way to create artificial beings whom they called "gears". These gears were very powerful, but did not have wills of their own, and were completely obedient to the humans. However, a gear named Justice was able to free himself from the control and led a rebellion against the humans. Since then, the humanity lived in fear that the gears will one day gain the power on the Earth. For that purpose, the Sacred Order of the Holy Knights organized fighting tournaments to find out who is strong enough to face the renegade gears.

"Guilty Gear Petit 2" is very similar to its predecessor, having the same "super-deformed" graphical style, battle moves (including the tension system to accumulate power and combo attacks), as well as backgrounds for battles. Several new characters appear in "Guilty Gear Petit 2", such as Zato-1, the former head of the assassin guild, the pirate captain Johnny, the time traveler Axl Lou from the 20th century, the mysterious Faust, and others.</desc>
	<image>./boxart/Guilty Gear Petit 2 (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Guilty Gear Petit 2 (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Guilty Gear Petit 2 (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Arc System Works Co., Ltd.</developer>
	<publisher>Sammy Corporation</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="38550" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./GunPey EX (Japan).wsc</path>
	<name>Gunpey EX</name>
	<desc>Direct sequel to the original Gunpey on the WonderSwan, Gunpey EX adds a number of new elements to the classic; most notably, color.

In addition to earning points for completing a line across the field you will now earn points if those lines are of a matching color. Previously only gray lines were possible now red, blue, and green lines appear.

Gunpey EX has the same modes as the previous game, except a story mode. Time Attack mode where one has to eliminate as many tiles as possible in two of five minutes. Endless mode give the player unlimited time to crank out whatever score they desire. Stage mode presents a set number of tiles to remove in a given time. Puzzle mode puts the player in the situation of having to remove a certain group of tiles, the player can change the color of the lines here when they swap their tiles positions.

A link mode is available to play against another human with a WonderSwan and Gunpey EX. 

This game could access the internet through a wireless phone and the WonderGate where it was able to interact with an online high score board.</desc>
	<image>./boxart/GunPey EX (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/GunPey EX (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/GunPey EX (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Koto Laboratory</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai Co., Ltd.</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87642" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Hanjuku Hero - Ah, Sekai yo Hanjuku Nare...!! (Japan).wsc</path>
	<name>Hanjuku Hero - Ah, Sekai yo Hanjuku Nare...!!</name>
	<desc/>
	<image>./boxart/Hanjuku Hero - Ah, Sekai yo Hanjuku Nare...!! (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Hanjuku Hero - Ah, Sekai yo Hanjuku Nare...!! (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Hanjuku Hero - Ah, Sekai yo Hanjuku Nare...!! (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Square Co., Ltd.</developer>
	<publisher>Square Co., Ltd.</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87643" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Hataraku Chocobo (Japan).wsc</path>
	<name>Hataraku Chocobo</name>
	<desc>A sim featuring Square's mascot released on the WonderSwan Color in Japan only.</desc>
	<image>./boxart/Hataraku Chocobo (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Hataraku Chocobo (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Hataraku Chocobo (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Square Co., Ltd.</developer>
	<publisher>Square Co., Ltd.</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87644" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Hunter X Hunter - Greed Island (Japan).wsc</path>
	<name>Hunter X Hunter - Greed Island</name>
	<desc>When you encounter the enemy, you rush into a command selection type turn system battle on a 8x3 field mas</desc>
	<image>./boxart/Hunter X Hunter - Greed Island (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Hunter X Hunter - Greed Island (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Hunter X Hunter - Greed Island (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Bandai</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87645" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Hunter X Hunter - Michibikareshi Mono (Japan).wsc</path>
	<name>Hunter X Hunter - Michibikareshi Mono</name>
	<desc/>
	<image>./boxart/Hunter X Hunter - Michibikareshi Mono (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Hunter X Hunter - Michibikareshi Mono (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Hunter X Hunter - Michibikareshi Mono (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Bandai</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87646" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Hunter X Hunter - Sorezore no Ketsui (Japan).wsc</path>
	<name>Hunter X Hunter - Sorezore no Ketsui</name>
	<desc>The story of Hunter X Hunter focuses on a young boy named Gon Freecss, who one day discovers that the father he had always been told was dead was ali</desc>
	<image>./boxart/Hunter X Hunter - Sorezore no Ketsui (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Hunter X Hunter - Sorezore no Ketsui (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Hunter X Hunter - Sorezore no Ketsui (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Bandai</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87648" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Inuyasha - Fuuun Emaki (Japan).wsc</path>
	<name>Inuyasha - Fuuun Emaki</name>
	<desc/>
	<image>./boxart/Inuyasha - Fuuun Emaki (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Inuyasha - Fuuun Emaki (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Inuyasha - Fuuun Emaki (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Bandai</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87649" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Inuyasha - Kagome no Sengoku Nikki (Japan).wsc</path>
	<name>Inuyasha - Kagome no Sengoku Nikki</name>
	<desc/>
	<image>./boxart/Inuyasha - Kagome no Sengoku Nikki (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Inuyasha - Kagome no Sengoku Nikki (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Inuyasha - Kagome no Sengoku Nikki (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Bandai</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87650" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Inuyasha - Kagome no Yume Nikki (Japan).wsc</path>
	<name>Inuyasha - Kagome no Yume Nikki</name>
	<desc/>
	<image>./boxart/Inuyasha - Kagome no Yume Nikki (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Inuyasha - Kagome no Yume Nikki (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Inuyasha - Kagome no Yume Nikki (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Bandai</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87651" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Judgement Silversword - Rebirth Edition (Japan).wsc</path>
	<name>Judgement Silversword - Rebirth Edition</name>
	<desc/>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>M-KAI</developer>
	<publisher>Qute</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players>1</players>
</game>
<game id="87658" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Kidou Senshi Gundam - Giren no Yabou - Tokubetsu Hen - Aoki Hoshi no Hasha (Japan).wsc</path>
	<name>Kidou Senshi Gundam - Giren no Yabou - Tokubetsu H</name>
	<desc/>
	<image>./boxart/Kidou Senshi Gundam - Giren no Yabou - Tokubetsu Hen - Aoki Hoshi no Hasha (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Kidou Senshi Gundam - Giren no Yabou - Tokubetsu Hen - Aoki Hoshi no Hasha (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Kidou Senshi Gundam - Giren no Yabou - Tokubetsu Hen - Aoki Hoshi no Hasha (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Bandai</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87659" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Kidou Senshi Gundam Seed (Japan).wsc</path>
	<name>Kidou Senshi Gundam Seed</name>
	<desc/>
	<image>./boxart/Kidou Senshi Gundam Seed (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Kidou Senshi Gundam Seed (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Kidou Senshi Gundam Seed (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Bandai</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87660" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Kidou Senshi Gundam Vol. 1 - Side 7 (Japan).wsc</path>
	<name>Kidou Senshi Gundam Vol. 1 - Side 7</name>
	<desc/>
	<image>./boxart/Kidou Senshi Gundam Vol. 1 - Side 7 (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Kidou Senshi Gundam Vol. 1 - Side 7 (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Kidou Senshi Gundam Vol. 1 - Side 7 (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Bandai</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87661" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Kidou Senshi Gundam Vol. 2 - Jaburo (Japan).wsc</path>
	<name>Kidou Senshi Gundam Vol. 2 - Jaburo</name>
	<desc/>
	<image>./boxart/Kidou Senshi Gundam Vol. 2 - Jaburo (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Kidou Senshi Gundam Vol. 2 - Jaburo (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Kidou Senshi Gundam Vol. 2 - Jaburo (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Bandai</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87662" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Kidou Senshi Gundam Vol. 3 - A Baoa Qu (Japan).wsc</path>
	<name>Kidou Senshi Gundam Vol. 3 - A Baoa Qu</name>
	<desc/>
	<image>./boxart/Kidou Senshi Gundam Vol. 3 - A Baoa Qu (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Kidou Senshi Gundam Vol. 3 - A Baoa Qu (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Kidou Senshi Gundam Vol. 3 - A Baoa Qu (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Bandai</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87652" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Kinnikuman IIsei - Choujin Seisenshi (Japan).wsc</path>
	<name>Kinnikuman IIsei - Choujin Seisenshi</name>
	<desc/>
	<image>./boxart/Kinnikuman IIsei - Choujin Seisenshi (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Kinnikuman IIsei - Choujin Seisenshi (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Kinnikuman IIsei - Choujin Seisenshi (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Bandai</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87653" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Kinnikuman IIsei - Dream Tag Match (Japan).wsc</path>
	<name>Kinnikuman IIsei - Dream Tag Match</name>
	<desc>The gameplay in this game is really simple, and you don't even have to understand Japanese in order </desc>
	<image>./boxart/Kinnikuman IIsei - Dream Tag Match (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Kinnikuman IIsei - Dream Tag Match (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Kinnikuman IIsei - Dream Tag Match (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Tose. Co. Ltd.</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87654" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Kurupara! (Japan).wsc</path>
	<name>Kurupara!</name>
	<desc/>
	<image>./boxart/Kurupara! (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Kurupara! (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Kurupara! (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Tomcreate</developer>
	<publisher>Tomcreate</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87655" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Last Alive (Japan).wsc</path>
	<name>Last Alive</name>
	<desc>Perhaps not the most 'Adventureous" adventure game.</desc>
	<image>./boxart/Last Alive (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Last Alive (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Last Alive (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Bandai</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87636" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Makai Toushi SaGa (Japan) (Translated En).wsc</path>
	<name>Makai Toushi Sa-Ga</name>
	<desc/>
	<image>./boxart/Makai Toushi SaGa (Japan) (Translated En).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Makai Toushi SaGa (Japan) (Translated En).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Makai Toushi SaGa (Japan) (Translated En).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Square Co., Ltd.</developer>
	<publisher>Square Co., Ltd.</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87630" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Meitantei Conan - Yuugure no Koujo (Japan).wsc</path>
	<name>Meitantei Conan - Yuugure no Koujo</name>
	<desc/>
	<image>./boxart/Meitantei Conan - Yuugure no Koujo (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Meitantei Conan - Yuugure no Koujo (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Meitantei Conan - Yuugure no Koujo (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Bandai</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87656" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Memories Off - Festa (Japan).wsc</path>
	<name>Memories Off - Festa</name>
	<desc/>
	<image>./boxart/Memories Off - Festa (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Memories Off - Festa (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Memories Off - Festa (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>KID Corp.</developer>
	<publisher>KID Corp.</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87657" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Mikeneko Holmes - Ghost Panic (Japan).wsc</path>
	<name>Mikeneko Holmes - Ghost Panic</name>
	<desc/>
	<image>./boxart/Mikeneko Holmes - Ghost Panic (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Mikeneko Holmes - Ghost Panic (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Mikeneko Holmes - Ghost Panic (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>MintJulep</developer>
	<publisher>Kobunsha</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="38554" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Mr. Driller (Japan).wsc</path>
	<name>Mr. Driller</name>
	<desc>Mr Driller's world has been covered with mysterious blocks. Armed with only a mighty drill, you'll have to dig your way down to safety before his air supply runs out!

Mr Driller is a real-time puzzle game that relies solely on quick-thinking and a bit of planning. Gameplay is a combination of Tetris and Boulder Dash: You have to drill down through multi-colored blocks to reach the bottom while avoiding the consequences of reckless drilling (blocks may fall on you and crush you).</desc>
	<image>./boxart/Mr. Driller (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Mr. Driller (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Mr. Driller (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Namco Limited</developer>
	<publisher>Namco Limited</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87663" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Namco Super Wars (Japan).wsc</path>
	<name>Namco Super Wars</name>
	<desc/>
	<image>./boxart/Namco Super Wars (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Namco Super Wars (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Namco Super Wars (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Namco Limited</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87664" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Naruto - Konoha Ninpouchou (Japan).wsc</path>
	<name>Naruto - Konoha Ninpouchou</name>
	<desc/>
	<image>./boxart/Naruto - Konoha Ninpouchou (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Naruto - Konoha Ninpouchou (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Naruto - Konoha Ninpouchou (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Bandai</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87634" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Pocket no Naka no Doraemon (Japan).wsc</path>
	<name>Pocket no Naka no Doraemon</name>
	<desc/>
	<image>./boxart/Pocket no Naka no Doraemon (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Pocket no Naka no Doraemon (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Pocket no Naka no Doraemon (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Bandai</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87670" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Raku Jongg (Japan).wsc</path>
	<name>Raku Jongg</name>
	<desc>Imagine Puyo Puyo or Panic Bomber, but with Mahjong tiles instead.</desc>
	<image>./boxart/Raku Jongg (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Raku Jongg (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Raku Jongg (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Enterbrain</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="38555" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Rhyme Rider Kerorican (Japan).wsc</path>
	<name>Rhyme Rider Kerorican</name>
	<desc>You play as the rhyme rider Kerorcian, a vivacious space girl with a large frog helmet, as she skips to the music through the games four stages. The games music is largely comprised of jazzy techno pieces.

Kerorcian skips down a set line while randomly placed enemies and obstacles appear before her. Various button combos will avoid certain obstacles, although a "one-button" easy mode is available. When you avoid an obstacle a note will sound, clearing long chains of obstacles will result in funky melodies popping up inside the song that is playing. This gameplay is reminiscent of the studios earlier game Vib Ribbon. 

Some of the obstacles are interactive, such as a rocket one can jump on and ride a short distance, others can merely be kicked out of the way or jumped over.

Occasionally a crown will appear over an obstacle, if you successfully clear it you will briefly soar over the stage avoiding anything that might have been in your path. This is especially common before obstacles that might require outlandish button combos.</desc>
	<image>./boxart/Rhyme Rider Kerorican (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Rhyme Rider Kerorican (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Rhyme Rider Kerorican (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>NanaOn-Sha Co., Ltd.</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai Co., Ltd.</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87671" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Riviera - Yakusoku no Chi Riviera (Japan).wsc</path>
	<name>Riviera - Yakusoku no Chi Riviera</name>
	<desc/>
	<image>./boxart/Riviera - Yakusoku no Chi Riviera (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Riviera - Yakusoku no Chi Riviera (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Riviera - Yakusoku no Chi Riviera (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Sting</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87672" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Rockman EXE - N1 Battle (Japan).wsc</path>
	<name>Rockman EXE - N1 Battle</name>
	<desc/>
	<image>./boxart/Rockman EXE - N1 Battle (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Rockman EXE - N1 Battle (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Rockman EXE - N1 Battle (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Capcom Co., Ltd.</developer>
	<publisher>Capcom Co., Ltd.</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87673" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Rockman EXE WS (Japan) (Translated En).wsc</path>
	<name>Rockman EXE WS</name>
	<desc/>
	<image>./boxart/Rockman EXE WS (Japan) (Translated En).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Rockman EXE WS (Japan) (Translated En).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Rockman EXE WS (Japan) (Translated En).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Capcom Co., Ltd.</developer>
	<publisher>Capcom Co., Ltd.</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="38557" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Romancing SaGa (Japan).wsc</path>
	<name>Romancing SaGa</name>
	<desc>Once upon a time, three evil gods fought against the holy gods, and the holy God-Father chose a human warrior to help them. Finally, after a prolonged, terrible war, the leader of the three evil gods - Death, the eldest of them - surrendered. The youngest evil god, Schirach, became a human and has lost her powers. The middle one, Saruin, was sealed away in the dark world. Now, after thousand years have passed, and the seal of Saruin has weakened, it is time for you, the hero of the new generation, to defeat him.

Romancing SaGa is the fourth installment in the long SaGa series - non-linear role-playing games with several main heroes. It is the first of three Super Nintendo entries. The first three games in the series were on the Gameboy and were known as "Final Fantasy Legend" outside of Japan. In this game, you play the stories of eight characters, which will later unite to face the ultimate evil. The eight characters belong to different classes and have different abilities. There are four male characters (noble son, thief, adventurer, and pirate), and four female ones (nomad, ranger, dancer, and savage). The combat is turn-based, with enemies visible on screen. Taking a cue from Final Fantasy II on the NES, instead of "Leveling" your character as a whole you level specific abilities such as a type of weapon or magic, as well as, stats such as HP and Strength and Intelligence. New to this entry abilities are randomly unlocked during battle as a light-bulb appears over the characters head and the new ability is unleashed to the surprise of friend and foe. This serendipitous element of gameplay along with the multiple heroes to choose from greatly enhance the replay value as no two playthroughs are alike. Which is good considering the steep learning curve of the SaGa games which require multiple playthroughs to truly master the system.

"Romancing SaGa" was never released outside of Japan until the Playstation 2 remake "Romancing SaGa: Minstrel Song"</desc>
	<image>./boxart/Romancing SaGa (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Romancing SaGa (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Romancing SaGa (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Square Co., Ltd.</developer>
	<publisher>Square Co., Ltd.</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87675" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./RUN=DIM - Return to Earth (Japan).wsc</path>
	<name>RUN=DIM - Return to Earth</name>
	<desc/>
	<image>./boxart/RUN=DIM - Return to Earth (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/RUN=DIM - Return to Earth (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/RUN=DIM - Return to Earth (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Digital Dream Inc.</developer>
	<publisher>Digital Dream Inc.</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87676" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Saint Seiya - Ougon Densetsuhen Perfect Edition (Japan).wsc</path>
	<name>Saint Seiya - Ougon Densetsu Hen - Perfect Edition</name>
	<desc/>
	<image>./boxart/Saint Seiya - Ougon Densetsuhen Perfect Edition (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Saint Seiya - Ougon Densetsuhen Perfect Edition (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Saint Seiya - Ougon Densetsuhen Perfect Edition (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Bandai</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87680" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./SD Gundam - Operation U.C. (Japan).wsc</path>
	<name>SD Gundam - Operation U.C.</name>
	<desc>When you start playing the game and reach the main menu, you will have some things which you can cho</desc>
	<image>./boxart/SD Gundam - Operation U.C. (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/SD Gundam - Operation U.C. (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/SD Gundam - Operation U.C. (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Bandai</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87679" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./SD Gundam Eiyuuden - Kishi Densetsu (Japan).wsc</path>
	<name>SD Gundam Eiyuuden - Kishi Densetsu</name>
	<desc/>
	<image>./boxart/SD Gundam Eiyuuden - Kishi Densetsu (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/SD Gundam Eiyuuden - Kishi Densetsu (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/SD Gundam Eiyuuden - Kishi Densetsu (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Bandai</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87681" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./SD Gundam Eiyuuden - Musha Densetsu (Japan).wsc</path>
	<name>SD Gundam Eiyuuden - Musha Densetsu</name>
	<desc/>
	<image>./boxart/SD Gundam Eiyuuden - Musha Densetsu (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/SD Gundam Eiyuuden - Musha Densetsu (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/SD Gundam Eiyuuden - Musha Densetsu (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Bandai</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87677" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./SD Gundam G-Generation - Gather Beat 2 (Japan).wsc</path>
	<name>SD Gundam G-Generation - Gather Beat 2</name>
	<desc/>
	<image>./boxart/SD Gundam G-Generation - Gather Beat 2 (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/SD Gundam G-Generation - Gather Beat 2 (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/SD Gundam G-Generation - Gather Beat 2 (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Bandai</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87678" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./SD Gundam G-Generation - Mono-Eye Gundams (Japan).wsc</path>
	<name>SD Gundam G-Generation - Mono-Eye Gundams</name>
	<desc/>
	<image>./boxart/SD Gundam G-Generation - Mono-Eye Gundams (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/SD Gundam G-Generation - Mono-Eye Gundams (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/SD Gundam G-Generation - Mono-Eye Gundams (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Bandai</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87684" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Senkaiden Ni - TV Animation Senkaiden Houshin Engi Yori (Japan).wsc</path>
	<name>Senkaiden Ni - TV Animation Senkaiden Houshin Engi</name>
	<desc>A beautiful female fox spirit named Dakki is controlling the emperor Chu-o and the ruling In dynasty, and is using her power over him to do evil in the nation. An immortal-in-training named Taikobo is chosen by the gr</desc>
	<image>./boxart/Senkaiden Ni - TV Animation Senkaiden Houshin Engi Yori (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Senkaiden Ni - TV Animation Senkaiden Houshin Engi Yori (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Senkaiden Ni - TV Animation Senkaiden Houshin Engi Yori (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Bandai</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87682" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Shaman King - Asu e no Ishi (Japan).wsc</path>
	<name>Shaman King - Asu heno Ishi</name>
	<desc/>
	<image>./boxart/Shaman King - Asu e no Ishi (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Shaman King - Asu e no Ishi (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Shaman King - Asu e no Ishi (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Bandai</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87683" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Soroban Gu (Japan).wsc</path>
	<name>Sorobang</name>
	<desc/>
	<image>./boxart/Soroban Gu (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Soroban Gu (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Soroban Gu (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Mechanic Arms</developer>
	<publisher>Naxat Soft</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87686" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Star Hearts - Hoshi to Daichi no Shisha (Japan).wsc</path>
	<name>Star Hearts - Hoshi to Daichi no Shisha</name>
	<desc/>
	<image>./boxart/Star Hearts - Hoshi to Daichi no Shisha (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Star Hearts - Hoshi to Daichi no Shisha (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Star Hearts - Hoshi to Daichi no Shisha (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Bandai</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87689" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Super Robot Taisen Compact 3 (Japan).wsc</path>
	<name>Super Robot Taisen Compact 3</name>
	<desc>As in most games of this type, you will mainly be playing in a story mode. As you progress through it, you will receive new a</desc>
	<image>./boxart/Super Robot Taisen Compact 3 (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Super Robot Taisen Compact 3 (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Super Robot Taisen Compact 3 (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Banpresto</developer>
	<publisher>Banpresto</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87688" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Super Robot Taisen Compact for WonderSwan Color (Japan).wsc</path>
	<name>Super Robot Taisen Compact for WonderSwan Color</name>
	<desc>During battle, the player chooses a unit and takes an action by the commands available, such as movement, attacking, forming squads an</desc>
	<image>./boxart/Super Robot Taisen Compact for WonderSwan Color (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Super Robot Taisen Compact for WonderSwan Color (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Super Robot Taisen Compact for WonderSwan Color (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Banpresto</developer>
	<publisher>Banpresto</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="38558" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Terrors 2 (Japan).wsc</path>
	<name>Terrors 2</name>
	<desc>Terrors 2 is a interactive text-based story with accompanying images that feature the following Japanese pop stars: Risa Goto, Kaori Manabe, Erika Yamakawa, Nami Ichinohe, Yumi Uehara. The games story is one of horror slowly sneaking into a Japanese school. The plot is revealed through four scenarios. The choices you make in the story will affect the path it takes, as such there are numerous alternate ending to encourage multiple playthroughs. 

Terrors 2 could connect to the internet with the WonderGate so that ingame events would take place at the same time of day that the player was experiencing.</desc>
	<image>./boxart/Terrors 2 (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Terrors 2 (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Terrors 2 (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Terrors 2 Project</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai Co., Ltd.</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87690" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Tetris (Japan).wsc</path>
	<name>Tetris</name>
	<desc> Geometric shapes fall from the top of a playfield to rest on the bottom; fit the pieces together, and the line they form disappears. If the pieces don't form lin</desc>
	<image>./boxart/Tetris (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Tetris (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Tetris (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Elorg</developer>
	<publisher>Vanguard Works</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87691" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Tonpuusou (Japan).wsc</path>
	<name>Tonpuusou</name>
	<desc>Standard play mechanics, though an understanding of Japanese is an advantage.</desc>
	<image>./boxart/Tonpuusou (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Tonpuusou (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Tonpuusou (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Bandai</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87685" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Uchuu Senkan Yamato (Japan).wsc</path>
	<name>Uchuu Senkan Yamato</name>
	<desc>Yamato is a flying naval ship and also the believed to be the essence of the Japanese spirit. The ga</desc>
	<image>./boxart/Uchuu Senkan Yamato (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Uchuu Senkan Yamato (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Uchuu Senkan Yamato (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Tom Create Co., Ltd.</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87692" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Ultraman - Hikari no Kuni no Shisha (Japan).wsc</path>
	<name>Ultraman - Hikari no Kuni no Shisha</name>
	<desc>Sinister aliens and giant monsters are constantly threatening civilization. The only Earth organization equipped to handle these disasters is the Science Special Search Party (SSSP), a special police force with br</desc>
	<image>./boxart/Ultraman - Hikari no Kuni no Shisha (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Ultraman - Hikari no Kuni no Shisha (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Ultraman - Hikari no Kuni no Shisha (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Bandai</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="38559" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Wild Card (Japan).wsc</path>
	<name>Wild Card</name>
	<desc>Although made by  Square, the famous Japanese RPG developer, "Wild Card" is a game that is very different from classic Asian RPGs. Most importantly, it is not story-driven. The game is based entirely on quests which are not connected by a story arc. You play a nameless character with no background and there is no plot information or development beside your own progress with the quests. The gameplay consists entirely of playing cards. In the beginning of the game, an enigmatic woman named Maria asks you a series of questions, to determine the cards you get. After that, your character begins an adventure in a town. Locations, other characters, inventory, your movement - everything appears in form of cards. To get quests, you must choose your correspondent cards when encountering different people. You can buy weapons and equipment, and also fight enemies in turn-based combat by choosing the cards from your deck. You gain levels and become stronger in a traditional RPG fashion.</desc>
	<image>./boxart/Wild Card (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Wild Card (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Wild Card (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Square Co., Ltd.</developer>
	<publisher>Square Co., Ltd.</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="38560" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./With You - Mitsumete Itai (Japan).wsc</path>
	<name>With You: Mitsumete Itai</name>
	<desc>With You is an adventure game with static graphics, in which the game advances as you choose what to do from a list of possible actions. Long time ago, a man and a woman made a promise, stating that although they were destined to be lonely souls, they should always remain together. But by a cruel joke of fate, they were separated and sealed into two jewels that were hidden for generations. Manami, who left the country 6 years before, has found one of the jewels while traveling. He will return to Japan to meet with their friends from childhood. This will entail a meeting of the two jewels again, for the second jewel seems to be owned by his father.</desc>
	<image>./boxart/With You - Mitsumete Itai (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/With You - Mitsumete Itai (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/With You - Mitsumete Itai (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Cocktail Soft</developer>
	<publisher>Shall Luck</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87694" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Wizardry Scenario 1 - Proving Grounds of the Mad Overlord (Japan).wsc</path>
	<name>Wizardry Scenario 1 - Proving Grounds of the Mad O</name>
	<desc>You generate and control a party of up to six different adventurers and send them into a 3D</desc>
	<image>./boxart/Wizardry Scenario 1 - Proving Grounds of the Mad Overlord (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Wizardry Scenario 1 - Proving Grounds of the Mad Overlord (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Wizardry Scenario 1 - Proving Grounds of the Mad Overlord (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Sir-Tech Software</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="38562" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Wonder Classic (Japan).wsc</path>
	<name>Wonder Classic</name>
	<desc>Wonder Classic is a golfing game where you will use different characters with specific abilities to your advantage. For example the character, Reiko Nagase nullifies the effects of wind, most others have certain benefits to certain types of shot. There are two starting characters and twenty-two unlockable and downloadable characters.

The game consists of the following modes:

1. Training: play whatever field you like as long as you like.

2. Character Get: you'll challenge your way through ten golfers, after you beat them you'll be able to play as them elsewhere in the game

3. Stroke: play against the score

4. Match: play by hole, each time golfer gets a hole he will go "1UP" while his opponent will go "1DOWN". Whoever is "UP" in the end wins. If the "DOWN" player cannot win given the number of remaining holes then the game will end.

5. Mini Battle: Driving Contest: a match contest where the golfers will only drive.

6. Mini Battle: Near-Pin: a match contest that will involve only shots near the pin.

7. Mini Course: you play on a 3-par 9 hole course, you may play against a computer if you so wish.

8. Tour: 32 contestants enter the tour, who will win? You'll have to hone your Wonder Classic golfing skills to best this. Winning in tour mode will unlock new courses.

9. Net Tour: this mode will allow you the download the best 32 Tour scores that have been uploaded via the WonderGate. And then play a tour against those people, not the real people but against their scores, in a tour. You can also upload you own scores to compare them online.

The gameplay of Wonder Classic includes the ability to use the Y-buttons to augment just how your club will come in contact with the ball, to subtlety alter its trajectory. You'll also have six "Power Shots" which will have to be carefully conserved in each match.

Using the WonderGate you could get new clubs as well as stat altering equipment, such as gloves. You also could get new characters and courses through the WonderGate as well. This feature also allowed you to see your score as part of a "global" ranking.</desc>
	<image>./boxart/Wonder Classic (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/Wonder Classic (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/Wonder Classic (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Namco Limited</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai Co., Ltd.</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87695" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./X - Card of Fate (Japan).wsc</path>
	<name>X - Card of Fate</name>
	<desc>This is Tokyo - the keystone that keeps Earth from falling into ruin.</desc>
	<image>./boxart/X - Card of Fate (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/X - Card of Fate (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/X - Card of Fate (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Access Software</developer>
	<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="87696" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./XI (Sai) Little (Japan).wsc</path>
	<name>XI [sai] Little</name>
	<desc>"Roll the dice game will be off the edge. I know that someone you know is a famous game. Chain can not be perplexed in the beginning, when man used to enjoy! Highly addictive puzzle. I </desc>
	<image>./boxart/XI (Sai) Little (Japan).png</image>
	<marquee>./wheel/XI (Sai) Little (Japan).png</marquee>
	<video>./snap/XI (Sai) Little (Japan).mp4</video>
	<thumbnail/>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>MBI Limited</developer>
	<publisher>Namco Limited</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players/>
</game>
</gameList>
