	<path>./1991 Du Ma Racing (China) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./4 Nin uchi Mahjong (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Advanced Dungeons &amp; Dragons - Dragons of Flame (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Airwolf (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Akira (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Akumajou Densetsu (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Akumajou Special - Boku Dracula-kun (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./American Dream (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Ankoku Shinwa - Yamato Takeru Densetsu (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Arctic (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc>Arctic is an action puzzle game that describes itself as "active rail playing". Each of more than two-dozen stages consists of a set of rails in various arrangements, often looping around each other and splitting in various directions. Each stage contains a number of colored balls which begin in corresponding slots, and after launching them the goal is to return the balls to the matching-colored slots. The only interaction the player has with the board is switching two sets of splits; there are yellow and blue splits, which will redirect any balls moving through them, and the player can only turn all of one color as a group. Many stages also contain bumpers and gates which will affect the speed and direction of the balls. Completing a puzzle often requires strategic use of the stage's features to bounce balls onto the correct paths.</desc>
	<path>./Argus (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc>Argus is a standard vertical shooting game like Raptor or Tyrian; this game bears a strong resemblance to Terra Cresta, an arcade game.  There is no story, this game is a straight arcade-action shooter.

The game scrolls upward as waves of enemies attempt to impede your progress, shooting slow and fast moving bullets at your ship. Armed with air-to-air and air-to-ground missiles, blast your way forward while looking for bonuses. Crudely drawn buildings must be shot or avoided since it is possible to crash into them. While moving forward the game allows your ship to move as far left or right as necessary. Finally, at the end of each level you will have to destroy a large enemy.</desc>
	<path>./Arkanoid II (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc>Revenge of Doh is a direct sequel to the original arcade smash Arkanoid. Along with improved graphic engine, better sound and music, better hardware support and more levels, Revenge of Doh also features a built-in editor and allows you to create your own level sets!

Revenge of Doh continues Arkanoid's plot as follows, directly taken (including typoes) from the game:

A long time period passed and the dimension controlling force Doh has again come back to life. Occupying the huge starship Xorg, it has entered our universe from a different dimension. Mixtec, Arkanoid type spaceship, has lauched the craft Vaus II to make a preemptive attack on Xorg.
</desc>
	<path>./Armadillo (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Astro Fang - Super Machine (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Astro Robo Sasa (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc>This is a shooting game with a twist. You are in control of a small character who has to go through a serious of stages. Each stage consists of one screen only and contains several energy packs hidden behind various obstacles. Your goal is to eat up all the energy packs at a given stage, or (which is sometimes easier, but with dire consequences to the later stages) destroy them. If you manage to eat the energy packs, you'll gain more energy points, which carry over to the next stage. You'll need the energy points because every shot from your gun costs you one, and each collision with the various enemies flying around can deplete a large bulk of them. 

The twist of the game is in the movement: instead of simply flying around, you must shoot into the direction opposite of the desired movement. For example, if you shoot several times to the left, you'll be thrown to the right. Everything is built around the reactive force of your gun and the gravity force, which will slowly make you descend onto the ground if you don't shoot continuously. Preserving the precious energy points and trying to propel yourself exactly to the obstacles which you must destroy on your way to the energy packs is the only way to successfully complete the game.</desc>
	<path>./Atlantis no Nazo (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc>In "Atlantis no Nazo", you play a nameless archaeologist who must descend into the dangerous caverns of the lost continent Atlantis, and eventually find his way to the inner sanctum with the legendary treasure. The game plays like a standard action-based platformer. The levels feature plenty of enemies and gaps you must jump over. Your only weapon are sticks of dynamite. When you throw a stick, it will bounce off the floor and explode only after a couple of seconds, so very precise aiming and timing are needed to defeat the enemies. Many levels contain optional treasure chests as well as hidden doors that lead to bonus levels. Sometimes level progression is non-linear, i.e. you can jump straight to a high-numbered zone if you find the correspondent door on the level. All the levels are timed. The protagonist dies when he falls into a pit, touches an enemy, or runs out of time.</desc>
	<path>./Attack Animal Gakuen (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Babel no Tou (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc>Adian no Tsue features two educational math games.  The first game involves controlling a sorcerer named Lucian who is armed with a cane. He is on a mission to rescue Princess Patricia who is being held deep inside a dungeon labyrinth. Gameplay is viewed </desc>
	<path>./Ballblazer (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc>In the year 3037, the most competitive sport in the known universe is Ballblazer. For the first time ever, humans from the planet Earth have won the right to compete in the final round of the Ballblazer Championship, to fight for Earth's honor and the title Masterblazer!

Ballblazer is a 3D futuristic soccer-like game, where the player (inside a Rotofoil) is set on a one-on-one 1,155 square playing field (the Grid). The objective of the player to kick a floating ball (Plasmorb) inside the opponent's goal (Goalbeams). A player may compete against a human or computer opponent.

The Rotofoil is equipped with a multi-purpose forcefield. This forcefield when in short distance of the Plasmorb will act as a pull field, automatically pulling the Plasmorb towards to player. When a player in possession of the Plasmorb shoots, the forcefield will act as push field and launches the ball. When the match starts, the player must move down field and attempt to gain possession of the Plasmorb using the joystick and blast the Plasmorb to an intended direction. 

The player should also be aware that the Goldbeams move slightly every second and the distance between them will shrink. The highest scoring goals are goals made when Goldbeams have disappeared across the horizon (Over The Horizon/OTH shots). A player may also attempt to steal possession of a Plasmorb by rushing beside the opponent and blast the Plasmorb away. The game ends when time runs out or a player wins 10 consecutive goals. If the game ends in a draw, over-time will apply and the first player to score will win the game.

Scoring

Close-in goals - 1 point
Goals near Goldbeams - 2 points
OTH shots - 3 points
Players may steal points from each other by making goals. 
The total combined score of both players cannot accede more than 10 points.
A player winning 10 consecutive points automatically wins the game.</desc>
	<path>./Baltron (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc>In the space year of 2999, the powerful Bismark Empire has decided to launch an attack on the planet Earth. First however, they must occupy a small planet named Star Lenion so they can use it as a launching point for their main attack on the planet Earth.</desc>
	<path>./Banana (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Bats &amp; Terry (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Battle City (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc>Destroy different enemy tanks, while trying to keep them away from your base. When you have destroyed 20 enemy tanks you advance to the next level with different layout. In each level there's some obstacles which you can use to your advantage. Obstacles include red bricks which you can shoot out of your way, silver bricks which are highly armored, water and ice. You start the game with a basic tank, which you can power up to better one little by little. 

The game includes a construction mode, so you can make your own levels when you have played through all the 35 original levels.</desc>
	<path>./Binary Land (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc>In this game, you have to guide two penguins, one male and one female, through top-down vertical levels. The penguins are in love with each other and must be re-united! The penguins start on opposite sides, separated by walls, bricks, and other obstacles. You take control of one of the penguins. The other makes exactly the same movements as you, but in the opposite direction. So if for example you see an enemy to the left of the penguin you are not controlling, you have to fire to the right in order to hit it. You have to reach the top of the level in such a way that the two penguins will arrive at the top square at the same time, coming from opposite sides. Enemies such as spiders will put web on your way or attack you. You can kill them for points. There are various power-ups that appear randomly on the levels. You should also be careful not to run out of time.</desc>
	<path>./Bio Force Ape (Japan) (Proto).zip</path>
	<desc>Originally slated for release in 1991, Bio Force Ape allows you to play as a pet chimpanzee who must rescue his family by taking the mysterious Bio Force serum and mutating into a pro wrestler. It was the recipient of an extremely positive profile in Nintendo Power ? ?extremely positive? being NP?s default setting back in the day ? but then vanished, presumably never to be seen again. Last week, though, the archivists at Lost Levels not only acquired the long-lost prototype cartridge, but uploaded a playable version of it to the Internet.</desc>
	<path>./Bio Senshi Dan - Increaser Tono Tatakai (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc>The year is 2081. The Earth has become a devastated planet, overrun by monsters, controlled by a mysterious entity known as Increaser. The only hope to save the beloved Earth lies with you, a young warrior named Dan. You are sent in a time machine to the year 1999, when the monster invasion was beginning. Your task is to find your way through monster-infested labyrinths and to defeat the Increaser  whatever he (or it) is.

The game is an action platformer with more emphasis on exploration than on "jump &amp; run" gameplay. You don't die immediately if a monster touches you, but have a life bar that gets gradually depleted as you are hit. Defeated enemies bring you energy points, which you can spend to buy upgrades. You start with a sword, but later obtain other weapons as well. The game's structure is not entirely linear; many areas have different doors leading to different places.</desc>
	<path>./Bio-Miracle Bokutte Upa (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Bird Week (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc>In "Bird Week", you control a mother bird, and your goal is to find food for your baby birds. The two babies are sitting on a branch, while you fly around and try to catch some butterflies or other things to feed your children. There are also hostile birds flying around, who try to kill you or take away your food. Once you have given your children enough food, you proceed to the next level.</desc>
	<path>./Blodia Land - Puzzle Quest (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Bloody Warriors - Shan-Go no Gyakushuu (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Bokosuka Wars (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc>King Ogreth of the Basam Empire has invaded your country and either captured or turned into rocks and trees all your soldiers. You, king Suren, are left completely alone. In a desperate attempt, you decide to walk to king Ogreth's castle and to defeat him. You hope you'll be able to find some way to bring your soldiers back to you...

In this strategy game, your goal sounds simple  just walk a distance of 600 meters and defeat king Ogreth. But to do that is not simple at all. Bumping into trees and rocks, king Suren can bring his soldiers to life. Once there are some knights in his small army, he will also be able to free imprisoned soldiers. King Ogreth's units will constantly attack you on the way. The results of the battles are calculated automatically, according to the strength of your units. So before you engage in a battle, you have to be sure you have the upper hand (you have gathered enough soldiers, they have trained in easier battles, etc.). If king Suren dies in a battle, the game is over - you'll have to start from the beginning no matter how near you were to your goal.</desc>
	<path>./Booby Kids (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc>The game is set in a pre-historic environment, complete with cavemen and dinosaurs. You play as a little boy who has to collect treasure without being killed by those ferocious creatures. The only thing you can do to immobilize the enemies is setting a trap right before they approach you. This gives you an opportunity to gain some valuable time. The enemies will pop out of the traps a few seconds later. The game is divided into levels with increasing difficulty. At each level, your goal is to collect all the treasure before you can proceed. You die if you allow an enemy to touch you.</desc>
	<path>./B-Wings (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc>B-Wings is based on the popular arcade game Battle Wings. It is a vertically scrolling space shooter that owes its name to the space fighter from  Star Wars movies. You have a wide variety of weapons at your disposal: Fire, Cannons, Jump, Hammer, etc. Each weapon has its own advantages and disadvantages. For example, Cannon fires powerful and rapid blasts, but you can only shoot directly in front of you; Van covers several directions, but has slow speed; Anti builds a protective shield around you each time you shoot, but its range is very small, and so on. You can change the weapons every time you are killed, before you run out of lives and lose the game. Typically, at the end of a level you'll have to face a boss enemy.</desc>
	<path>./Cadillac (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Captain Silver (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Captain Tsubasa Vol. II - Super Striker (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Castle Quest (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Chack'n Pop (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc>This game is the predecessor of Bubble Bobble and it's
a platform game where a roundish yellow creature, named Chack'n, must fight against Monstas and Mightas. The Monstas hatch from eggs at the ceilings and the Mightas push a rock that is used as the game's timer.
The eggs have three phases: if it's blue, it's completely harmless, if it's yellow it will pop within 10 seconds and if an eggs turns red it will pop almost immediately.
Chack'n uses bombs to release the en-caged hearts and to blow up the Monstas. When the heart is released it will fly up and destroy the separator block between the level and the Mighta. Go to the Mighta and you are in the next level.
After 14 levels there's a wedding between Mr. and Mrs. Chack'n.</desc>
	<path>./Challenger (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc>One of Hudson Soft's earliest NES titles, Challenger is an arcade-style game that combines side scrolling, run 'n jump action with overhead, exploratory gameplay. The game consists of two parts.

The first level (or "scene") has you racing the clock to get to the front of a train, where a purple-faced villain is holding your significant other (or, perhaps just some anonymous princess). You have at your disposal a trusty throwing knife to take care of enemies. You will also have to dodge obstacles and jump gaps in the train. This section is taken from the earlier Hudson game, Stop the Express.

Scene 2 places you in an overhead, maze-like environment, where you once again have to fight the clock. This time though, you have to navigate your way through the area, in search of all the different "keywords", which are placed in different caves. Once you have cleared all the caves, the path will be open to the boss' final lair.</desc>
	<path>./Championship Lode Runner (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc>A follow-up to the original Lode Runner, with identical gameplay.  This package contained 50 of the most challenging levels ever designed, and was intended for expert players only.  It did not include the level editor, you had to play through the levels in order, but a save-game option was provided (although you lost one life every time you restored).</desc>
	<path>./Chaos World (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Chess Academy (China) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Chester Field - Ankoku Shin e no Chousen (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Chiisana Obake - Acchi Socchi Kocchi (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Cho Jiku Yosai Macross (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc>In this side-scrolling shooter, players take control of a VF-1 Valkyrie and do battle with the forces of the Zentradi. The main goal is to enter the Zentradi ship and destroy its reactor core.The players Valkyrie can change its appearance and abilities by</desc>
	<path>./Choplifter (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc>Choplifter is a side-scrolling action/arcade game that puts you in command of an attack chopper.  Your mission: Go behind enemy lines and rescue up to 16 hostages per level.  Be careful, though, because tanks and enemy aircraft will try to stop you -- and they won't stop shooting while you are rescuing those hostages!

Originally released for Apple II home computers, Choplifter was later ported to the arcades and a number of video game consoles. Many imitators and homages would follow.</desc>
	<path>./Choujin Sentai - Jetman (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Choujinrou Senki Warwolf (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Chuuka Taisen (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Circus Charlie (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc>You are Charlie, a member of a circus troupe. Your job is to please the crowd by performing five death-defying stunts:

Stunt #1: You and the lion must jump through several rings of fire. Remember to avoid the jugs that emit fire. You must do this for 100 meters.

Stunt #2: Walk the tightrope for 70 meters, avoiding the monkeys that get in your way. Jump the cyan monkeys for 500 points.

Stunt #3: Roll on a ball for 80 meters, jumping from ball to ball. You can move balls backwards if the target is too close to make a successful jump. Avoid contact with the ground.

Stunt #4: Ride a horse for 200 meters, bouncing on trampolines along the way. Be careful not to miss the jump or go over the tops of trampolines. You can speed up or slow down the horse.

Stunt #5: Finally, trapeze from swing to swing for 50 meters. If you miss, make sure that you land on the platforms below so you bounce back on a swing.

Once you have completed all five stunts, you have to do them again and hopefully, more points will be awarded.</desc>
	<path>./Cocoron (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Columbus - Ougon no Yoake (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc>In "Columbus: Ougon no Yoake" you take control of young Columbus, who is dreaming to sail the seas and explore the world. You start at the age of 14, becoming a apprentice aboard an old ship, where you learn the basics of combat. Your ultimate goal in this role-playing-game is to discover the continent America, just like the original model Christoph Kolumbus.
The Game can be played in two different modes. Either in "Normal Mode" or in "Historical Mode". The only difference of the historical mode compared to the normal mode, is that you have a limited ammount of time to complete the game. You start in December of 1465 and the game then ends by the end of 1492. The time ticks off, based on the number of steps you take, what means that you'll want to keep your steps as low as possible.
Discover the new world and take your place in history!</desc>
	<path>./Contra (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Cosmic Epsilon (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Cosmo Genesis (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Cosmo Police Galivan (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Crazy Climber (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc>As Crazy Climber, climb your way to the top of a series of buildings, where a helicopter is waiting to pick you up and take you to the next building. As Climber scales a building, he is able to climb up and sideways but he cannot climb down.
While climbing a building, windows will open and close simultaneously. If any window closes on either of his hands he will lose his grip. However, if a window closes on both of his hands, he will fall to his death, resulting in the loss of a life. You have three Climbers in total, but you are awarded an extra Climber every 30,000 points. Besides windows, Climber is faced with other dangers, including:

1. Bald-headed guys who hurl various objects at you.
2. Pesky condors who fly by, dropping eggs and droppings of an unpleasant substance.
3. Falling steel girders and iron dumbells.
4. Electrical "Nichibutsu" signs with a dangling live wire.
5. Falling "Crazy Climber" signs.
6. King Kong leaping from side to side of the building and slams his hands against the windows.

The climber must try to avoid or overcome each of those hazards which he will encounter as he continues climbing in his attempt to reach the rooftop. If he falls to his death by windows or objects, another climber will replace him and will start at the same location where the last one fell. The specific danger will not be present at the same point, so the climber can go further up to face the next danger. Most of the hazards are announced by certain recognizable musical themes. 

Crazy Climber is awarded a bonus score on each building every time after getting carried off by the helicopter. However, each bonus score will decrease by every ten seconds that the climber will spend scaling each building as he attempts reach the top. Somewhere in the game, there is "The Lucky Balloon", which can lift Climber about ten stories and raise the player's bonus score if he catches it.</desc>
	<path>./Crisis Force (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Cycle Race - Road Man (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Dai Meiro - Meikyuu no Tatsujin (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Dai-2-Ji Super Robot Taisen (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Daisenryaku (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc>One of many grand war simulations in Daisenryaku series, Daisenryaku for Famicom is a turn-based strategy with quite modern armies, the abstract "Blue" and "Red" countries (controlled by the player or AI), are at war with each other.Three basic phases mak</desc>
	<path>./Daiva Story 6 - Imperial of Nirsartia (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Dark Lord (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Dash Yarou (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Deblock (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc>De-Block is a puzzle game that can be most easily explained as a 4-way Tetris. The player controls a block in the center of the screen which can move and rotate freely. Larger blocks move inward from each side of the screen and attach to the center block, then change color depending on their distance from the center. If the player completes a colored ring, that layer and all the blocks inside of it are cleared, and all the ones outside are moved inward. Play ends if a newly-appearing block overlaps with the player's structure.</desc>
	<path>./Deep Dungeon III - Yuushi heno Tabi (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Deep Dungeon IV - Kuro no Youjutsushi (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Devil Man (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Dezaemon (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc>Dezaemon is a game designing application that lets aspiring developers create their own vertical scrolling shoot-'em-up. Players have control over how their ship looks, design how their levels (up to three) will look, and also create a title screen. Playe</desc>
	<path>./Dig Dug (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc>Dig Dug is a 1-2 player arcade game in which you have to use your shovel to dig your way through the earth. Stopping you from doing this are two monsters, called Pooka and Fygar, who will continually chase you around. The only weapon that you carry is an air pump, which you can use to inflate the monsters to the point where they explode. (if you start to inflate them but stop doing so, the monsters will get turned back to their normal selves.) Furthermore, rocks are scattered throughout the earth, and you can use these rocks to squash them. If the monsters do not find you for several seconds, they will eventually get turned into ghosts, which are able to walk through the earth. They are invincible and cannot be killed. From time to time, vegetables will appear in the center, and you can get these for points.</desc>
	<path>./Digital Devil Monogatari - Megami Tensei (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc>A high-school student and skillful computer programmer named Akemi Nakajima created a software called "Devil Summoning Program". At first Nakajima intended to use the software to gain revenge on a classmate who bullied him. However, things went out of control and Nakajima summoned malicious demons. Together with his friend Yumiko Shirasagi, a transfer student, he now must fight the demons he unleashed!</desc>
	<path>./Don Doko Don (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc>In this game, you play a bearded dwarf whose girlfriend has been kidnapped and taken away to the dragon's castle, and in order to rescue her, you must defeat enemies with your mallet. Once you do, you can pick them up and throw them at other enemies, and collect the fruit that they leave behind. When you have defeated all enemies, you proceed onwards to the next round. If you take too long to complete a level, a winged devil will appear who will try to kill you while flying around the screen

Occasionally, power-ups will appear in the middle of the level, and these power-ups will increase your power, award you with different weapons, kill enemies, or freeze time. The more power you have, the more walls that you can through enemies through. At maximum power, you are able to throw enemies through all walls.
If you happen to carry the blue hammer, you are able to throw it through walls, too.

There are five areas that consist of ten levels each. At the end of each area, you have to defeat a boss in order to proceed further.</desc>
	<path>./Don Doko Don 2 (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Donald Land (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc>The game stars Ronald McDonald (known in Japan as Donald McDonald), the mascot of the McDonald's fast food chain. The objective is to bring peace to his magical land by controlling the famous fast food clown. Most of Ronald's companions have been kidnapped, and the animals have turned feral. His brainwashed companions will occasionally attack. Ronald can defend himself using apple bombs, thrown in a carefully calculated parabola.Being hit by the enemy causes damage, which decreases Ronald's "Life" meter. During various parts of a stage, players have the opportunity to collect up to 100 hamburger icons throughout the game. This will result in gaining a bonus life along with the hamburger counter resetting itself to zero. It is also possible to play a mini-game challenge, to earn commodities that the player orders from McDonald's.
</desc>
	<path>./Door Door (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc>DoorDoor is platform game in which you have to lock up the monster creatures that pursue you. Only one creature can be locked up behind one door. Don't forget to close the door or the creatures will walk out and pursue you again.</desc>
	<path>./Doraemon - Giga Zombie no Gyakushuu (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Doraemon (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Dough Boy (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc>The president has been kidnapped and it is currently being held behind enemy lines. Players take control of a soldier who has to cross through the enemy lines to rescue this very important prisoner of war.  The game consist of five different timed maps wh</desc>
	<path>./Downtown Special - Kunio-kun no Jidaigeki Da yo Zenin Shuugou! (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Dragon Ball - Daimaou Fukkatsu (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Dragon Ball - Shenron no Nazo (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Dragon Ball Z - Kyoushuu! Saiya Jin (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Dragon Ball Z Gaiden - Saiya Jin Zetsumetsu Keikaku (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Dragon Ball Z III - Ressen Jinzou Ningen (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Dragon Buster (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc>"Dragon Buster" is a conversion of Namco's arcade game from 1984. The game is composed of several large levels, each one containing various stages: a cave, a tower, a castle, etc. Your goal in every level is to reach the final stage where you face the level boss. There are often several ways to reach the final stages, and not all stages are necessary to visit. Equipped with a sword, you move through the platform-like stages, clearing them of diverse monsters, collecting power-ups and trying to stay in good health until the level boss, since you can't heal your character between the stages.</desc>
	<path>./Dragon Buster II - Yami no Fuuin (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Dragon Knife (China) (Unl) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Dragon Ninja (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Dragon Scroll - Yomigaerishi Maryuu (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc>Aeons ago, two dragons and their follower were fighting each other. The  "Black Mages" worshipped the three-headed Chrome Dragon, and the "White Mages" worshipped the glimmering Gold Dragon. The wars fought for territory and ideals where endless. After ages of fighting, the god Narume put the Chrome Dragon to sleep in the mountains and the Gold Dragon to sleep in the desert, to stop the wars. Then he took th magic away from the mages, and sealed it in the 8 Magic Books, which he hid in the sacred desert tower.

Hundreds of years later, three thieves stumbled upon the desert tower, and found the Magic Books. They split them up amongst themselves and every one of them, walked his own way. Now that the Magic Books were gone, the Chrome Dragon awoke from his slumber. Narume then infused the Gold Dragon with the spirit of justice, summoning him forth in the form of a hero named "Feram"
Now it is up to him, to find the Magic Books and put the Chrome Dragon to sleep again.</desc>
	<path>./Dream Master (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Dynamite Bowl (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc>Dynamite Bowl is a bowling game simulation based on the real bowling sport and can be played up to five players at one of the thirty lanes.
The game has two difficulty levels.
Game variables that can be controlled are: your position at the lane, set the strength of the throw and control the loft and curve of the bowling ball.</desc>
	<path>./Eggerland - Meikyuu no Fukkatsu (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Egypt (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Elnark no Zaihou (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Elysion (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Esper Bouken Tai (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Esper Dream 2 - Aratanaru Tatakai (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc>Far beyond our world, there's a world that resides in the books you read. But the five areas of the Book Worlds are in deep trouble! As Mamoru, a bookworm with ESP, you must go forth (with the help of a magical fairy and several other allies) to grab five</desc>
	<path>./Exciting Boxing (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Exciting Rally - World Rally Championship (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Exed Exes (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc>On a planet 6000 light-years from earth, there were creatures called Exes, which resemble large insects, that were used for industrial purposes. However, these creatures one day took to revolting against their creators. Two battle machines have been sent to fight against the Exes, known as Colonel and Sargent. The Exes are nearing completion of their secret weapon, Exed Exes, and they must be defeated before this is allowed to happen!

Exed Exes is a basic vertical scrolling shooter, converted from the 1985 coin-op. The game scrolls forward, and the player can maneuver their ship around the screen to shoot enemies and avoid attack. POW icons sometimes appear that can power up the ship or turn enemies into fruit that are worth extra points. The game can be played either solo or two-player cooperatively.</desc>
	<path>./Exerion (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc>This is a shoot-em-up game with parallax effects in the background. It does have a simulation of inertia in the control of the ship.
There are dozens of enemies and two types of shooting: slow and fast. Two weapon systems: one slow double-shot cannon and one fast single-shot cannon.
With each enemy hit by the slow cannon you get one shot added to the fast cannon ammunition supply.
A challenge stage follows each stage in which you can build up your fast-shot bullet supply.</desc>
	<path>./F-1 Race (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc>In this game, which is similar to Pole Position, the player takes control of an F1 car. The player can race the vehicle on one of three different skill levels. Each skill level contains five different tracks for the player to race on. On each of these tracks, the player must complete 2 laps before a countdown timer expires. The player must also try not to crash into other racers and obstacles on the sides of the road. The vehicle has a manual transmission, so the player has to switch between low and hi gear while racing.
</desc>
	<path>./Famicom Wars (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Fantasy Zone 2 - Opa-Opa no Namida (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc>Fantasy Zone II: The Tears of Opa-Opa is the sequel to Fantasy Zone, in which you control Opa-Opa, a pretty colored ship with wings on its side. You must destroy the large creatures in each world before moving on to the next. Your task becomes difficult by other small creatures that happen to pass by. If you destroy a large creature, they will drop a dollar bill, which you can pick up and use at the shop to buy items and powerful weapons such as laser beams, x-way shots, and big wings. Another way to get money is to shoot certain kinds of enemies all in a row.

More often than not, some large creatures will reveal a warp gate rather than a dollar bill. You can go through the warp gate to get to another part of the land, and destroy more large creatures. Only one of them will have a warp gate in the form of a 'stop' sign - that is your ticket to the round boss, but you must defeat all large creatures in order to pass through it. Also like in the original can you walk on the ground to avoid approaching enemies, and spend money in the shop to get new weapons (but they only last for a limited time).</desc>
	<path>./Field Combat (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc>Players are assigned the role as the field commander of the blue colored forces who are in a battle against the red colored forces. Players take control of the Genesis, a flying saucer shaped craft, that can fire missiles, capture enemy units with a tract</desc>
	<path>./Final Fantasy II (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Final Fantasy III (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Final Fantasy VII (China) (Unl) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Final Lap (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc>Final Lap by Namco is considered by many to be the spiritual successor to Pole Position. This fairly straightforward Formula 1 racing game features a one or two player mode which is raced via split-screen. Up to eight players can take turns playing in a tournament mode. 

The initial race takes place on an oval track in New York while subsequent tracks with more challenging turns and corners will take players all over the world; from Mexico to Monaco. Each car can be upgraded before a race with allotted points to customize the tires, engine, brakes, and nitro. Nitro is kicked in by pressing up on the control pad. Colliding into competitors will bump your car back but sliding into billboards on the side can cause your vehicle to spin out.</desc>
	<path>./Final Mission (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Fire Emblem (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Fire Emblem Gaiden (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Flappy (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc>In this puzzle game, you control Flappy, a yellow mole.  The object of the game is to help Flappy push the Blue Stone onto its Blue Platform in each level.

Red Stones are placed in key locations across the levels. They can be pushed, stacked on top of each other, and even destroyed. Flappy must strategically take advantage of the gravity and the Red Stones in order to clear the path for pushing the Blue Stone. Three different types of enemies will try to prevent Flappy from clearing the level, so you must either avoid the enemies, crush them from above with the Stones, or pick up Sleeping Mushrooms to knock them out temporarily.</desc>
	<path>./Fleet Commander (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Flipull - An Exciting Cube Game (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Flying Hero (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Formation Z (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc>The player competes in a marathon continuous scrolling horizontal shoot-em-up game across land, sea, air and outer space. You can hold down the fire button for a burst of Charged fire, which is especially essential to defeat the bosses.

The player can hold down the Jump button to transform back and forth between a Mobile Robot or an Aero Fighter. Some sections have confrontations on both ground and air; others insist on aerial battling. Your time in the Aero Fighter is limited by its fuel requirement.</desc>
	<path>./Front Line (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc>Front Line is a vertically scrolling action game. Your mission is to infiltrate enemy territory and destroy their fortress. To reach the fortress, you will have to make your way through varied and dangerous terrain. Jungles, deserts, brush, and rocks all slow your progress, plus each area has numerous enemy fighters and tanks trying to stop you. To help get past these obstacles, you are armed with a machine gun and grenades; at some points in the game you may even come across an abandoned tank which you can control to increase your odds of survival. When you reach the end of the level and successfully destroy the fortress, the game will repeat at a higher level of difficulty. Gameplay is for one or two players, and four different skill levels are available.</desc>
	<path>./Fudou Myouou Den (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Fushigi no Umi no Nadia (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Fuzzical Fighter (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Galaxian (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc>Galaxian is a shoot 'em up in which the player is at the bottom of the screen, with an arrangement of aliens at the top. The player moves left and right to aim at an alien, then shoots a bullet up the screen, and the alien it hits is killed. The aliens are classed as Drones, Emissaries, Hornets and Commanders, with those higher up the screen scoring more points when destroyed. At set intervals an enemy will move down the screen towards you, escorting a bomber, which is a moment of high danger. Clear a wave and another is generated.</desc>
	<path>./Game Party (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc>Game Party allows you to play 5 different games on one cartridge. The games involved are Air Hockey, Hockey, Pinball, Basketball, and  Mind-Q. So grab a friend and start playing some good multiplayer games!</desc>
	<path>./Ganbare Goemon 2 (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Ganbare Goemon! - Karakuri Douchuu (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Garfield - A Week of Garfield (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc>Garfield, the lovable fat orange cat, has gotten himself into a spot of trouble. His pal and center of abuse, the yellow dog Odie, has gone and disappeared somewhere. Their owner, Jon, is too lazy to go look for Odie himself, so he has Garfield go out and look for him. And so Garfield heads off, out into the world.

A Week of Garfield is a side-scrolling platform game based on the comic strip by Jim Davis. Garfield heads to the right through various indoor and outdoor city environments, dealing with endless vermin like frogs, birds, and mice using his judo kick skills and several different weapons such as bones that can be thrown. He has a life bar that can quickly deplete if he isn't careful, but hidden all around each stage are various items, which can replenish his health, refill his weapon supplies, and give him super speed or invincibility; be careful, though, as sometimes he'll also find fish bones which will harm Garfield if eaten.

The game is divided into seven stages, each representing a day of the week, and each with several sections. At the end of each section is a door, and Garfield must find the key hidden somewhere on the screen to unlock the door and continue. At the last door of each stage, there is a boss that must be defeated before Garfield can find the key. Each stage also has a strict time limit to keep him from dawdling, and between stages, Jon will appear to encourage Garfield or give him some advice.</desc>
	<path>./Gegege no Kitarou - Youkai Daimakyou (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Gegege no Kitarou 2 - Youkai Gundan no Chousen (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Geimos (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc>Geimos is an arcade style space shooter where players take control of a spaceship that flies over several different planets' surfaces destroying the incoming enemy units. The game contains two different game modes. "Mode A" keeps the games camera perspect</desc>
	<path>./Gekitotsu Yonku Battle (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Getsu Fuuma Den (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Golf '92, The (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Golf Club - Birdie Rush (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Goonies (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc>The Goonies is based on a movie of the same name from 1985. A group of youngsters from a neighborhood called the "Goon Docks" are trying to find the lost treasure of One-Eyed Willie to prevent the foreclosure of their houses. Unfortunately, the treasure is buried under the hide-out of the infamous Fratelli gang, a family of ruthless criminals who are on the run from the law. You play as the asthmatic Mikey, who must find the treasure and save the other Goonies before time runs out.

The game consists of six levels. In each level, you must collect three keys to advance to the next area. These can be found by blowing open doors with bombs that are dropped by enemies. Also hidden behind doors are power-ups and other Goonies to rescue. Trying to stop you are enemies such as rats, skeletons, and even members of the Fratelli Gang. Bonus points can be gained by picking up diamonds and other valuables, rescuing the other Goonies, or by dispatching enemies with your slingshot or kicking them.

Unlike the sequel, the Famicom version was never released outside of Japan.</desc>
	<path>./Gorby no Pipeline Daisakusen (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Gradius II (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc>Gradius II is a sequel to Gradius, and Life Force, and is a horizontal space shooter composed of 7 levels.
Like it's predecessor, you can collect power up from enemies and chose which ones to use when. This time, this system is enhanced because you can chose between 4 different power-up sequences, allowing you to use differents types of weapons against your enemies. There is also the possibility to gain options, which are mysterious balls of fire that follows your spaceship closely and mimic all its movements (including shots). While you only could have 2 of them in Gradius, you now can have up to 4 of them.</desc>
	<path>./Grand Master (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Great Deal (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Gyrodine (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc>Gyrodine is basic vertical shooter based on Taito's arcade game with the same name. You pilot a helicopter and have to shoot as many enemies you can. You will fight against enemy helicopters, bunkers, tanks and fighter jets above different terrains like water, desserts and military camps. There is no background story and there are no levels.</desc>
	<path>./Hebereke (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Heisei Tensai Bakabon (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Hello Kitty no Ohanabatake (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc>During the course of this video game, Hello Kitty must water all the flowers in each stage while avoiding the many animals and insects. Kitty's ribbon always stays on the left side of her ear; even if the player changes the orientation of the character.
She can defend herself with the use of a large mallet. Running into enemies will make her cry, which causes Kitty to get angry and lose a life. Points in the game are collected as money for the cash register. Allowing the time limit to expire will also cause the player to lose a life. However, there are infinite continues and losing the game score is the only penalty for "game overs." There are 18 stages in the game and the game does not repeat itself after the 18th stage. While the second half of the game is more difficult then the first nine levels, they can be cleared once the player is accustomed to the game controls.</desc>
	<path>./Hello Kitty World (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Heracles no Eikou - Toujin Makyou Den (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Heracles no Eikou II - Titan no Metsubou (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Hi no Tori Hououhen - Gaou no Bouken (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Higemaru Makaijima - Nanatsu no Shima Daibouken (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Hikari no Senshi Photon - The Ultimate Game on Planet Earth (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Hirake! Ponkikki (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Hitler no Fukkatsu - Top Secret (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Hokuto no Ken (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Holy Diver (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Honoo no Doukyuuji - Dodge Danpei (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Honoo no Doukyuuji - Dodge Danpei 2 (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Hottaman no Chitei Tanken (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Hyaku no Sekai no Monogatari - The Tales on a Watery Wilderness (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Hyper Sports (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc>Six tough events await in this joystick-waggling action game. The full sequence of events is - swimming, skeet shooting, gymnastics, archery, triple jumping and weightlifting. You must complete each event in order to be allowed onto the next one.Swimming </desc>
	<path>./Ike Ike! Nekketsu Hockey-bu - Subette Koronde Dairantou (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Ikinari Musician (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc>Ikinari Musician lets players interact with a keyboard synthesizer. Players can select beats from different musical genres the world over. Players can create riffs, turn on or off the instruments they want to use, and change the way the notes are displaye</desc>
	<path>./Ikki (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc>They are currently involved in an uprising against their feudal lord. The feudal lord has dispatched his army of ninjas t</desc>
	<path>./Insector X (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./J.League Fighting Soccer - The King of Ace Strikers (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./J.League Winning Goal (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Jajamaru Gekimaden - Maboroshi no Kinmajou (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Jajamaru no Daibouken (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Jekyll Hakase no Houma ga Toki (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Jesus - Kyoufu no Bio Monster (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Jigoku Gokuraku Maru (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Jikuu Yuuden - Debias (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./JJ - Tobidase Daisakusen Part II (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Joy Mech Fight (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc>The evil scientist Warunachi has hacked all the otherwise peaceful robots in Japan and now plans to launch an attack for world domination the likes of which the world has never seen. Fortunately his former partner, Dr. Eamon, saved one robot from the takeover and has now programmed him to defeat the other robots and foil Dr. Warunachi's evil plans.

Joy Mecha Fight is a one-on-one 2D fighter, in which you control a robot and attempt to defeat your opponent by attacking him with your basic moves and special attacks triggered by specific control motions. Each robot is composed of six hovering segments: the head, torso and limbs, which hover around each other forming a basic humanoid shape. 

The game features story, instant fight, and Vs modes. In the story mode you start with the Sukapon robot, and as you defeat other robots they become available for selection as you advance through the story with all moves being explained via a pre-fight tutorial if you want to.
</desc>
	<path>./Jumbo Ozaki no Hole in One Professional (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc>This is the second golf game from HAL Laboratory after Hole in One. Like it's predecessor, Hole in One Professional is a standard 18-hole golf game, played from a top-down perspective. Players can compete in stroke play with up to four players, or match play against a friend or the computer. When playing against the computer, the player will play against an opponent that uses metal clubs, which hit farther than the standard wooden clubs.

In addition to stroke and match play, players can obtain passwords that allow a replay of any spectacular shots that are made (eagles, holes-in-one, and double-eagles).</desc>
	<path>./Just Breed (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc>The town of Astholm is protected by a Sapphire, one of the magical stones mentioned in old legends. Generation of honorable priestesses protect the stone, and with it the town. Tonight is the annual Sapphire Festival, and the young priestess Firis is going to conduct the ceremony. But just after the joyous event, the priestess is kidnapped by Gel du Rey, the henchman of the evil Lord Ezelkiel. You play the role of the captain of Astholm's guards. You and Firis have been close friends ever since the childhood. You decide to rescue the priestess, with the help of your loyal guards and friends you meet on your journey.

Just Breed is a hybrid of traditional console-style RPG like Dragon Warrior or Final Fantasy, and strategy RPG. During confrontations with the enemies, the battle screen occupies the entire location, and large parties of allies and enemies fight each other in turn-based style, moving on the field to perform physical attacks (melee as well as ranged) or to cast magic spells.</desc>
	<path>./Juuouki (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Juuryoku Soukou Metal Storm (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Juvei Quest (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Kaguya Hime Densetsu (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Kai no Bouken - The Quest of Ki (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Kaijuu Monogatari (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Kaiketsu Yancha Maru 2 - Karakuri Land (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Kaiketsu Yancha Maru 3 - Taiketsu! Zouringen (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Kanshakudama Nage Kantarou no Toukaidou Gojuusan Tsugi (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc>Players take the role of Kantarou, whose occupation is to make fireworks. He is currently traveling on the Tokaido highway starting in Kyoto trying to make his way home to Edo, where his girlfriend Momoko resides. However, this is a long walk home as the </desc>
	<path>./Karakuri Kengoden Musashi Lord - Karakuri Jin Hashiru! (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Karateka (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc>The evil Akuma has destroyed your homeland, killed many of your friends and kidnapped your Princess Mariko. Fortunately, you are skilled in Martial Arts, so your inevitable quest to reach Akuma's palace has a chance of success.

The game is viewed from the side and features a succession of increasingly-difficult opponents. All the standard karate kicks and punches are available to both you and your foes. The game's design was serious and realistic, and the game featured lots of cutscenes to develop the story.</desc>
	<path>./Karnov (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Kawa no Nushi Tsuri (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Keisan Game - Sansuu 1 Nen (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Keisan Game - Sansuu 3 Nen (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Keisan Game - Sansuu 4 Nen (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Keisan Game - Sansuu 5+6 Nen (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Kekkyoku Nankyoku Daibouken (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Kero Kero Keroppi no Daibouken (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Kero Kero Keroppi no Daibouken 2 - Donuts Ike wa Oosawagi! (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Keroppi to Keroriinu no Splash Bomb! (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./King Kong 2 - Ikari no Megaton Punch (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Kinnikuman - Muscle Tag Match (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Kouryuu Densetsu Villgust Gaiden (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Kujaku Ou (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Kujaku Ou II (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Kunio-kun no Nekketsu Soccer League (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Kyatto Ninden Teyandee (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Kyouryuu Sentai Zyuranger (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Labyrinth - Maou no Meikyuu (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc>Labyrinth is a maze game similar to Gauntlet, but with a more definite goal and some adventure elements. It is based upon the Jim Henson film of the same name incorporates many scenes from the movie as areas with the maze.

The goal of the game is to collect twelve coins Sara can use to buy back her baby brother from his kidnapper, the goblin king, Jareth. There is one coin in each of the twelve mazes surrounding the central castle. At first only a few of the mazes are accessible; however, upon collecting a section of a broken key, of which there is also one per region, Sara is sent to a hub where a friendly goblin will open up a new area. Each section of the maze has its own gimmick, for instance the Hedge Maze rearranges itself as the player wanders through it, and the Fieries' Forest is filled with teleports. The areas are also connected via a large underground maze. Upon gaining all the sections of the key Sara can open the door to the castle and enter the final series of mazes, however, she cannot win if she has not collected all of the coins.

Throughout all this Sara is constant beset by enemies at which she must throw a neverending supply of stones to dissipate. Her stones can be upgraded eventually and she can also gain the favor of her friends from the movie who will follow her around and try to help her shoot at her aggressors.

All of this must be done in no more than 13 minutes or the game must be restarted, and every time an enemy attacks Sara she loses a few more seconds. However, there are several ways to gain more time, and part of winning the game is balancing actually solving the maze and spending time searching for minutes to do just that.</desc>
	<path>./Lagrange Point (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Layla (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc>LayLa is on a mission to rescue her friend Iris from an evil doctor who has kidnapped her. This mission will take LayLa through eight different explorable asteroids.Gameplay mainly involves controlling LayLa through the cavernous maze-like asteroids shoot</desc>
	<path>./Lost Word of Jenny - Ushinawareta Message (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Lot Lot (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc>Lot lot is a puzzle game. The goal of the game is of extreme simplicity. Manipulate the balls in such a way till they fall into the pits and generating points.

The game has five pits: Out, 0 points, 10 points, 30 points and 50 points.

Each level starts by giving you a target score that you'll have to reach before you continue to the next level.

The screen is divided into sixteen sections. The walls of those sections randomly disappear and the balls will then drop or roll into the other section or a pit at the bottom of the screen.

On the screen you will find two arrows of which the second arrow follows the first one but with a slight delay and it stops at the same position as the first one.

The arrows will start in an empty section of which one of the walls will soon disappear. To move the balls to the empty section move your first arrow to a section that is filled with balls end press the space bar or fire button. The balls will then be moved to the empty section.
If both sections contain balls then the balls will be swapped accordingly.

Now you have to manipulate the balls in such a way that they will generating points by getting them to the pits that generate points.

In the bottom left of the screen there is a section that has a thin red line at the bottom. Never move the balls in that section because if any balls enter that section a crab will appear and cut the red line with it's razor sharp claws. The balls will disappear in the pit labeled 'OUT' and you loose a life.</desc>
	<path>./Lupin Sansei - Pandora no Isan (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Mad City (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Madoola no Tsubasa (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc>The Kingdom of Badham was once the host of the legendary Wing of Madoola bird statue. Anyone who possessed the wing would be granted tremendous power. Many wars were caused by nations wanting to have control over this powerful artifact. Thankfully, a king</desc>
	<path>./Magic John (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Magical Doropie (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Magnum Kikiippatsu - Empire City - 1931 (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc>In this arcade hall conversion of Empire City: 1931 which is set in 1931 you are a federal agent that has to eliminate all criminal activities in New York City.
You must hunt the criminals down and shoot them one by one. To locate a criminal you just have to follow the arrow on the left or right of the screen. Killing criminals is done by moving the cross hair over them.
A countdown timer will start counting down if a criminal starts shooting at you. You must kill the criminal before the timer reaches zero or you'll loose a life.
New bullets can be collected by shooting at the bullet boxes that regularly appear in the game as other useful objects.
The criminals sometimes take hostages for protection. Rescue these hostages for additional points.

Firing your gun is done with fire button 1 and deflecting bullets by pressing the fire button 2.
</desc>
	<path>./MahaRaja (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Majin Eiyuuden Wataru Gaiden (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Majou Densetsu II - Daimashikyou Galious (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Mappy (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc>You control Mappy a police-mouse whose job is to collect valuables (consumer electronics)from a cat's house. You are being pursued by a gang of five pink cats. Doors are your only defense against the cats. You get from floor to floor by jumping on one of the trampolines.
Points are earned by recovering stolen goods. Other ways of earning points are bouncing on a trampoline, putting cats in the microwave, striking a cat with a door, striking cats with a bell, retrieving a treasures from the Boss cat Goro or dropping cats through a hole in the floor.</desc>
	<path>./Mappy Kids (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Matendouji (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Metro-Cross (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc>Simple side-scrolling game, where you play a skater who has to pass a set of obstacles in order to reach the end of the level.

You can skate up or down in the screen, or even jump, to be safe from the pipes you encounter on the way. As the game progresses, obstacles are more frequent and more challenging, but the essence is the same. Timing is everything in this game.</desc>
	<path>./Mickey Mouse 3 - Yume Fuusen (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Minelvaton Saga - Ragon no Fukkatsu (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Mini Putt (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Minna no Taabou no Nakayoshi Daisakusen (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Miracle Ropit's Adventure in 2100 (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Mirai Senshi - Lios (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Mirai Shinwa Jarvas (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Mitsume ga Tooru (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Moai-Kun (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Momotarou Densetsu (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Moon Crystal (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc>Moon Crystal is a platform action game where you control Ricky Slater on his mission to free his kidnapped father from the evil Count Crimson. The Count is forcing his father, a great scientist, to use the power of the moon crystal to turn the dead into living and rule the world.

There are 7 stages, each ending with a boss fight. The themes of the stages follow the story closely. The player begins each stage with only small knife to defend yourself. The player can find power-ups that can extend the range of your knife, give additional health containers, allow Ricky to make double jumps etc. The player has 3 lives and also an unlimited amount of continues.

The game is notable for its fluid animations and rich graphic cut scenes which moves the story forward. It was never officially released outside of Japan, but an unofficial English translation patch exists.</desc>
	<path>./Mother (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Motocross Champion (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Mottomo Abunai Deka (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Mouryou Senki Madara (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc>As a baby, Madara was found floating in a river near Mount Shumi. The elder Tatara saved him, build gadgets to replace his missing body parts and raised him together with his grandchild Kirin. On Madara's 15th birthday, when most of the world had already fallen to the Moki controlled by the Emperor Miroku, Madara sets out to find his real body and save the world from the Moki.

Mouryou Senki Madara is an RPG in which players control a party consisting of up two four characters exploring towns, dungeons and a world map from a top-down perspective. Battles occur randomly and the characters move and fight autonomously, although it is possible to pause battles at any time and order characters to fight, defend, use magic or items or flee. Furthermore, a basic battle strategy (attack, defend, stop or flee) can be selected from a tactics menu, where it is also possible to change the characters' starting formation.</desc>
	<path>./Musashi no Bouken (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Nagagutsu o Haita Neko - Sekai Isshuu 80 Nichi Daibouken (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Nakayoshi to Issho (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Nekketsu Kakutou Densetsu (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Nekketsu Kouha Kunio-Kun (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Nekketsu! Street Basket - Ganbare Dunk Heroes (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Niji no Silk Road (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Ninja Hattori-kun - Ninja wa Syugyou de Gozaru (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Ninja Jajamaru - Ginga Daisakusen (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Ninja Jajamaru Kun (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Ninja-kun - Ashura no Shou (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Ninja-kun - Majou no Bouken (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Ninjara Hoi! (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Nuts &amp; Milk (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc>In this Arcade game the gameplay is quite simple, the hero, named "Milk" must get all the fruits in the screen in order to free his girlfriend (don't ask me what's the relation) who is captured inside of a house. Your rival "'Nuts" will try to keep you away from your goal. To obtain the fruit, Milk will climb up ladders and jump onto different platforms.

Points are earned by obtaining the fruit, jumping over Nuts and completing the level in the shortest amount of time (obtaining the Bonus score value). Two game modes are included as well as a level editor.</desc>
	<path>./Obake no Q Tarou - Wan Wan Panic (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Oishinbo - Kyukyoku no Menu 3bon Syoubu (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Onyanko Town (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc>In Onyanko Town, a kitten named Michael has wandered outside its house and has now gotten lost. Now, it's up to the kitten's mother, Milky, to search all over the town trying to locate the kitten and return it to their household. The game is set in a town</desc>
	<path>./Paaman Part 2 - Himitsu Kessha Madoodan o Taose! (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Pachicom (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc>Pachicom is a pachinko game simulation. Pachinko can be described as a game that is a cross between pinball and a slot machine. This game comes with two different game modes to play. Game A lets the player play until they attain a score of at least 3000. </desc>
	<path>./Pac-Land (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc>Pac-Land is a side-scrolling 1-2 player game with a cartoony feel to it. Now equipped with arms, face, and legs, Pac must guide a fairy back to her home in Fairy Land, but this task will not be easy because Inky, Blinky, Pinky, Clyde, and Sue will pursue Pac-Man as he travels through Pac-Land. When he finally transports the fairy back to her home, Pac is given some magic shoes, which will help him get to his own home, where he will be greeted by his family: Ms. Pac-Man, Baby Pac-Man, Chomp Chomp, and Sourpuss. 

There are sixteen rounds to complete, with four trips each. During each round, he can grab a power pellet, which cause ghosts to turn blue, allowing Pac-Man to eat them for points. Points are also awarded by collecting fruit that appear, like cherries and strawberries. In some rounds, Pac must use a springboard to jump over a lake. He must also make it to the end of each round before time runs out, otherwise a ghost will chase him.</desc>
	<path>./Palamedes II - Star Twinkles (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Parallel World (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc>Having been sucked into and stranded in an alternate universe, you and your girlfriend must work your way around the puzzles of a magnificent castle to make your way back home.

The castle itself consists of a total of twenty worlds consisting of five stages apiece, each of which is filled to the brim with enemies. From your overhead view, you must use your directional pad to move your character around the grid and push the onscreen obstacles into your enemies to destroy them for the keys to escape as well as other goodies (extra time, bonus points, etc.), but keep in mind that you'll need to use those same obstacles to construct a path to the exit. And don't forget to work fast either, as you only have 100 seconds to clear each puzzle. Fail and you'll lose a life (you start with only three).

This game may be played with either one or two players (simultaneous play). Player One controls the boy. Player Two gets to be the girl. Both must have their wits about them to make it past the hoards of springs, crazy rollers, witches, zombies, and more to make it home in one piece.</desc>
	<path>./Paris-Dakar Rally Special (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Parodius Da! (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Peepar Time (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Penguin-Kun Wars (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Perfect Bowling (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Pescatore (Japan) (Proto) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Pizza Pop! (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc>A pizza delivery guy is in love with a girl named Betty. He's going about his careless job, delivering in hopes of big tips, when something catches his eye. It's a beautiful diamond ring, and it's impossible to resist! Unfortunately, it costs $10,000 - wa</desc>
	<path>./Pooyan (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc>In this remake of the arcade game Pooyan from the early '80s, you play the role of a pig, protecting its piglets from wolves.  

The first screen takes place near the pigs' home. Mrs. Pig rides up and down in a cable car, shooting at wolves, who are riding balloons downward, towards the ground. If the wolves land safely on the ground, then they can climb a ladder, near the cable-car, and catch Mrs. Pig. But if she shoots their balloons, they splat on the ground instead.

The wolves shoot acorns at the pig. But Mrs. Pig has a food based weapon too. If she gets to the top, she can get meat, to toss at the wolves and make them jump off their balloons in pursuit. Each wolf taken out this way is worth bonus points (on a doubling scheme: 400, 800 1600...)

The second scene takes place at the wolves lair. Here the wolves have reinforced balloons--it takes multiple hits to make them fall. Here they float upwards toward a big rock, which they push on top of Mrs. Pig, when seven wolves are present. Additionally, an alpha wolf (wolf leader) appears and summons wolves in packs.</desc>
	<path>./Popeye no Eigo Asobi (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Portopia Renzoku Satsujin Jiken (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Power Blazer (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Power Soccer (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Puyo Puyo (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc>This is a falling pieces puzzle, Puyo Puyo originated on the MSX system and was later turned into an arcade hall version. Get four same-colored puyos touching each other to make them disappear. If more puyos of the same color are connected then they will disappear too. This game can be played simultaneously by two players for a competitive gameplay. Hinder your opponent by making multiple puyo combinations.</desc>
	<path>./Puzslot (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Quarth (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc>Quarth is a typical puzzle/arcade game. Quarth can be moved  from right to left while the screen scrolls down. The playing field is filled with different blocks and your aim is to fill them in so they form complete rectangles or squares. Only when you succeed in this mission, the concerned blocks will disappear. New 'unformed' blocks appear while the playing field scrolls down making you play into full action at all times. As soon as a line of blocks reaches the bottom line, it is Game Over. Then you 'll be granted 10 seconds to decide if you want continue the level. Each Level consists of 9 Areas and you progress to the next level once you've cleared the last area. The Battle mode is a dual player mode.</desc>
	<path>./Radia Senki - Reimei Hen (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Robocco Wars (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Rockman 2 - Dr. Wily no Nazo (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Romancia (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc>In Romancia: Dragon Slayer Jr., you are a young warrior whom the king sends on a mission to rescue a lost princess. You must leave the town and enter the dreadful monster-infested catacombs in order to complete your quest. 

The game is a departure from Dragon Slayer RPG-oriented gameplay style. It tends more towards medieval-themed platformer action. The hero has hit points, can buy items and weapons, use magic, and stay in inns to recover health. However, instead of receiving experience points and becoming stronger, you simply must attack quicker (by bumping into your opponent on platform levels) and jump higher.</desc>
	<path>./Route-16 Turbo (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc>In Route-16 Turbo, players get behind the wheel of a car and drive around trying to collect valuable items lying around on the road while avoiding chase cars whose only purpose is to crash into the player's car.In the game, the player's car drives around </desc>
	<path>./Saint Seiya - Ougon Densetsu (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Saint Seiya - Ougon Densetsu Kanketsu Hen (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Saiyuuki World 2 - Tenjoukai no Majin (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Sanrio Carnival 2 (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Sanrio Cup - Pon Pon Volley (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Sansara Naga (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./SD Keiji - Blader (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Seirei Gari (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Shanghai (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc>Shanghai is one of the first video game adaptations of the tile-based game played with the Chinese mahjong stones - essentially a puzzle game that has little to do with real mahjong rules.The gameplay involves 144 tiles, each depicting different images, w</desc>
	<path>./Shanghai II (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc>Shanghai II is a variant of the puzzle game also known as solitaire mahjong. 144 mahjong tiles are arranged in rows and stacked upon each other in various patterns; the player's goal is to remove pairs of matching tiles that do not have adjacent tiles fro</desc>
	<path>./Shikinjou (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Shinsenden (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Shufflepuck Cafe (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc>One puck, and only two competitors. One is the computer, and the other is, of course, you. You get a chance to match your skills at this Air Hockey style game, over 'Cantina Band' inspired music. Deflect the puck around the walled area using your bat, trying to knock it into your opponent's goal.

There are several competitors, from which some of them definitely cheat, so be prepared to be laughed at. However, you can cheat as well, as you can resize your stick to fill the whole table width, or add one in the middle, and see who breaks glass first. There are single plays or the tournament where you play opponents in order of difficulty. The winner is the one who reaches 15 glassbreaks first.</desc>
	<path>./Silva Saga (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Sky Destroyer (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc>Sky Destroyer is an aerial combat game. Players take the role of a warplane that has to defeat various enemy combatants in the air and in the sea. The player's warplane is equipped with machine guns and can also fire off torpedoes. The main goal is to des</desc>
	<path>./Softball Tengoku (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Son Son (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc>In this game, you play the role of either Son Son or Ton Ton as you try to rescue your three friends from the clutches of a random bad guy who kidnapped them right in front of you. This game is a side scrolling adventure, where the game field advances automatically, and the screen is divided in six different floors, all of which are populated by enemies or obstacles that will kill you if you touch them; but both Son Son and Ton Ton attack their enemies by shooting small bullets at them out of their weapons (a magic cane and a pitchfork, respectively). Their attack can also stop many enemy projectiles! Your chosen character must jump from floor to floor, evading hunters, bats, fish, statues, insects, skull coins, and mad bombers! As you advance, you can pick up several food items to increase your score. Clearing the screen of enemies will also net you several hefty bonuses.

The story is heavily based upon &amp;quot;Journey To The West&amp;quot;; the player characters as well as the kidnapped ones are based upon the main characters in the story. This game is also a port of Capcom's original arcade game.
</desc>
	<path>./Space Harrier (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc>Run fly dodge those obstacles, but return fire on wave after wave of attacking aliens. Armed with a really big gun, you have to defend yourself against the alien hordes using your wits to navigate around the screen. But watch out for those end of level bosses!</desc>
	<path>./Space Invaders (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc>Earth is under attack from rows of bomb dropping aliens, and you need to defend it! The rows of aliens begin at the top of the screen, and you control a laser cannon at the bottom of the screen. Your goal is to earn points by shooting the aliens before they can land. The aliens march back and forth, and each time the end of the screen is reached they will drop one row closer to the bottom. Shoot them all, and you move on to the next (tougher) level, but if even one of them lands the game is over. From time to time a flying saucer will pass by along the top of the screen; shoot this to earn extra points. Just above your laser canon are three shields; these can be used to hide from the alien's bombs, but will also block your own shots. You begin the game with a limited number of laser canons, and if all of them are bombed the game ends.</desc>
	<path>./Space Shadow (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Spartan X 2 (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc>Somewhat more faithful to the plot of the movie than the first Spartan X game, it attempts to tell the same story: In Barcelona, Mr. X has captured the pickpocket Silvia. In order to get her back, Thomas, a Kung-Fu master who runs a restaurant must travel the city, eventually reaching Mr. X's castle and attempt to rescue her.

Spartan X 2 is an expanded version of the original Spartan X game (aka Kung-Fu). Similar to that game, Spartan X 2 is a side-scrolling fighting game. Controlling Thomas, the player is able to move left and right, jump, kick and punch. Thomas has an energy bar and is defeated if he loses all of the energy. Some enemies drop items such as potions which will help replenish this bar. At the end of each level, Thomas encounters a boss.

Story cutscenes are displayed between each level, where Thomas contacts other characters through use of a computer.</desc>
	<path>./Spelunker II - Yuusha e no Chousen (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Splatterhouse - Wanpaku Graffiti (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc>Wanpaku Graffiti is the first Splatterhouse game to appear on a home console. It is not clear how it fits in the series' timeline, but it starts with Jennifer mourning over Rick's grave (her boyfriend). Lightning strikes his grave and he is resurrected. Before she can rejoice, another bolt strikes the grave next to him and a jack-o-lantern appears. This pumpkin king kidnaps Jennifer and Rick barely has the time to wipe off the dust from his clothes before he sets off to rescue his girlfriend.

Although the game is not as gory as the other titles, there is still plenty of disturbing enemies such as headless chickens, severed hands and zombies. Through seven side-scrolling levels, including a graveyard, a mansion, a Japanese pagoda and an Egyptian pyramid, you chase the pumpkin king with your cleaver and a shotgun you can pick up along the road. Just like the other games in the series, there are lots of movie references. The game often needs good timing and pixel perfect jumps, as falling down from platforms will regenerate the enemies. You can pick up candy, hamburgers and cans of soda to restore your health.
</desc>
	<path>./Sqoon (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Star Luster (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc>In Star Luster, the player controls Dan Heinick, a pilot of the starfighter Gaia. He is tasked with having to fight the evil being Battura and its minions, who are bent on controlling the entire universe.The game is played from an inside the cockpit view.</desc>
	<path>./Star Wars (Japan) (Namco) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Sted - Iseki Wakusei no Yabou (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Stick Hunter - Exciting Ice Hockey (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Sugoro Quest - Dice no Senshitachi (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Summer Carnival '92 - Recca (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Super Arabian (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc>The object of Super Arabian is to collect all the pots on the screen, while avoiding pests like birds and worms who will block your way and eventually destroy you. If they do this, you can kick their Arabian butt and knock them off the screen. If you manage to kick two or more enemies at once, something will hit you that will make you invincible for a few seconds.

It doesn't matter about the order in which you collect the pots. However, each pot has a different letter on it, and if you collect the pots in the order that they appear at the top-right of the screen, you will receive a whopping 5000 points. After you collect the pots, you move on to the next level. There are four levels in each part (section), and each part has a theme to them. In Part 1, Level 1, for instance, you have to collect the letters that make up the word ANIMAL. In subsequent levels, you have to create words that are actual animals (HORSE, RABBIT, MONKEY). Also, if you take too long to complete the level, a red genie will emerge from one of the pots and will attack you.</desc>
	<path>./Super Black Onyx (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc>Rumor says that the legendary Black Onyx, an artifact that grants eternal youth and happiness to those who can find it, lies within the Black Tower near the town of Utsuro. You assemble a party of brave adventurers and venture into the tower, defeating monsters on your way to the great treasure.

The Black Onyx is the very first RPG made by a Japanese company. It is similar in gameplay to early Wizardry and Ultima games with killing monsters and exploring dungeons, with dark, realistic visuals. You create a party (up to five members) and explore a maze-like 3D dungeon, fighting random enemies on the way. You also meet adventurers whom you can convince to join your party. The combat engine is turn-based.
</desc>
	<path>./Super Contra 7 (China) (Unl) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Super Donkey Kong - Xiang Jiao Chuan (China) (Unl) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Super Dyna'mix Badminton (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc>Radically different from other racquet sports such as tennis, badminton uses a high-drag shuttle which gives it an irregular path. In this video game adaptation, the player controls the Japanese player in a competition against five opponents: Canada, USA, UK, South Korea and China. Each match is played on best-of-five sets, played to 15 (boys) or 11 (girls) points. Four different courts can be chosen.

Along the d-pad, two buttons are used to control the player - one to swing the racquet, and other to jump. By following the shadow of the shuttle the player can position himself correctly, and then hit it in perfect timing, giving it enough power and lift to reach the opponent's side, and then (hopefully) descend out of the opponent's reach. Jumping allows the player to hit the shuttle downwards but still over the net, reducing the reaction time for a proper return drastically.</desc>
	<path>./Super Pinball (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Super Xevious - Gump no Nazo (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc>Super Xevious is a 2D shoot 'm up by Namco and is part of the Xevious series. Xevious is known as one of the hardest and fastest shooters around and Super Xevious is even harder and faster!

The enemies of the first Xevious game are back! But this time they are not alone. No, the brought some nasty friends with them!
It is your job, as a fighter pilot, to blast them away! Destroy everything in sight!

Some ground structures that must be destroyed are hidden and are called Sol Citadels. To locate these hidden structures you must keep an eye on the target-sight that will flash when it goes over the structures.

Super Xevious takes all the great elements of the original Xevious and has also some improvements.
Some examples of improvements are, for instance, the shield option and the upgrade option.
The shield protects you from immediately death if you got hit during an attack.
The upgrade option gives you the possibility to upgrade your bombs, lasers and shields.
</desc>
	<path>./Superstar Pro Wrestling (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Sweet Home (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc>"Sweet Home" follows the exploits of five members of
an investigation group: Kazuo, Akiko, Taro, Asuka, and Emi. The famous painter Mamiya Ichirou lived many years in a secluded mansion, and rumor says there are some valuable frescos to find inside. Our investigators decide to take some pictures of the frescos. However, upon entering the mansion, a ghost-like figure of Mamiya appears and threatens them. After this, they find themselves trapped in the mansion. The heroes must now find a way out of the mansion, not forgetting the frescos they came there for, and the destiny of an earlier investigation group that has disappeared under mysterious circumstances.

"Sweet Home" is perhaps the first known example of survival horror genre, created by the same company that later made the famous Resident Evil. However, "Sweet Home" is also a console-style RPG: characters fight random monsters in turn-based battles, equip various weapons and level up. You can (and must) form different teams from the five available characters, both for battles and for solving puzzles. Each character has his (or her) own item-based skill: Taro can take pictures, Emi can unlock almost any door, Kazuo has a lighter, Akiko uses a vacuum cleaner to remove dust and other obstacles, and Asuka has medical kits.

The game was never released outside of Japan.</desc>
	<path>./Taito Chase H.Q. (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc>As an undercover agent of Chase Headquarters, your job is to patrol the streets and track down five criminals. You are given a mission briefing before you start which gives information on the suspect and what car they drive. Then you drive across the city without crashing into other cars, and catch up with the criminal's car. To arrest the suspects, you must keep bumping into their car until it is no longer functional. And you have to do this under a strict time limit. You can't afford to crash into cars or buildings or you waste time getting on the road again. 

However, once you've caught up with your suspect, you are given more time. Your car is also equipped with turbo boosts, which you can use to gain extra speed if you are way behind the criminal. Each arrest is based on a "suspicion".</desc>
	<path>./Taiyou no Yuusha Fighbird (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Takahashi Meijin no Bouken Jima IV (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Takahashi Meijin no Bugutte Honey (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Takeshi no Chousenjou (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Tao (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Tashiro Masashi no Princess ga Ippai (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Tenchi wo Kurau II - Shokatsu Koumei Den (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Tetrastar - The Fighter (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Tetris (Bulletproof) (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc>This version of Tetris is one of many conversions of the famous block-stacking game, as well as the best-known (but not the only) version on Nintendo's first home console. The goal is to place pieces made up of four tiles in a ten-by-twenty well, organizing them into complete rows, which disappear. As rows are cleared, the pace of the game increases, and the game ends if the stack reaches the top of the well.

The game offers two different modes of play, "Type A" and "Type B". "Type A" is a standard endless mode, where the speed of the game increases every ten lines, with an option for the starting level when beginning the game. "Type B", on the other hand, is a race to clear 25 lines, with options for both drop speed and starting garbage. In both modes, successful play is rewarded with cute animations. There are also three different background songs to choose from.</desc>
	<path>./Tetris 2 + Bombliss (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc>Tetris 2 + BomBliss is one of the many versions of the famous soviet puzzle game. There are, naturally, two variations featured on this cartridge: regular Tetris with several modes, as well as a new game called BomBliss. Also included is a two-player battle version of regular Tetris.

Tetris mode includes three game types. First is A-Type, which is a standard endless mode that continually increases pace until the player loses. Next is B-Type, which is a race to 25 lines under increasingly tough conditions. Last is C-Type, which is similar to A-Type, but adds a continually-rising stack of garbage appearing from the bottom of the well.

BomBliss is slightly different from regular Tetris. In each stage, the well is filled with a preset pattern of blocks and bombs. Completing a line will, unlike Tetris, not clear it. It will, however, activate any bombs within the completed line, which can then destroy the blocks. The goal is to clear the entire well of blocks.

BomBliss also includes three different modes of play. Contest mode tasks the player with clearing out a preset field in as few blocks as possible; the top three scores for each stage are saved. Puzzle mode tasks the player with clearing a preset field with a preset sequence of pieces. Last, there is Construction mode, which allows the player to build their own puzzle stages.</desc>
	<path>./Thexder (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc>A platform shooter from Japan, Thexder offers many levels and diverse enemies that gradually increase in difficulty.  You pilot a Battletech-style robot capable of switching from a 'mech into a jet at any time.  Your weapon auto-aims, but uses up a fixed amount of rechargable energy; if you run out of this energy, you'll have to wait a few seconds before you can fire again.  Your 'mech also contains a shield that can be activated to protect you from harm, but this lasts for a few seconds and uses up some of your life energy.</desc>
	<path>./Time Zone (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Titan (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc>Titan is a 2D arcade game / puzzle game hybrid.For some reason, mad professors of the future tend to invent strange entertainment games in which every participant dies. Professor Hybrysâ variant is called Titan and involves a ball, a control unit and 80</desc>
	<path>./Tokkyuu Shirei Solbrain (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Top Rider (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc>Top-Rider is a motorcycle game in which the main objective is to basically make a decent or random time in each race.To achieve a decent time the player must avoid getting off the track and colliding with the "endless" number of motorcycles that will appe</desc>
	<path>./Toukon Club (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Tower of Druaga, The (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc>You control a heroic knight, who is actually prince Gilgamesh, who must attempt to rescue the maiden from the demon Druaga. You are armed with a sword and shield to attack and defend.
You move from floor to floor, which are constructed as mazes, searching for the key, this key will unlock the stage exit.
Items can be found by killing (all) enemies.</desc>
	<path>./Transformers - Convoy no Nazo (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Triathron, The (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./TwinBee (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc>TwinBee is a vertical scrolling shooter. The players control cartoon-like spacecrafts with anthropomorphic arms, player one being TwinBee and player two being WinBee. The spacecrafts can be moved in all 8 directions, with one button for regular shooting flying enemies and one button for dropping ground bombs.

Power-ups in the form of bells can be collected by shooting clouds. The color of the bell will change if it is shot by the player, assuming one of the possible colors:

1. Yellow: grants bonus points;
2. White: upgrades player's guns to a twin cannon;
3. Blue: increases player's speed (up to five levels);
4. Green: creates image copies of the craft for more firepower;
5. Red: provides a shield to sustain damage.

The green and red bells cannot be combined. Alternate power ups can be collected from the ground, such as an alternate bell which upgrades the craft with a three way gun and a star which destroys all enemies on screen.

One shot in the middle section of the craft will destroy it. Shots which hit one of the craft's arms will destroy only the arm. If both arms are lost, the craft won't be able to shoot bombs anymore and will have to be repaired by an ambulance.

In the two-player mode, TwinBee (cyan craft) and WinBee (red craft) have the same speed and they can join "hand-to-hand" and fire a super blast. Also in two player mode, if one craft is hit by the other from behind, it will fire four multi-directional shots.</desc>
	<path>./TwinBee 3 - Poko Poko Daimaou (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Uchuu Keibitai SDF (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc>Space Defence Force SDF is a vertically scrolling space shooter. Though it scrolls vertically, you are granted some movement horizontal movement as well. The action isn't frantic, but the game is still somewhat difficult due to tight enemy attack waves and the possibility of being shot in the back. For this reason, you should not let enemies pass unscathed, since they may shoot back at you from off-screen. At some points, power up capsules will materialize in space. They will grant you not only greater firepower, but also serve as a reconfigurable armor, which is SDF's main selling point. The armor may be moved from your front to your back, and while it is moved in a large arc, it will destroy any enemies it happens to ram. When fastened to your rear, it will also grant a small speed boost. Learning to use the armor is the key to surviving in this game.</desc>
	<path>./Urusei Yatsura - Lum no Wedding Bell (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Valis - The Fantastic Soldier (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Valkyrie no Bouken - Toki no Kagi Densetsu (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Volguard II (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc>Volguard II is a side-scrolling shooter that is a follow-up to Volguard. Players have to shoot their way through 25 areas in one of the four difficulty levels the game offers.Players control a flying craft that has the ability to shoot both bullets and bo</desc>
	<path>./Wagyan Land (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Wagyan Land 2 (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Wai Wai World (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Wai Wai World 2 - SOS!! Paseri Jou (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc>Parsley Castle, an outer space kingdom, has been invaded! And strange beings are to blame. Playing as Rickle, a cyborg built by Dr. Cinnamon from Konami's Twinbee series, and several of his friends from other (mostly Japan-only) Konami games, your objecti</desc>
	<path>./Wanpaku Kokkun no Gourmet World (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Warpman (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc>This game is an updated version of Warp Warp. Players once again take control of the monster fighter as he does battle with various types of enemy Beroberos.The game features two types of gameplay. First, players start out in the Space World. Players cont</desc>
	<path>./Wily &amp; Light no Rockboard - That's Paradise (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Wit's (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Woody Poko (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Yie Ar Kung-Fu (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc>Based on the popular arcade game, Yie Ar Kung-Fu follows Oolong's quest to become a Kung-Fu master.  Of course this involves fighting a wide range of opponents in a traditional one-on-one 2D environment.  Oolong has a wide range of attacks he can use to lower his opponent's life bar, including traditional punching and kicking attacks as well as jumping ones.  Opponents are well armed with unique weapons and attacks, so Oolong's task won't be easy.</desc>
	<path>./Youkai Club (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Ys (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc>You are Adol (Aron in Sega Master System version) Christian, a red-haired adventurer and expert swordsman. One day you encounter a fortuneteller who sends you on a quest to find information about the six books of Ys. It appears that there was once an ancient land called Ys, whose secret was sealed in those six books. Before long you learn that the six books were all stolen by the evil wizard Dark Fact (Dulk Dekt in Sega Master System version, Malificus in PC version). It is your task to defeat the villain and to discover the secret of Ys!

Ys is an action RPG with original combat: instead of pressing the "attack" button, you simply run into the enemies you encounter. You do more damage if you run into them from the back or from the sides - a head-to-head collision might result in Adol's death if the monster is stronger than him. You gain gold and experience points for defeating your foes; once you have gained enough experience, you level up and become stronger. You can buy and equip swords, armor, shields, and other accessories.
</desc>
	<path>./Ys II - Ancient Ys Vanished - The Final Chapter (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc>This is the second game in the long-running Ys action RPG series. A bright light shot up from Dahm Tower in the end of the first game, and our hero Adol Christian is awakened by a young girl who finds him lying on the ground. She introduces herself as Lilia and tells Adol he is in the land of Ys. Finally he was able to establish a connection between his world and this mysterious land! But finding the gateway to Ys is not enough: Adol must stop the evil entity that his archenemy Dark Fact served. And his foes already know where he is...

This game is a direct sequel to what PC players know as Ancient Land of Ys (of which the original NES version was simply called Ys), and is also the same game (story-wise) as the second part of Ys: Book I &amp; II for TurboGrafx CD. The gameplay utilizes an unusual action RPG combat style, where you don't press any attack button, but run into your enemies in order to cause damage. You should choose the angles and the measure of contact with the enemy carefully, otherwise you'll be dead. You can (and should) level up, perform quests for village people, gather money, and upgrade your weapons and inventory, like in any other RPG.
</desc>
	<path>./Ys III - Wanderers from Ys (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc>Adol's long time friend, Dogi wishes to return to his home town of Redmont after hearing about strange disturbances that are happening there.  Always looking for an adventure, Adol joins him and soon finds out the cause of this new evil.

Ys III breaks away from the "bumping into enemies" battle system of the first two games and allows Adol to control his sword in a variety of directions. As well as changing the battle system, the game is now side scrolling instead of the previous games top-down view. Adol also now has the ability to jump. Not new to the series is the use of magical rings which give Adol different powering up abilities such as healing and shielding. The game also uses various key items found along the way to solve minor puzzles and progress the story.
</desc>
	<path>./Yume Penguin Monogatari (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Zippy Race (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc>In a game reminiscent of both Road Fighter and Rally Bike, the player takes control of a motorcyclist who's in a race to be the first to traverse the United States from the west to the east coast, starting in Los Angeles and ending up in New York City.

Gameplay consists of the player dodging cars and other roadway hazards on their way to the next checkpoint. Players can either accelerate or hit the brakes on their motorcycle so they can avoid getting into an accident. Accidents cause the player to lose fuel and running out of fuel can end the game. So players must keep an eye out on the fuel gauge, which can be refilled by fuel barrels littered throughout each stage. Each car the player passes betters their ranks which increases their score.</desc>
	<path>./Zoids - Mokushiroku (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Zombie Hunter (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
	<desc>The city of Palma has always been protected by the spirits of the four elements. However, Dolgo, the spirit of the earth, revolts and makes off with the Life Seeker, the controller of the world's life energies, to his underground lair. In doing so, the people of Palma begin to lose their very souls. The spirit of the air has ordered that a champion needs to be found, to retrieve the Life Seeker from the clutches of Dolgo. You are that champion.

Zombie Hunter is an action-adventure RPG that plays similar to Zelda II with its side-scrolling battles. You receive experience from defeating your enemies and you have an inventory complete with armor and weapons.</desc>
	<path>./Zunou Senkan Galg (Japan).zip</path>
	<desc>The Zystasians are at war with Dragg and his forces and need help from the artificial intelligence battleship Galg. The player is given the mission to collect 100 enemy parts in order to have a final showdown with Dragg.The game is a vertical scrolling sh</desc>
	<path>./1991 Du Ma Racing (China) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./4 Nin uchi Mahjong (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Advanced Dungeons &amp; Dragons - Dragons of Flame (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Airwolf (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Akira (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Akumajou Densetsu (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Akumajou Special - Boku Dracula-kun (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./American Dream (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Ankoku Shinwa - Yamato Takeru Densetsu (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Arctic (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc>Arctic is an action puzzle game that describes itself as "active rail playing". Each of more than two-dozen stages consists of a set of rails in various arrangements, often looping around each other and splitting in various directions. Each stage contains a number of colored balls which begin in corresponding slots, and after launching them the goal is to return the balls to the matching-colored slots. The only interaction the player has with the board is switching two sets of splits; there are yellow and blue splits, which will redirect any balls moving through them, and the player can only turn all of one color as a group. Many stages also contain bumpers and gates which will affect the speed and direction of the balls. Completing a puzzle often requires strategic use of the stage's features to bounce balls onto the correct paths.</desc>
	<path>./Argus (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc>Argus is a standard vertical shooting game like Raptor or Tyrian; this game bears a strong resemblance to Terra Cresta, an arcade game.  There is no story, this game is a straight arcade-action shooter.

The game scrolls upward as waves of enemies attempt to impede your progress, shooting slow and fast moving bullets at your ship. Armed with air-to-air and air-to-ground missiles, blast your way forward while looking for bonuses. Crudely drawn buildings must be shot or avoided since it is possible to crash into them. While moving forward the game allows your ship to move as far left or right as necessary. Finally, at the end of each level you will have to destroy a large enemy.</desc>
	<path>./Arkanoid II (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc>Revenge of Doh is a direct sequel to the original arcade smash Arkanoid. Along with improved graphic engine, better sound and music, better hardware support and more levels, Revenge of Doh also features a built-in editor and allows you to create your own level sets!

Revenge of Doh continues Arkanoid's plot as follows, directly taken (including typoes) from the game:

A long time period passed and the dimension controlling force Doh has again come back to life. Occupying the huge starship Xorg, it has entered our universe from a different dimension. Mixtec, Arkanoid type spaceship, has lauched the craft Vaus II to make a preemptive attack on Xorg.
</desc>
	<path>./Armadillo (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Astro Fang - Super Machine (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Astro Robo Sasa (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc>This is a shooting game with a twist. You are in control of a small character who has to go through a serious of stages. Each stage consists of one screen only and contains several energy packs hidden behind various obstacles. Your goal is to eat up all the energy packs at a given stage, or (which is sometimes easier, but with dire consequences to the later stages) destroy them. If you manage to eat the energy packs, you'll gain more energy points, which carry over to the next stage. You'll need the energy points because every shot from your gun costs you one, and each collision with the various enemies flying around can deplete a large bulk of them. 

The twist of the game is in the movement: instead of simply flying around, you must shoot into the direction opposite of the desired movement. For example, if you shoot several times to the left, you'll be thrown to the right. Everything is built around the reactive force of your gun and the gravity force, which will slowly make you descend onto the ground if you don't shoot continuously. Preserving the precious energy points and trying to propel yourself exactly to the obstacles which you must destroy on your way to the energy packs is the only way to successfully complete the game.</desc>
	<path>./Atlantis no Nazo (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc>In "Atlantis no Nazo", you play a nameless archaeologist who must descend into the dangerous caverns of the lost continent Atlantis, and eventually find his way to the inner sanctum with the legendary treasure. The game plays like a standard action-based platformer. The levels feature plenty of enemies and gaps you must jump over. Your only weapon are sticks of dynamite. When you throw a stick, it will bounce off the floor and explode only after a couple of seconds, so very precise aiming and timing are needed to defeat the enemies. Many levels contain optional treasure chests as well as hidden doors that lead to bonus levels. Sometimes level progression is non-linear, i.e. you can jump straight to a high-numbered zone if you find the correspondent door on the level. All the levels are timed. The protagonist dies when he falls into a pit, touches an enemy, or runs out of time.</desc>
	<path>./Attack Animal Gakuen (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Babel no Tou (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc>Adian no Tsue features two educational math games.  The first game involves controlling a sorcerer named Lucian who is armed with a cane. He is on a mission to rescue Princess Patricia who is being held deep inside a dungeon labyrinth. Gameplay is viewed </desc>
	<path>./Ballblazer (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc>In the year 3037, the most competitive sport in the known universe is Ballblazer. For the first time ever, humans from the planet Earth have won the right to compete in the final round of the Ballblazer Championship, to fight for Earth's honor and the title Masterblazer!

Ballblazer is a 3D futuristic soccer-like game, where the player (inside a Rotofoil) is set on a one-on-one 1,155 square playing field (the Grid). The objective of the player to kick a floating ball (Plasmorb) inside the opponent's goal (Goalbeams). A player may compete against a human or computer opponent.

The Rotofoil is equipped with a multi-purpose forcefield. This forcefield when in short distance of the Plasmorb will act as a pull field, automatically pulling the Plasmorb towards to player. When a player in possession of the Plasmorb shoots, the forcefield will act as push field and launches the ball. When the match starts, the player must move down field and attempt to gain possession of the Plasmorb using the joystick and blast the Plasmorb to an intended direction. 

The player should also be aware that the Goldbeams move slightly every second and the distance between them will shrink. The highest scoring goals are goals made when Goldbeams have disappeared across the horizon (Over The Horizon/OTH shots). A player may also attempt to steal possession of a Plasmorb by rushing beside the opponent and blast the Plasmorb away. The game ends when time runs out or a player wins 10 consecutive goals. If the game ends in a draw, over-time will apply and the first player to score will win the game.

Scoring

Close-in goals - 1 point
Goals near Goldbeams - 2 points
OTH shots - 3 points
Players may steal points from each other by making goals. 
The total combined score of both players cannot accede more than 10 points.
A player winning 10 consecutive points automatically wins the game.</desc>
	<path>./Baltron (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc>In the space year of 2999, the powerful Bismark Empire has decided to launch an attack on the planet Earth. First however, they must occupy a small planet named Star Lenion so they can use it as a launching point for their main attack on the planet Earth.</desc>
	<path>./Banana (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Bats &amp; Terry (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Battle City (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc>Destroy different enemy tanks, while trying to keep them away from your base. When you have destroyed 20 enemy tanks you advance to the next level with different layout. In each level there's some obstacles which you can use to your advantage. Obstacles include red bricks which you can shoot out of your way, silver bricks which are highly armored, water and ice. You start the game with a basic tank, which you can power up to better one little by little. 

The game includes a construction mode, so you can make your own levels when you have played through all the 35 original levels.</desc>
	<path>./Binary Land (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc>In this game, you have to guide two penguins, one male and one female, through top-down vertical levels. The penguins are in love with each other and must be re-united! The penguins start on opposite sides, separated by walls, bricks, and other obstacles. You take control of one of the penguins. The other makes exactly the same movements as you, but in the opposite direction. So if for example you see an enemy to the left of the penguin you are not controlling, you have to fire to the right in order to hit it. You have to reach the top of the level in such a way that the two penguins will arrive at the top square at the same time, coming from opposite sides. Enemies such as spiders will put web on your way or attack you. You can kill them for points. There are various power-ups that appear randomly on the levels. You should also be careful not to run out of time.</desc>
	<path>./Bio Force Ape (Japan) (Proto).nes</path>
	<desc>Originally slated for release in 1991, Bio Force Ape allows you to play as a pet chimpanzee who must rescue his family by taking the mysterious Bio Force serum and mutating into a pro wrestler. It was the recipient of an extremely positive profile in Nintendo Power ? ?extremely positive? being NP?s default setting back in the day ? but then vanished, presumably never to be seen again. Last week, though, the archivists at Lost Levels not only acquired the long-lost prototype cartridge, but uploaded a playable version of it to the Internet.</desc>
	<path>./Bio Senshi Dan - Increaser Tono Tatakai (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc>The year is 2081. The Earth has become a devastated planet, overrun by monsters, controlled by a mysterious entity known as Increaser. The only hope to save the beloved Earth lies with you, a young warrior named Dan. You are sent in a time machine to the year 1999, when the monster invasion was beginning. Your task is to find your way through monster-infested labyrinths and to defeat the Increaser  whatever he (or it) is.

The game is an action platformer with more emphasis on exploration than on "jump &amp; run" gameplay. You don't die immediately if a monster touches you, but have a life bar that gets gradually depleted as you are hit. Defeated enemies bring you energy points, which you can spend to buy upgrades. You start with a sword, but later obtain other weapons as well. The game's structure is not entirely linear; many areas have different doors leading to different places.</desc>
	<path>./Bio-Miracle Bokutte Upa (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Bird Week (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc>In "Bird Week", you control a mother bird, and your goal is to find food for your baby birds. The two babies are sitting on a branch, while you fly around and try to catch some butterflies or other things to feed your children. There are also hostile birds flying around, who try to kill you or take away your food. Once you have given your children enough food, you proceed to the next level.</desc>
	<path>./Blodia Land - Puzzle Quest (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Bloody Warriors - Shan-Go no Gyakushuu (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Bokosuka Wars (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc>King Ogreth of the Basam Empire has invaded your country and either captured or turned into rocks and trees all your soldiers. You, king Suren, are left completely alone. In a desperate attempt, you decide to walk to king Ogreth's castle and to defeat him. You hope you'll be able to find some way to bring your soldiers back to you...

In this strategy game, your goal sounds simple  just walk a distance of 600 meters and defeat king Ogreth. But to do that is not simple at all. Bumping into trees and rocks, king Suren can bring his soldiers to life. Once there are some knights in his small army, he will also be able to free imprisoned soldiers. King Ogreth's units will constantly attack you on the way. The results of the battles are calculated automatically, according to the strength of your units. So before you engage in a battle, you have to be sure you have the upper hand (you have gathered enough soldiers, they have trained in easier battles, etc.). If king Suren dies in a battle, the game is over - you'll have to start from the beginning no matter how near you were to your goal.</desc>
	<path>./Booby Kids (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc>The game is set in a pre-historic environment, complete with cavemen and dinosaurs. You play as a little boy who has to collect treasure without being killed by those ferocious creatures. The only thing you can do to immobilize the enemies is setting a trap right before they approach you. This gives you an opportunity to gain some valuable time. The enemies will pop out of the traps a few seconds later. The game is divided into levels with increasing difficulty. At each level, your goal is to collect all the treasure before you can proceed. You die if you allow an enemy to touch you.</desc>
	<path>./B-Wings (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc>B-Wings is based on the popular arcade game Battle Wings. It is a vertically scrolling space shooter that owes its name to the space fighter from  Star Wars movies. You have a wide variety of weapons at your disposal: Fire, Cannons, Jump, Hammer, etc. Each weapon has its own advantages and disadvantages. For example, Cannon fires powerful and rapid blasts, but you can only shoot directly in front of you; Van covers several directions, but has slow speed; Anti builds a protective shield around you each time you shoot, but its range is very small, and so on. You can change the weapons every time you are killed, before you run out of lives and lose the game. Typically, at the end of a level you'll have to face a boss enemy.</desc>
	<path>./Cadillac (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Captain Silver (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Captain Tsubasa Vol. II - Super Striker (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Castle Quest (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Chack'n Pop (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc>This game is the predecessor of Bubble Bobble and it's
a platform game where a roundish yellow creature, named Chack'n, must fight against Monstas and Mightas. The Monstas hatch from eggs at the ceilings and the Mightas push a rock that is used as the game's timer.
The eggs have three phases: if it's blue, it's completely harmless, if it's yellow it will pop within 10 seconds and if an eggs turns red it will pop almost immediately.
Chack'n uses bombs to release the en-caged hearts and to blow up the Monstas. When the heart is released it will fly up and destroy the separator block between the level and the Mighta. Go to the Mighta and you are in the next level.
After 14 levels there's a wedding between Mr. and Mrs. Chack'n.</desc>
	<path>./Challenger (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc>One of Hudson Soft's earliest NES titles, Challenger is an arcade-style game that combines side scrolling, run 'n jump action with overhead, exploratory gameplay. The game consists of two parts.

The first level (or "scene") has you racing the clock to get to the front of a train, where a purple-faced villain is holding your significant other (or, perhaps just some anonymous princess). You have at your disposal a trusty throwing knife to take care of enemies. You will also have to dodge obstacles and jump gaps in the train. This section is taken from the earlier Hudson game, Stop the Express.

Scene 2 places you in an overhead, maze-like environment, where you once again have to fight the clock. This time though, you have to navigate your way through the area, in search of all the different "keywords", which are placed in different caves. Once you have cleared all the caves, the path will be open to the boss' final lair.</desc>
	<path>./Championship Lode Runner (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc>A follow-up to the original Lode Runner, with identical gameplay.  This package contained 50 of the most challenging levels ever designed, and was intended for expert players only.  It did not include the level editor, you had to play through the levels in order, but a save-game option was provided (although you lost one life every time you restored).</desc>
	<path>./Chaos World (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Chess Academy (China) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Chester Field - Ankoku Shin e no Chousen (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Chiisana Obake - Acchi Socchi Kocchi (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Cho Jiku Yosai Macross (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc>In this side-scrolling shooter, players take control of a VF-1 Valkyrie and do battle with the forces of the Zentradi. The main goal is to enter the Zentradi ship and destroy its reactor core.The players Valkyrie can change its appearance and abilities by</desc>
	<path>./Choplifter (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc>Choplifter is a side-scrolling action/arcade game that puts you in command of an attack chopper.  Your mission: Go behind enemy lines and rescue up to 16 hostages per level.  Be careful, though, because tanks and enemy aircraft will try to stop you -- and they won't stop shooting while you are rescuing those hostages!

Originally released for Apple II home computers, Choplifter was later ported to the arcades and a number of video game consoles. Many imitators and homages would follow.</desc>
	<path>./Choujin Sentai - Jetman (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Choujinrou Senki Warwolf (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Chuuka Taisen (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Circus Charlie (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc>You are Charlie, a member of a circus troupe. Your job is to please the crowd by performing five death-defying stunts:

Stunt #1: You and the lion must jump through several rings of fire. Remember to avoid the jugs that emit fire. You must do this for 100 meters.

Stunt #2: Walk the tightrope for 70 meters, avoiding the monkeys that get in your way. Jump the cyan monkeys for 500 points.

Stunt #3: Roll on a ball for 80 meters, jumping from ball to ball. You can move balls backwards if the target is too close to make a successful jump. Avoid contact with the ground.

Stunt #4: Ride a horse for 200 meters, bouncing on trampolines along the way. Be careful not to miss the jump or go over the tops of trampolines. You can speed up or slow down the horse.

Stunt #5: Finally, trapeze from swing to swing for 50 meters. If you miss, make sure that you land on the platforms below so you bounce back on a swing.

Once you have completed all five stunts, you have to do them again and hopefully, more points will be awarded.</desc>
	<path>./Cocoron (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Columbus - Ougon no Yoake (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc>In "Columbus: Ougon no Yoake" you take control of young Columbus, who is dreaming to sail the seas and explore the world. You start at the age of 14, becoming a apprentice aboard an old ship, where you learn the basics of combat. Your ultimate goal in this role-playing-game is to discover the continent America, just like the original model Christoph Kolumbus.
The Game can be played in two different modes. Either in "Normal Mode" or in "Historical Mode". The only difference of the historical mode compared to the normal mode, is that you have a limited ammount of time to complete the game. You start in December of 1465 and the game then ends by the end of 1492. The time ticks off, based on the number of steps you take, what means that you'll want to keep your steps as low as possible.
Discover the new world and take your place in history!</desc>
	<path>./Contra (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Cosmic Epsilon (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Cosmo Genesis (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Cosmo Police Galivan (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Crazy Climber (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc>As Crazy Climber, climb your way to the top of a series of buildings, where a helicopter is waiting to pick you up and take you to the next building. As Climber scales a building, he is able to climb up and sideways but he cannot climb down.
While climbing a building, windows will open and close simultaneously. If any window closes on either of his hands he will lose his grip. However, if a window closes on both of his hands, he will fall to his death, resulting in the loss of a life. You have three Climbers in total, but you are awarded an extra Climber every 30,000 points. Besides windows, Climber is faced with other dangers, including:

1. Bald-headed guys who hurl various objects at you.
2. Pesky condors who fly by, dropping eggs and droppings of an unpleasant substance.
3. Falling steel girders and iron dumbells.
4. Electrical "Nichibutsu" signs with a dangling live wire.
5. Falling "Crazy Climber" signs.
6. King Kong leaping from side to side of the building and slams his hands against the windows.

The climber must try to avoid or overcome each of those hazards which he will encounter as he continues climbing in his attempt to reach the rooftop. If he falls to his death by windows or objects, another climber will replace him and will start at the same location where the last one fell. The specific danger will not be present at the same point, so the climber can go further up to face the next danger. Most of the hazards are announced by certain recognizable musical themes. 

Crazy Climber is awarded a bonus score on each building every time after getting carried off by the helicopter. However, each bonus score will decrease by every ten seconds that the climber will spend scaling each building as he attempts reach the top. Somewhere in the game, there is "The Lucky Balloon", which can lift Climber about ten stories and raise the player's bonus score if he catches it.</desc>
	<path>./Crisis Force (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Cycle Race - Road Man (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Dai Meiro - Meikyuu no Tatsujin (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Dai-2-Ji Super Robot Taisen (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Daisenryaku (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc>One of many grand war simulations in Daisenryaku series, Daisenryaku for Famicom is a turn-based strategy with quite modern armies, the abstract "Blue" and "Red" countries (controlled by the player or AI), are at war with each other.Three basic phases mak</desc>
	<path>./Daiva Story 6 - Imperial of Nirsartia (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Dark Lord (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Dash Yarou (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Deblock (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc>De-Block is a puzzle game that can be most easily explained as a 4-way Tetris. The player controls a block in the center of the screen which can move and rotate freely. Larger blocks move inward from each side of the screen and attach to the center block, then change color depending on their distance from the center. If the player completes a colored ring, that layer and all the blocks inside of it are cleared, and all the ones outside are moved inward. Play ends if a newly-appearing block overlaps with the player's structure.</desc>
	<path>./Deep Dungeon III - Yuushi heno Tabi (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Deep Dungeon IV - Kuro no Youjutsushi (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Devil Man (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Dezaemon (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc>Dezaemon is a game designing application that lets aspiring developers create their own vertical scrolling shoot-'em-up. Players have control over how their ship looks, design how their levels (up to three) will look, and also create a title screen. Playe</desc>
	<path>./Dig Dug (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc>Dig Dug is a 1-2 player arcade game in which you have to use your shovel to dig your way through the earth. Stopping you from doing this are two monsters, called Pooka and Fygar, who will continually chase you around. The only weapon that you carry is an air pump, which you can use to inflate the monsters to the point where they explode. (if you start to inflate them but stop doing so, the monsters will get turned back to their normal selves.) Furthermore, rocks are scattered throughout the earth, and you can use these rocks to squash them. If the monsters do not find you for several seconds, they will eventually get turned into ghosts, which are able to walk through the earth. They are invincible and cannot be killed. From time to time, vegetables will appear in the center, and you can get these for points.</desc>
	<path>./Digital Devil Monogatari - Megami Tensei (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc>A high-school student and skillful computer programmer named Akemi Nakajima created a software called "Devil Summoning Program". At first Nakajima intended to use the software to gain revenge on a classmate who bullied him. However, things went out of control and Nakajima summoned malicious demons. Together with his friend Yumiko Shirasagi, a transfer student, he now must fight the demons he unleashed!</desc>
	<path>./Don Doko Don (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc>In this game, you play a bearded dwarf whose girlfriend has been kidnapped and taken away to the dragon's castle, and in order to rescue her, you must defeat enemies with your mallet. Once you do, you can pick them up and throw them at other enemies, and collect the fruit that they leave behind. When you have defeated all enemies, you proceed onwards to the next round. If you take too long to complete a level, a winged devil will appear who will try to kill you while flying around the screen

Occasionally, power-ups will appear in the middle of the level, and these power-ups will increase your power, award you with different weapons, kill enemies, or freeze time. The more power you have, the more walls that you can through enemies through. At maximum power, you are able to throw enemies through all walls.
If you happen to carry the blue hammer, you are able to throw it through walls, too.

There are five areas that consist of ten levels each. At the end of each area, you have to defeat a boss in order to proceed further.</desc>
	<path>./Don Doko Don 2 (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Donald Land (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc>The game stars Ronald McDonald (known in Japan as Donald McDonald), the mascot of the McDonald's fast food chain. The objective is to bring peace to his magical land by controlling the famous fast food clown. Most of Ronald's companions have been kidnapped, and the animals have turned feral. His brainwashed companions will occasionally attack. Ronald can defend himself using apple bombs, thrown in a carefully calculated parabola.Being hit by the enemy causes damage, which decreases Ronald's "Life" meter. During various parts of a stage, players have the opportunity to collect up to 100 hamburger icons throughout the game. This will result in gaining a bonus life along with the hamburger counter resetting itself to zero. It is also possible to play a mini-game challenge, to earn commodities that the player orders from McDonald's.
</desc>
	<path>./Door Door (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc>DoorDoor is platform game in which you have to lock up the monster creatures that pursue you. Only one creature can be locked up behind one door. Don't forget to close the door or the creatures will walk out and pursue you again.</desc>
	<path>./Doraemon - Giga Zombie no Gyakushuu (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Doraemon (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Dough Boy (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc>The president has been kidnapped and it is currently being held behind enemy lines. Players take control of a soldier who has to cross through the enemy lines to rescue this very important prisoner of war.  The game consist of five different timed maps wh</desc>
	<path>./Downtown Special - Kunio-kun no Jidaigeki Da yo Zenin Shuugou! (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Dragon Ball - Daimaou Fukkatsu (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Dragon Ball - Shenron no Nazo (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Dragon Ball Z - Kyoushuu! Saiya Jin (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Dragon Ball Z Gaiden - Saiya Jin Zetsumetsu Keikaku (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Dragon Ball Z III - Ressen Jinzou Ningen (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Dragon Buster (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc>"Dragon Buster" is a conversion of Namco's arcade game from 1984. The game is composed of several large levels, each one containing various stages: a cave, a tower, a castle, etc. Your goal in every level is to reach the final stage where you face the level boss. There are often several ways to reach the final stages, and not all stages are necessary to visit. Equipped with a sword, you move through the platform-like stages, clearing them of diverse monsters, collecting power-ups and trying to stay in good health until the level boss, since you can't heal your character between the stages.</desc>
	<path>./Dragon Buster II - Yami no Fuuin (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Dragon Knife (China) (Unl) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Dragon Ninja (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Dragon Scroll - Yomigaerishi Maryuu (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc>Aeons ago, two dragons and their follower were fighting each other. The  "Black Mages" worshipped the three-headed Chrome Dragon, and the "White Mages" worshipped the glimmering Gold Dragon. The wars fought for territory and ideals where endless. After ages of fighting, the god Narume put the Chrome Dragon to sleep in the mountains and the Gold Dragon to sleep in the desert, to stop the wars. Then he took th magic away from the mages, and sealed it in the 8 Magic Books, which he hid in the sacred desert tower.

Hundreds of years later, three thieves stumbled upon the desert tower, and found the Magic Books. They split them up amongst themselves and every one of them, walked his own way. Now that the Magic Books were gone, the Chrome Dragon awoke from his slumber. Narume then infused the Gold Dragon with the spirit of justice, summoning him forth in the form of a hero named "Feram"
Now it is up to him, to find the Magic Books and put the Chrome Dragon to sleep again.</desc>
	<path>./Dream Master (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Dynamite Bowl (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc>Dynamite Bowl is a bowling game simulation based on the real bowling sport and can be played up to five players at one of the thirty lanes.
The game has two difficulty levels.
Game variables that can be controlled are: your position at the lane, set the strength of the throw and control the loft and curve of the bowling ball.</desc>
	<path>./Eggerland - Meikyuu no Fukkatsu (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Egypt (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Elnark no Zaihou (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Elysion (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Esper Bouken Tai (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Esper Dream 2 - Aratanaru Tatakai (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc>Far beyond our world, there's a world that resides in the books you read. But the five areas of the Book Worlds are in deep trouble! As Mamoru, a bookworm with ESP, you must go forth (with the help of a magical fairy and several other allies) to grab five</desc>
	<path>./Exciting Boxing (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Exciting Rally - World Rally Championship (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Exed Exes (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc>On a planet 6000 light-years from earth, there were creatures called Exes, which resemble large insects, that were used for industrial purposes. However, these creatures one day took to revolting against their creators. Two battle machines have been sent to fight against the Exes, known as Colonel and Sargent. The Exes are nearing completion of their secret weapon, Exed Exes, and they must be defeated before this is allowed to happen!

Exed Exes is a basic vertical scrolling shooter, converted from the 1985 coin-op. The game scrolls forward, and the player can maneuver their ship around the screen to shoot enemies and avoid attack. POW icons sometimes appear that can power up the ship or turn enemies into fruit that are worth extra points. The game can be played either solo or two-player cooperatively.</desc>
	<path>./Exerion (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc>This is a shoot-em-up game with parallax effects in the background. It does have a simulation of inertia in the control of the ship.
There are dozens of enemies and two types of shooting: slow and fast. Two weapon systems: one slow double-shot cannon and one fast single-shot cannon.
With each enemy hit by the slow cannon you get one shot added to the fast cannon ammunition supply.
A challenge stage follows each stage in which you can build up your fast-shot bullet supply.</desc>
	<path>./F-1 Race (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc>In this game, which is similar to Pole Position, the player takes control of an F1 car. The player can race the vehicle on one of three different skill levels. Each skill level contains five different tracks for the player to race on. On each of these tracks, the player must complete 2 laps before a countdown timer expires. The player must also try not to crash into other racers and obstacles on the sides of the road. The vehicle has a manual transmission, so the player has to switch between low and hi gear while racing.
</desc>
	<path>./Famicom Wars (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Fantasy Zone 2 - Opa-Opa no Namida (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc>Fantasy Zone II: The Tears of Opa-Opa is the sequel to Fantasy Zone, in which you control Opa-Opa, a pretty colored ship with wings on its side. You must destroy the large creatures in each world before moving on to the next. Your task becomes difficult by other small creatures that happen to pass by. If you destroy a large creature, they will drop a dollar bill, which you can pick up and use at the shop to buy items and powerful weapons such as laser beams, x-way shots, and big wings. Another way to get money is to shoot certain kinds of enemies all in a row.

More often than not, some large creatures will reveal a warp gate rather than a dollar bill. You can go through the warp gate to get to another part of the land, and destroy more large creatures. Only one of them will have a warp gate in the form of a 'stop' sign - that is your ticket to the round boss, but you must defeat all large creatures in order to pass through it. Also like in the original can you walk on the ground to avoid approaching enemies, and spend money in the shop to get new weapons (but they only last for a limited time).</desc>
	<path>./Field Combat (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc>Players are assigned the role as the field commander of the blue colored forces who are in a battle against the red colored forces. Players take control of the Genesis, a flying saucer shaped craft, that can fire missiles, capture enemy units with a tract</desc>
	<path>./Final Fantasy II (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Final Fantasy III (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Final Fantasy VII (China) (Unl) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Final Lap (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc>Final Lap by Namco is considered by many to be the spiritual successor to Pole Position. This fairly straightforward Formula 1 racing game features a one or two player mode which is raced via split-screen. Up to eight players can take turns playing in a tournament mode. 

The initial race takes place on an oval track in New York while subsequent tracks with more challenging turns and corners will take players all over the world; from Mexico to Monaco. Each car can be upgraded before a race with allotted points to customize the tires, engine, brakes, and nitro. Nitro is kicked in by pressing up on the control pad. Colliding into competitors will bump your car back but sliding into billboards on the side can cause your vehicle to spin out.</desc>
	<path>./Final Mission (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Fire Emblem (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Fire Emblem Gaiden (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Flappy (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc>In this puzzle game, you control Flappy, a yellow mole.  The object of the game is to help Flappy push the Blue Stone onto its Blue Platform in each level.

Red Stones are placed in key locations across the levels. They can be pushed, stacked on top of each other, and even destroyed. Flappy must strategically take advantage of the gravity and the Red Stones in order to clear the path for pushing the Blue Stone. Three different types of enemies will try to prevent Flappy from clearing the level, so you must either avoid the enemies, crush them from above with the Stones, or pick up Sleeping Mushrooms to knock them out temporarily.</desc>
	<path>./Fleet Commander (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Flipull - An Exciting Cube Game (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Flying Hero (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Formation Z (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc>The player competes in a marathon continuous scrolling horizontal shoot-em-up game across land, sea, air and outer space. You can hold down the fire button for a burst of Charged fire, which is especially essential to defeat the bosses.

The player can hold down the Jump button to transform back and forth between a Mobile Robot or an Aero Fighter. Some sections have confrontations on both ground and air; others insist on aerial battling. Your time in the Aero Fighter is limited by its fuel requirement.</desc>
	<path>./Front Line (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc>Front Line is a vertically scrolling action game. Your mission is to infiltrate enemy territory and destroy their fortress. To reach the fortress, you will have to make your way through varied and dangerous terrain. Jungles, deserts, brush, and rocks all slow your progress, plus each area has numerous enemy fighters and tanks trying to stop you. To help get past these obstacles, you are armed with a machine gun and grenades; at some points in the game you may even come across an abandoned tank which you can control to increase your odds of survival. When you reach the end of the level and successfully destroy the fortress, the game will repeat at a higher level of difficulty. Gameplay is for one or two players, and four different skill levels are available.</desc>
	<path>./Fudou Myouou Den (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Fushigi no Umi no Nadia (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Fuzzical Fighter (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Galaxian (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc>Galaxian is a shoot 'em up in which the player is at the bottom of the screen, with an arrangement of aliens at the top. The player moves left and right to aim at an alien, then shoots a bullet up the screen, and the alien it hits is killed. The aliens are classed as Drones, Emissaries, Hornets and Commanders, with those higher up the screen scoring more points when destroyed. At set intervals an enemy will move down the screen towards you, escorting a bomber, which is a moment of high danger. Clear a wave and another is generated.</desc>
	<path>./Game Party (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc>Game Party allows you to play 5 different games on one cartridge. The games involved are Air Hockey, Hockey, Pinball, Basketball, and  Mind-Q. So grab a friend and start playing some good multiplayer games!</desc>
	<path>./Ganbare Goemon 2 (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Ganbare Goemon! - Karakuri Douchuu (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Garfield - A Week of Garfield (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc>Garfield, the lovable fat orange cat, has gotten himself into a spot of trouble. His pal and center of abuse, the yellow dog Odie, has gone and disappeared somewhere. Their owner, Jon, is too lazy to go look for Odie himself, so he has Garfield go out and look for him. And so Garfield heads off, out into the world.

A Week of Garfield is a side-scrolling platform game based on the comic strip by Jim Davis. Garfield heads to the right through various indoor and outdoor city environments, dealing with endless vermin like frogs, birds, and mice using his judo kick skills and several different weapons such as bones that can be thrown. He has a life bar that can quickly deplete if he isn't careful, but hidden all around each stage are various items, which can replenish his health, refill his weapon supplies, and give him super speed or invincibility; be careful, though, as sometimes he'll also find fish bones which will harm Garfield if eaten.

The game is divided into seven stages, each representing a day of the week, and each with several sections. At the end of each section is a door, and Garfield must find the key hidden somewhere on the screen to unlock the door and continue. At the last door of each stage, there is a boss that must be defeated before Garfield can find the key. Each stage also has a strict time limit to keep him from dawdling, and between stages, Jon will appear to encourage Garfield or give him some advice.</desc>
	<path>./Gegege no Kitarou - Youkai Daimakyou (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Gegege no Kitarou 2 - Youkai Gundan no Chousen (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Geimos (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc>Geimos is an arcade style space shooter where players take control of a spaceship that flies over several different planets' surfaces destroying the incoming enemy units. The game contains two different game modes. "Mode A" keeps the games camera perspect</desc>
	<path>./Gekitotsu Yonku Battle (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Getsu Fuuma Den (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Golf '92, The (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Golf Club - Birdie Rush (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Goonies (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc>The Goonies is based on a movie of the same name from 1985. A group of youngsters from a neighborhood called the "Goon Docks" are trying to find the lost treasure of One-Eyed Willie to prevent the foreclosure of their houses. Unfortunately, the treasure is buried under the hide-out of the infamous Fratelli gang, a family of ruthless criminals who are on the run from the law. You play as the asthmatic Mikey, who must find the treasure and save the other Goonies before time runs out.

The game consists of six levels. In each level, you must collect three keys to advance to the next area. These can be found by blowing open doors with bombs that are dropped by enemies. Also hidden behind doors are power-ups and other Goonies to rescue. Trying to stop you are enemies such as rats, skeletons, and even members of the Fratelli Gang. Bonus points can be gained by picking up diamonds and other valuables, rescuing the other Goonies, or by dispatching enemies with your slingshot or kicking them.

Unlike the sequel, the Famicom version was never released outside of Japan.</desc>
	<path>./Gorby no Pipeline Daisakusen (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Gradius II (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc>Gradius II is a sequel to Gradius, and Life Force, and is a horizontal space shooter composed of 7 levels.
Like it's predecessor, you can collect power up from enemies and chose which ones to use when. This time, this system is enhanced because you can chose between 4 different power-up sequences, allowing you to use differents types of weapons against your enemies. There is also the possibility to gain options, which are mysterious balls of fire that follows your spaceship closely and mimic all its movements (including shots). While you only could have 2 of them in Gradius, you now can have up to 4 of them.</desc>
	<path>./Grand Master (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Great Deal (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Gyrodine (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc>Gyrodine is basic vertical shooter based on Taito's arcade game with the same name. You pilot a helicopter and have to shoot as many enemies you can. You will fight against enemy helicopters, bunkers, tanks and fighter jets above different terrains like water, desserts and military camps. There is no background story and there are no levels.</desc>
	<path>./Hebereke (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Heisei Tensai Bakabon (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Hello Kitty no Ohanabatake (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc>During the course of this video game, Hello Kitty must water all the flowers in each stage while avoiding the many animals and insects. Kitty's ribbon always stays on the left side of her ear; even if the player changes the orientation of the character.
She can defend herself with the use of a large mallet. Running into enemies will make her cry, which causes Kitty to get angry and lose a life. Points in the game are collected as money for the cash register. Allowing the time limit to expire will also cause the player to lose a life. However, there are infinite continues and losing the game score is the only penalty for "game overs." There are 18 stages in the game and the game does not repeat itself after the 18th stage. While the second half of the game is more difficult then the first nine levels, they can be cleared once the player is accustomed to the game controls.</desc>
	<path>./Hello Kitty World (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Heracles no Eikou - Toujin Makyou Den (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Heracles no Eikou II - Titan no Metsubou (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Hi no Tori Hououhen - Gaou no Bouken (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Higemaru Makaijima - Nanatsu no Shima Daibouken (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Hikari no Senshi Photon - The Ultimate Game on Planet Earth (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Hirake! Ponkikki (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Hitler no Fukkatsu - Top Secret (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Hokuto no Ken (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Holy Diver (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Honoo no Doukyuuji - Dodge Danpei (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Honoo no Doukyuuji - Dodge Danpei 2 (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Hottaman no Chitei Tanken (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Hyaku no Sekai no Monogatari - The Tales on a Watery Wilderness (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Hyper Sports (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc>Six tough events await in this joystick-waggling action game. The full sequence of events is - swimming, skeet shooting, gymnastics, archery, triple jumping and weightlifting. You must complete each event in order to be allowed onto the next one.Swimming </desc>
	<path>./Ike Ike! Nekketsu Hockey-bu - Subette Koronde Dairantou (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Ikinari Musician (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc>Ikinari Musician lets players interact with a keyboard synthesizer. Players can select beats from different musical genres the world over. Players can create riffs, turn on or off the instruments they want to use, and change the way the notes are displaye</desc>
	<path>./Ikki (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc>They are currently involved in an uprising against their feudal lord. The feudal lord has dispatched his army of ninjas t</desc>
	<path>./Insector X (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./J.League Fighting Soccer - The King of Ace Strikers (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./J.League Winning Goal (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Jajamaru Gekimaden - Maboroshi no Kinmajou (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Jajamaru no Daibouken (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Jekyll Hakase no Houma ga Toki (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Jesus - Kyoufu no Bio Monster (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Jigoku Gokuraku Maru (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Jikuu Yuuden - Debias (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./JJ - Tobidase Daisakusen Part II (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Joy Mech Fight (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc>The evil scientist Warunachi has hacked all the otherwise peaceful robots in Japan and now plans to launch an attack for world domination the likes of which the world has never seen. Fortunately his former partner, Dr. Eamon, saved one robot from the takeover and has now programmed him to defeat the other robots and foil Dr. Warunachi's evil plans.

Joy Mecha Fight is a one-on-one 2D fighter, in which you control a robot and attempt to defeat your opponent by attacking him with your basic moves and special attacks triggered by specific control motions. Each robot is composed of six hovering segments: the head, torso and limbs, which hover around each other forming a basic humanoid shape. 

The game features story, instant fight, and Vs modes. In the story mode you start with the Sukapon robot, and as you defeat other robots they become available for selection as you advance through the story with all moves being explained via a pre-fight tutorial if you want to.
</desc>
	<path>./Jumbo Ozaki no Hole in One Professional (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc>This is the second golf game from HAL Laboratory after Hole in One. Like it's predecessor, Hole in One Professional is a standard 18-hole golf game, played from a top-down perspective. Players can compete in stroke play with up to four players, or match play against a friend or the computer. When playing against the computer, the player will play against an opponent that uses metal clubs, which hit farther than the standard wooden clubs.

In addition to stroke and match play, players can obtain passwords that allow a replay of any spectacular shots that are made (eagles, holes-in-one, and double-eagles).</desc>
	<path>./Just Breed (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc>The town of Astholm is protected by a Sapphire, one of the magical stones mentioned in old legends. Generation of honorable priestesses protect the stone, and with it the town. Tonight is the annual Sapphire Festival, and the young priestess Firis is going to conduct the ceremony. But just after the joyous event, the priestess is kidnapped by Gel du Rey, the henchman of the evil Lord Ezelkiel. You play the role of the captain of Astholm's guards. You and Firis have been close friends ever since the childhood. You decide to rescue the priestess, with the help of your loyal guards and friends you meet on your journey.

Just Breed is a hybrid of traditional console-style RPG like Dragon Warrior or Final Fantasy, and strategy RPG. During confrontations with the enemies, the battle screen occupies the entire location, and large parties of allies and enemies fight each other in turn-based style, moving on the field to perform physical attacks (melee as well as ranged) or to cast magic spells.</desc>
	<path>./Juuouki (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Juuryoku Soukou Metal Storm (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Juvei Quest (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Kaguya Hime Densetsu (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Kai no Bouken - The Quest of Ki (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Kaijuu Monogatari (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Kaiketsu Yancha Maru 2 - Karakuri Land (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Kaiketsu Yancha Maru 3 - Taiketsu! Zouringen (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Kanshakudama Nage Kantarou no Toukaidou Gojuusan Tsugi (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc>Players take the role of Kantarou, whose occupation is to make fireworks. He is currently traveling on the Tokaido highway starting in Kyoto trying to make his way home to Edo, where his girlfriend Momoko resides. However, this is a long walk home as the </desc>
	<path>./Karakuri Kengoden Musashi Lord - Karakuri Jin Hashiru! (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Karateka (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc>The evil Akuma has destroyed your homeland, killed many of your friends and kidnapped your Princess Mariko. Fortunately, you are skilled in Martial Arts, so your inevitable quest to reach Akuma's palace has a chance of success.

The game is viewed from the side and features a succession of increasingly-difficult opponents. All the standard karate kicks and punches are available to both you and your foes. The game's design was serious and realistic, and the game featured lots of cutscenes to develop the story.</desc>
	<path>./Karnov (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Kawa no Nushi Tsuri (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Keisan Game - Sansuu 1 Nen (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Keisan Game - Sansuu 3 Nen (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Keisan Game - Sansuu 4 Nen (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Keisan Game - Sansuu 5+6 Nen (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Kekkyoku Nankyoku Daibouken (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Kero Kero Keroppi no Daibouken (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Kero Kero Keroppi no Daibouken 2 - Donuts Ike wa Oosawagi! (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Keroppi to Keroriinu no Splash Bomb! (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./King Kong 2 - Ikari no Megaton Punch (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Kinnikuman - Muscle Tag Match (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Kouryuu Densetsu Villgust Gaiden (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Kujaku Ou (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Kujaku Ou II (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Kunio-kun no Nekketsu Soccer League (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Kyatto Ninden Teyandee (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Kyouryuu Sentai Zyuranger (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Labyrinth - Maou no Meikyuu (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc>Labyrinth is a maze game similar to Gauntlet, but with a more definite goal and some adventure elements. It is based upon the Jim Henson film of the same name incorporates many scenes from the movie as areas with the maze.

The goal of the game is to collect twelve coins Sara can use to buy back her baby brother from his kidnapper, the goblin king, Jareth. There is one coin in each of the twelve mazes surrounding the central castle. At first only a few of the mazes are accessible; however, upon collecting a section of a broken key, of which there is also one per region, Sara is sent to a hub where a friendly goblin will open up a new area. Each section of the maze has its own gimmick, for instance the Hedge Maze rearranges itself as the player wanders through it, and the Fieries' Forest is filled with teleports. The areas are also connected via a large underground maze. Upon gaining all the sections of the key Sara can open the door to the castle and enter the final series of mazes, however, she cannot win if she has not collected all of the coins.

Throughout all this Sara is constant beset by enemies at which she must throw a neverending supply of stones to dissipate. Her stones can be upgraded eventually and she can also gain the favor of her friends from the movie who will follow her around and try to help her shoot at her aggressors.

All of this must be done in no more than 13 minutes or the game must be restarted, and every time an enemy attacks Sara she loses a few more seconds. However, there are several ways to gain more time, and part of winning the game is balancing actually solving the maze and spending time searching for minutes to do just that.</desc>
	<path>./Lagrange Point (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Layla (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc>LayLa is on a mission to rescue her friend Iris from an evil doctor who has kidnapped her. This mission will take LayLa through eight different explorable asteroids.Gameplay mainly involves controlling LayLa through the cavernous maze-like asteroids shoot</desc>
	<path>./Lost Word of Jenny - Ushinawareta Message (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Lot Lot (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc>Lot lot is a puzzle game. The goal of the game is of extreme simplicity. Manipulate the balls in such a way till they fall into the pits and generating points.

The game has five pits: Out, 0 points, 10 points, 30 points and 50 points.

Each level starts by giving you a target score that you'll have to reach before you continue to the next level.

The screen is divided into sixteen sections. The walls of those sections randomly disappear and the balls will then drop or roll into the other section or a pit at the bottom of the screen.

On the screen you will find two arrows of which the second arrow follows the first one but with a slight delay and it stops at the same position as the first one.

The arrows will start in an empty section of which one of the walls will soon disappear. To move the balls to the empty section move your first arrow to a section that is filled with balls end press the space bar or fire button. The balls will then be moved to the empty section.
If both sections contain balls then the balls will be swapped accordingly.

Now you have to manipulate the balls in such a way that they will generating points by getting them to the pits that generate points.

In the bottom left of the screen there is a section that has a thin red line at the bottom. Never move the balls in that section because if any balls enter that section a crab will appear and cut the red line with it's razor sharp claws. The balls will disappear in the pit labeled 'OUT' and you loose a life.</desc>
	<path>./Lupin Sansei - Pandora no Isan (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Mad City (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Madoola no Tsubasa (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc>The Kingdom of Badham was once the host of the legendary Wing of Madoola bird statue. Anyone who possessed the wing would be granted tremendous power. Many wars were caused by nations wanting to have control over this powerful artifact. Thankfully, a king</desc>
	<path>./Magic John (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Magical Doropie (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Magnum Kikiippatsu - Empire City - 1931 (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc>In this arcade hall conversion of Empire City: 1931 which is set in 1931 you are a federal agent that has to eliminate all criminal activities in New York City.
You must hunt the criminals down and shoot them one by one. To locate a criminal you just have to follow the arrow on the left or right of the screen. Killing criminals is done by moving the cross hair over them.
A countdown timer will start counting down if a criminal starts shooting at you. You must kill the criminal before the timer reaches zero or you'll loose a life.
New bullets can be collected by shooting at the bullet boxes that regularly appear in the game as other useful objects.
The criminals sometimes take hostages for protection. Rescue these hostages for additional points.

Firing your gun is done with fire button 1 and deflecting bullets by pressing the fire button 2.
</desc>
	<path>./MahaRaja (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Majin Eiyuuden Wataru Gaiden (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Majou Densetsu II - Daimashikyou Galious (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Mappy (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc>You control Mappy a police-mouse whose job is to collect valuables (consumer electronics)from a cat's house. You are being pursued by a gang of five pink cats. Doors are your only defense against the cats. You get from floor to floor by jumping on one of the trampolines.
Points are earned by recovering stolen goods. Other ways of earning points are bouncing on a trampoline, putting cats in the microwave, striking a cat with a door, striking cats with a bell, retrieving a treasures from the Boss cat Goro or dropping cats through a hole in the floor.</desc>
	<path>./Mappy Kids (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Matendouji (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Metro-Cross (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc>Simple side-scrolling game, where you play a skater who has to pass a set of obstacles in order to reach the end of the level.

You can skate up or down in the screen, or even jump, to be safe from the pipes you encounter on the way. As the game progresses, obstacles are more frequent and more challenging, but the essence is the same. Timing is everything in this game.</desc>
	<path>./Mickey Mouse 3 - Yume Fuusen (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Minelvaton Saga - Ragon no Fukkatsu (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Mini Putt (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Minna no Taabou no Nakayoshi Daisakusen (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Miracle Ropit's Adventure in 2100 (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Mirai Senshi - Lios (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Mirai Shinwa Jarvas (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Mitsume ga Tooru (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Moai-Kun (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Momotarou Densetsu (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Moon Crystal (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc>Moon Crystal is a platform action game where you control Ricky Slater on his mission to free his kidnapped father from the evil Count Crimson. The Count is forcing his father, a great scientist, to use the power of the moon crystal to turn the dead into living and rule the world.

There are 7 stages, each ending with a boss fight. The themes of the stages follow the story closely. The player begins each stage with only small knife to defend yourself. The player can find power-ups that can extend the range of your knife, give additional health containers, allow Ricky to make double jumps etc. The player has 3 lives and also an unlimited amount of continues.

The game is notable for its fluid animations and rich graphic cut scenes which moves the story forward. It was never officially released outside of Japan, but an unofficial English translation patch exists.</desc>
	<path>./Mother (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Motocross Champion (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Mottomo Abunai Deka (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Mouryou Senki Madara (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc>As a baby, Madara was found floating in a river near Mount Shumi. The elder Tatara saved him, build gadgets to replace his missing body parts and raised him together with his grandchild Kirin. On Madara's 15th birthday, when most of the world had already fallen to the Moki controlled by the Emperor Miroku, Madara sets out to find his real body and save the world from the Moki.

Mouryou Senki Madara is an RPG in which players control a party consisting of up two four characters exploring towns, dungeons and a world map from a top-down perspective. Battles occur randomly and the characters move and fight autonomously, although it is possible to pause battles at any time and order characters to fight, defend, use magic or items or flee. Furthermore, a basic battle strategy (attack, defend, stop or flee) can be selected from a tactics menu, where it is also possible to change the characters' starting formation.</desc>
	<path>./Musashi no Bouken (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Nagagutsu o Haita Neko - Sekai Isshuu 80 Nichi Daibouken (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Nakayoshi to Issho (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Nekketsu Kakutou Densetsu (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Nekketsu Kouha Kunio-Kun (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Nekketsu! Street Basket - Ganbare Dunk Heroes (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Niji no Silk Road (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Ninja Hattori-kun - Ninja wa Syugyou de Gozaru (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Ninja Jajamaru - Ginga Daisakusen (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Ninja Jajamaru Kun (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Ninja-kun - Ashura no Shou (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Ninja-kun - Majou no Bouken (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Ninjara Hoi! (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Nuts &amp; Milk (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc>In this Arcade game the gameplay is quite simple, the hero, named "Milk" must get all the fruits in the screen in order to free his girlfriend (don't ask me what's the relation) who is captured inside of a house. Your rival "'Nuts" will try to keep you away from your goal. To obtain the fruit, Milk will climb up ladders and jump onto different platforms.

Points are earned by obtaining the fruit, jumping over Nuts and completing the level in the shortest amount of time (obtaining the Bonus score value). Two game modes are included as well as a level editor.</desc>
	<path>./Obake no Q Tarou - Wan Wan Panic (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Oishinbo - Kyukyoku no Menu 3bon Syoubu (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Onyanko Town (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc>In Onyanko Town, a kitten named Michael has wandered outside its house and has now gotten lost. Now, it's up to the kitten's mother, Milky, to search all over the town trying to locate the kitten and return it to their household. The game is set in a town</desc>
	<path>./Paaman Part 2 - Himitsu Kessha Madoodan o Taose! (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Pachicom (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc>Pachicom is a pachinko game simulation. Pachinko can be described as a game that is a cross between pinball and a slot machine. This game comes with two different game modes to play. Game A lets the player play until they attain a score of at least 3000. </desc>
	<path>./Pac-Land (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc>Pac-Land is a side-scrolling 1-2 player game with a cartoony feel to it. Now equipped with arms, face, and legs, Pac must guide a fairy back to her home in Fairy Land, but this task will not be easy because Inky, Blinky, Pinky, Clyde, and Sue will pursue Pac-Man as he travels through Pac-Land. When he finally transports the fairy back to her home, Pac is given some magic shoes, which will help him get to his own home, where he will be greeted by his family: Ms. Pac-Man, Baby Pac-Man, Chomp Chomp, and Sourpuss. 

There are sixteen rounds to complete, with four trips each. During each round, he can grab a power pellet, which cause ghosts to turn blue, allowing Pac-Man to eat them for points. Points are also awarded by collecting fruit that appear, like cherries and strawberries. In some rounds, Pac must use a springboard to jump over a lake. He must also make it to the end of each round before time runs out, otherwise a ghost will chase him.</desc>
	<path>./Palamedes II - Star Twinkles (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Parallel World (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc>Having been sucked into and stranded in an alternate universe, you and your girlfriend must work your way around the puzzles of a magnificent castle to make your way back home.

The castle itself consists of a total of twenty worlds consisting of five stages apiece, each of which is filled to the brim with enemies. From your overhead view, you must use your directional pad to move your character around the grid and push the onscreen obstacles into your enemies to destroy them for the keys to escape as well as other goodies (extra time, bonus points, etc.), but keep in mind that you'll need to use those same obstacles to construct a path to the exit. And don't forget to work fast either, as you only have 100 seconds to clear each puzzle. Fail and you'll lose a life (you start with only three).

This game may be played with either one or two players (simultaneous play). Player One controls the boy. Player Two gets to be the girl. Both must have their wits about them to make it past the hoards of springs, crazy rollers, witches, zombies, and more to make it home in one piece.</desc>
	<path>./Paris-Dakar Rally Special (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Parodius Da! (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Peepar Time (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Penguin-Kun Wars (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Perfect Bowling (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Pescatore (Japan) (Proto) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Pizza Pop! (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc>A pizza delivery guy is in love with a girl named Betty. He's going about his careless job, delivering in hopes of big tips, when something catches his eye. It's a beautiful diamond ring, and it's impossible to resist! Unfortunately, it costs $10,000 - wa</desc>
	<path>./Pooyan (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc>In this remake of the arcade game Pooyan from the early '80s, you play the role of a pig, protecting its piglets from wolves.  

The first screen takes place near the pigs' home. Mrs. Pig rides up and down in a cable car, shooting at wolves, who are riding balloons downward, towards the ground. If the wolves land safely on the ground, then they can climb a ladder, near the cable-car, and catch Mrs. Pig. But if she shoots their balloons, they splat on the ground instead.

The wolves shoot acorns at the pig. But Mrs. Pig has a food based weapon too. If she gets to the top, she can get meat, to toss at the wolves and make them jump off their balloons in pursuit. Each wolf taken out this way is worth bonus points (on a doubling scheme: 400, 800 1600...)

The second scene takes place at the wolves lair. Here the wolves have reinforced balloons--it takes multiple hits to make them fall. Here they float upwards toward a big rock, which they push on top of Mrs. Pig, when seven wolves are present. Additionally, an alpha wolf (wolf leader) appears and summons wolves in packs.</desc>
	<path>./Popeye no Eigo Asobi (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Portopia Renzoku Satsujin Jiken (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Power Blazer (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Power Soccer (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Puyo Puyo (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc>This is a falling pieces puzzle, Puyo Puyo originated on the MSX system and was later turned into an arcade hall version. Get four same-colored puyos touching each other to make them disappear. If more puyos of the same color are connected then they will disappear too. This game can be played simultaneously by two players for a competitive gameplay. Hinder your opponent by making multiple puyo combinations.</desc>
	<path>./Puzslot (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Quarth (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc>Quarth is a typical puzzle/arcade game. Quarth can be moved  from right to left while the screen scrolls down. The playing field is filled with different blocks and your aim is to fill them in so they form complete rectangles or squares. Only when you succeed in this mission, the concerned blocks will disappear. New 'unformed' blocks appear while the playing field scrolls down making you play into full action at all times. As soon as a line of blocks reaches the bottom line, it is Game Over. Then you 'll be granted 10 seconds to decide if you want continue the level. Each Level consists of 9 Areas and you progress to the next level once you've cleared the last area. The Battle mode is a dual player mode.</desc>
	<path>./Radia Senki - Reimei Hen (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Robocco Wars (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Rockman 2 - Dr. Wily no Nazo (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Romancia (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc>In Romancia: Dragon Slayer Jr., you are a young warrior whom the king sends on a mission to rescue a lost princess. You must leave the town and enter the dreadful monster-infested catacombs in order to complete your quest. 

The game is a departure from Dragon Slayer RPG-oriented gameplay style. It tends more towards medieval-themed platformer action. The hero has hit points, can buy items and weapons, use magic, and stay in inns to recover health. However, instead of receiving experience points and becoming stronger, you simply must attack quicker (by bumping into your opponent on platform levels) and jump higher.</desc>
	<path>./Route-16 Turbo (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc>In Route-16 Turbo, players get behind the wheel of a car and drive around trying to collect valuable items lying around on the road while avoiding chase cars whose only purpose is to crash into the player's car.In the game, the player's car drives around </desc>
	<path>./Saint Seiya - Ougon Densetsu (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Saint Seiya - Ougon Densetsu Kanketsu Hen (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Saiyuuki World 2 - Tenjoukai no Majin (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Sanrio Carnival 2 (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Sanrio Cup - Pon Pon Volley (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Sansara Naga (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./SD Keiji - Blader (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Seirei Gari (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Shanghai (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc>Shanghai is one of the first video game adaptations of the tile-based game played with the Chinese mahjong stones - essentially a puzzle game that has little to do with real mahjong rules.The gameplay involves 144 tiles, each depicting different images, w</desc>
	<path>./Shanghai II (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc>Shanghai II is a variant of the puzzle game also known as solitaire mahjong. 144 mahjong tiles are arranged in rows and stacked upon each other in various patterns; the player's goal is to remove pairs of matching tiles that do not have adjacent tiles fro</desc>
	<path>./Shikinjou (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Shinsenden (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Shufflepuck Cafe (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc>One puck, and only two competitors. One is the computer, and the other is, of course, you. You get a chance to match your skills at this Air Hockey style game, over 'Cantina Band' inspired music. Deflect the puck around the walled area using your bat, trying to knock it into your opponent's goal.

There are several competitors, from which some of them definitely cheat, so be prepared to be laughed at. However, you can cheat as well, as you can resize your stick to fill the whole table width, or add one in the middle, and see who breaks glass first. There are single plays or the tournament where you play opponents in order of difficulty. The winner is the one who reaches 15 glassbreaks first.</desc>
	<path>./Silva Saga (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Sky Destroyer (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc>Sky Destroyer is an aerial combat game. Players take the role of a warplane that has to defeat various enemy combatants in the air and in the sea. The player's warplane is equipped with machine guns and can also fire off torpedoes. The main goal is to des</desc>
	<path>./Softball Tengoku (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Son Son (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc>In this game, you play the role of either Son Son or Ton Ton as you try to rescue your three friends from the clutches of a random bad guy who kidnapped them right in front of you. This game is a side scrolling adventure, where the game field advances automatically, and the screen is divided in six different floors, all of which are populated by enemies or obstacles that will kill you if you touch them; but both Son Son and Ton Ton attack their enemies by shooting small bullets at them out of their weapons (a magic cane and a pitchfork, respectively). Their attack can also stop many enemy projectiles! Your chosen character must jump from floor to floor, evading hunters, bats, fish, statues, insects, skull coins, and mad bombers! As you advance, you can pick up several food items to increase your score. Clearing the screen of enemies will also net you several hefty bonuses.

The story is heavily based upon &amp;quot;Journey To The West&amp;quot;; the player characters as well as the kidnapped ones are based upon the main characters in the story. This game is also a port of Capcom's original arcade game.
</desc>
	<path>./Space Harrier (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc>Run fly dodge those obstacles, but return fire on wave after wave of attacking aliens. Armed with a really big gun, you have to defend yourself against the alien hordes using your wits to navigate around the screen. But watch out for those end of level bosses!</desc>
	<path>./Space Invaders (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc>Earth is under attack from rows of bomb dropping aliens, and you need to defend it! The rows of aliens begin at the top of the screen, and you control a laser cannon at the bottom of the screen. Your goal is to earn points by shooting the aliens before they can land. The aliens march back and forth, and each time the end of the screen is reached they will drop one row closer to the bottom. Shoot them all, and you move on to the next (tougher) level, but if even one of them lands the game is over. From time to time a flying saucer will pass by along the top of the screen; shoot this to earn extra points. Just above your laser canon are three shields; these can be used to hide from the alien's bombs, but will also block your own shots. You begin the game with a limited number of laser canons, and if all of them are bombed the game ends.</desc>
	<path>./Space Shadow (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Spartan X 2 (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc>Somewhat more faithful to the plot of the movie than the first Spartan X game, it attempts to tell the same story: In Barcelona, Mr. X has captured the pickpocket Silvia. In order to get her back, Thomas, a Kung-Fu master who runs a restaurant must travel the city, eventually reaching Mr. X's castle and attempt to rescue her.

Spartan X 2 is an expanded version of the original Spartan X game (aka Kung-Fu). Similar to that game, Spartan X 2 is a side-scrolling fighting game. Controlling Thomas, the player is able to move left and right, jump, kick and punch. Thomas has an energy bar and is defeated if he loses all of the energy. Some enemies drop items such as potions which will help replenish this bar. At the end of each level, Thomas encounters a boss.

Story cutscenes are displayed between each level, where Thomas contacts other characters through use of a computer.</desc>
	<path>./Spelunker II - Yuusha e no Chousen (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Splatterhouse - Wanpaku Graffiti (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc>Wanpaku Graffiti is the first Splatterhouse game to appear on a home console. It is not clear how it fits in the series' timeline, but it starts with Jennifer mourning over Rick's grave (her boyfriend). Lightning strikes his grave and he is resurrected. Before she can rejoice, another bolt strikes the grave next to him and a jack-o-lantern appears. This pumpkin king kidnaps Jennifer and Rick barely has the time to wipe off the dust from his clothes before he sets off to rescue his girlfriend.

Although the game is not as gory as the other titles, there is still plenty of disturbing enemies such as headless chickens, severed hands and zombies. Through seven side-scrolling levels, including a graveyard, a mansion, a Japanese pagoda and an Egyptian pyramid, you chase the pumpkin king with your cleaver and a shotgun you can pick up along the road. Just like the other games in the series, there are lots of movie references. The game often needs good timing and pixel perfect jumps, as falling down from platforms will regenerate the enemies. You can pick up candy, hamburgers and cans of soda to restore your health.
</desc>
	<path>./Sqoon (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Star Luster (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc>In Star Luster, the player controls Dan Heinick, a pilot of the starfighter Gaia. He is tasked with having to fight the evil being Battura and its minions, who are bent on controlling the entire universe.The game is played from an inside the cockpit view.</desc>
	<path>./Star Wars (Japan) (Namco) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Sted - Iseki Wakusei no Yabou (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Stick Hunter - Exciting Ice Hockey (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Sugoro Quest - Dice no Senshitachi (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Summer Carnival '92 - Recca (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Super Arabian (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc>The object of Super Arabian is to collect all the pots on the screen, while avoiding pests like birds and worms who will block your way and eventually destroy you. If they do this, you can kick their Arabian butt and knock them off the screen. If you manage to kick two or more enemies at once, something will hit you that will make you invincible for a few seconds.

It doesn't matter about the order in which you collect the pots. However, each pot has a different letter on it, and if you collect the pots in the order that they appear at the top-right of the screen, you will receive a whopping 5000 points. After you collect the pots, you move on to the next level. There are four levels in each part (section), and each part has a theme to them. In Part 1, Level 1, for instance, you have to collect the letters that make up the word ANIMAL. In subsequent levels, you have to create words that are actual animals (HORSE, RABBIT, MONKEY). Also, if you take too long to complete the level, a red genie will emerge from one of the pots and will attack you.</desc>
	<path>./Super Black Onyx (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc>Rumor says that the legendary Black Onyx, an artifact that grants eternal youth and happiness to those who can find it, lies within the Black Tower near the town of Utsuro. You assemble a party of brave adventurers and venture into the tower, defeating monsters on your way to the great treasure.

The Black Onyx is the very first RPG made by a Japanese company. It is similar in gameplay to early Wizardry and Ultima games with killing monsters and exploring dungeons, with dark, realistic visuals. You create a party (up to five members) and explore a maze-like 3D dungeon, fighting random enemies on the way. You also meet adventurers whom you can convince to join your party. The combat engine is turn-based.
</desc>
	<path>./Super Contra 7 (China) (Unl) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Super Donkey Kong - Xiang Jiao Chuan (China) (Unl) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Super Dyna'mix Badminton (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc>Radically different from other racquet sports such as tennis, badminton uses a high-drag shuttle which gives it an irregular path. In this video game adaptation, the player controls the Japanese player in a competition against five opponents: Canada, USA, UK, South Korea and China. Each match is played on best-of-five sets, played to 15 (boys) or 11 (girls) points. Four different courts can be chosen.

Along the d-pad, two buttons are used to control the player - one to swing the racquet, and other to jump. By following the shadow of the shuttle the player can position himself correctly, and then hit it in perfect timing, giving it enough power and lift to reach the opponent's side, and then (hopefully) descend out of the opponent's reach. Jumping allows the player to hit the shuttle downwards but still over the net, reducing the reaction time for a proper return drastically.</desc>
	<path>./Super Pinball (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Super Xevious - Gump no Nazo (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc>Super Xevious is a 2D shoot 'm up by Namco and is part of the Xevious series. Xevious is known as one of the hardest and fastest shooters around and Super Xevious is even harder and faster!

The enemies of the first Xevious game are back! But this time they are not alone. No, the brought some nasty friends with them!
It is your job, as a fighter pilot, to blast them away! Destroy everything in sight!

Some ground structures that must be destroyed are hidden and are called Sol Citadels. To locate these hidden structures you must keep an eye on the target-sight that will flash when it goes over the structures.

Super Xevious takes all the great elements of the original Xevious and has also some improvements.
Some examples of improvements are, for instance, the shield option and the upgrade option.
The shield protects you from immediately death if you got hit during an attack.
The upgrade option gives you the possibility to upgrade your bombs, lasers and shields.
</desc>
	<path>./Superstar Pro Wrestling (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Sweet Home (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc>"Sweet Home" follows the exploits of five members of
an investigation group: Kazuo, Akiko, Taro, Asuka, and Emi. The famous painter Mamiya Ichirou lived many years in a secluded mansion, and rumor says there are some valuable frescos to find inside. Our investigators decide to take some pictures of the frescos. However, upon entering the mansion, a ghost-like figure of Mamiya appears and threatens them. After this, they find themselves trapped in the mansion. The heroes must now find a way out of the mansion, not forgetting the frescos they came there for, and the destiny of an earlier investigation group that has disappeared under mysterious circumstances.

"Sweet Home" is perhaps the first known example of survival horror genre, created by the same company that later made the famous Resident Evil. However, "Sweet Home" is also a console-style RPG: characters fight random monsters in turn-based battles, equip various weapons and level up. You can (and must) form different teams from the five available characters, both for battles and for solving puzzles. Each character has his (or her) own item-based skill: Taro can take pictures, Emi can unlock almost any door, Kazuo has a lighter, Akiko uses a vacuum cleaner to remove dust and other obstacles, and Asuka has medical kits.

The game was never released outside of Japan.</desc>
	<path>./Taito Chase H.Q. (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc>As an undercover agent of Chase Headquarters, your job is to patrol the streets and track down five criminals. You are given a mission briefing before you start which gives information on the suspect and what car they drive. Then you drive across the city without crashing into other cars, and catch up with the criminal's car. To arrest the suspects, you must keep bumping into their car until it is no longer functional. And you have to do this under a strict time limit. You can't afford to crash into cars or buildings or you waste time getting on the road again. 

However, once you've caught up with your suspect, you are given more time. Your car is also equipped with turbo boosts, which you can use to gain extra speed if you are way behind the criminal. Each arrest is based on a "suspicion".</desc>
	<path>./Taiyou no Yuusha Fighbird (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Takahashi Meijin no Bouken Jima IV (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Takahashi Meijin no Bugutte Honey (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Takeshi no Chousenjou (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Tao (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Tashiro Masashi no Princess ga Ippai (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Tenchi wo Kurau II - Shokatsu Koumei Den (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Tetrastar - The Fighter (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Tetris (Bulletproof) (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc>This version of Tetris is one of many conversions of the famous block-stacking game, as well as the best-known (but not the only) version on Nintendo's first home console. The goal is to place pieces made up of four tiles in a ten-by-twenty well, organizing them into complete rows, which disappear. As rows are cleared, the pace of the game increases, and the game ends if the stack reaches the top of the well.

The game offers two different modes of play, "Type A" and "Type B". "Type A" is a standard endless mode, where the speed of the game increases every ten lines, with an option for the starting level when beginning the game. "Type B", on the other hand, is a race to clear 25 lines, with options for both drop speed and starting garbage. In both modes, successful play is rewarded with cute animations. There are also three different background songs to choose from.</desc>
	<path>./Tetris 2 + Bombliss (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc>Tetris 2 + BomBliss is one of the many versions of the famous soviet puzzle game. There are, naturally, two variations featured on this cartridge: regular Tetris with several modes, as well as a new game called BomBliss. Also included is a two-player battle version of regular Tetris.

Tetris mode includes three game types. First is A-Type, which is a standard endless mode that continually increases pace until the player loses. Next is B-Type, which is a race to 25 lines under increasingly tough conditions. Last is C-Type, which is similar to A-Type, but adds a continually-rising stack of garbage appearing from the bottom of the well.

BomBliss is slightly different from regular Tetris. In each stage, the well is filled with a preset pattern of blocks and bombs. Completing a line will, unlike Tetris, not clear it. It will, however, activate any bombs within the completed line, which can then destroy the blocks. The goal is to clear the entire well of blocks.

BomBliss also includes three different modes of play. Contest mode tasks the player with clearing out a preset field in as few blocks as possible; the top three scores for each stage are saved. Puzzle mode tasks the player with clearing a preset field with a preset sequence of pieces. Last, there is Construction mode, which allows the player to build their own puzzle stages.</desc>
	<path>./Thexder (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc>A platform shooter from Japan, Thexder offers many levels and diverse enemies that gradually increase in difficulty.  You pilot a Battletech-style robot capable of switching from a 'mech into a jet at any time.  Your weapon auto-aims, but uses up a fixed amount of rechargable energy; if you run out of this energy, you'll have to wait a few seconds before you can fire again.  Your 'mech also contains a shield that can be activated to protect you from harm, but this lasts for a few seconds and uses up some of your life energy.</desc>
	<path>./Time Zone (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Titan (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc>Titan is a 2D arcade game / puzzle game hybrid.For some reason, mad professors of the future tend to invent strange entertainment games in which every participant dies. Professor Hybrysâ variant is called Titan and involves a ball, a control unit and 80</desc>
	<path>./Tokkyuu Shirei Solbrain (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Top Rider (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc>Top-Rider is a motorcycle game in which the main objective is to basically make a decent or random time in each race.To achieve a decent time the player must avoid getting off the track and colliding with the "endless" number of motorcycles that will appe</desc>
	<path>./Toukon Club (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Tower of Druaga, The (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc>You control a heroic knight, who is actually prince Gilgamesh, who must attempt to rescue the maiden from the demon Druaga. You are armed with a sword and shield to attack and defend.
You move from floor to floor, which are constructed as mazes, searching for the key, this key will unlock the stage exit.
Items can be found by killing (all) enemies.</desc>
	<path>./Transformers - Convoy no Nazo (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Triathron, The (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./TwinBee (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc>TwinBee is a vertical scrolling shooter. The players control cartoon-like spacecrafts with anthropomorphic arms, player one being TwinBee and player two being WinBee. The spacecrafts can be moved in all 8 directions, with one button for regular shooting flying enemies and one button for dropping ground bombs.

Power-ups in the form of bells can be collected by shooting clouds. The color of the bell will change if it is shot by the player, assuming one of the possible colors:

1. Yellow: grants bonus points;
2. White: upgrades player's guns to a twin cannon;
3. Blue: increases player's speed (up to five levels);
4. Green: creates image copies of the craft for more firepower;
5. Red: provides a shield to sustain damage.

The green and red bells cannot be combined. Alternate power ups can be collected from the ground, such as an alternate bell which upgrades the craft with a three way gun and a star which destroys all enemies on screen.

One shot in the middle section of the craft will destroy it. Shots which hit one of the craft's arms will destroy only the arm. If both arms are lost, the craft won't be able to shoot bombs anymore and will have to be repaired by an ambulance.

In the two-player mode, TwinBee (cyan craft) and WinBee (red craft) have the same speed and they can join "hand-to-hand" and fire a super blast. Also in two player mode, if one craft is hit by the other from behind, it will fire four multi-directional shots.</desc>
	<path>./TwinBee 3 - Poko Poko Daimaou (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Uchuu Keibitai SDF (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc>Space Defence Force SDF is a vertically scrolling space shooter. Though it scrolls vertically, you are granted some movement horizontal movement as well. The action isn't frantic, but the game is still somewhat difficult due to tight enemy attack waves and the possibility of being shot in the back. For this reason, you should not let enemies pass unscathed, since they may shoot back at you from off-screen. At some points, power up capsules will materialize in space. They will grant you not only greater firepower, but also serve as a reconfigurable armor, which is SDF's main selling point. The armor may be moved from your front to your back, and while it is moved in a large arc, it will destroy any enemies it happens to ram. When fastened to your rear, it will also grant a small speed boost. Learning to use the armor is the key to surviving in this game.</desc>
	<path>./Urusei Yatsura - Lum no Wedding Bell (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Valis - The Fantastic Soldier (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Valkyrie no Bouken - Toki no Kagi Densetsu (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Volguard II (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc>Volguard II is a side-scrolling shooter that is a follow-up to Volguard. Players have to shoot their way through 25 areas in one of the four difficulty levels the game offers.Players control a flying craft that has the ability to shoot both bullets and bo</desc>
	<path>./Wagyan Land (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Wagyan Land 2 (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Wai Wai World (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Wai Wai World 2 - SOS!! Paseri Jou (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc>Parsley Castle, an outer space kingdom, has been invaded! And strange beings are to blame. Playing as Rickle, a cyborg built by Dr. Cinnamon from Konami's Twinbee series, and several of his friends from other (mostly Japan-only) Konami games, your objecti</desc>
	<path>./Wanpaku Kokkun no Gourmet World (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Warpman (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc>This game is an updated version of Warp Warp. Players once again take control of the monster fighter as he does battle with various types of enemy Beroberos.The game features two types of gameplay. First, players start out in the Space World. Players cont</desc>
	<path>./Wily &amp; Light no Rockboard - That's Paradise (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Wit's (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Woody Poko (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Yie Ar Kung-Fu (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc>Based on the popular arcade game, Yie Ar Kung-Fu follows Oolong's quest to become a Kung-Fu master.  Of course this involves fighting a wide range of opponents in a traditional one-on-one 2D environment.  Oolong has a wide range of attacks he can use to lower his opponent's life bar, including traditional punching and kicking attacks as well as jumping ones.  Opponents are well armed with unique weapons and attacks, so Oolong's task won't be easy.</desc>
	<path>./Youkai Club (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Ys (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc>You are Adol (Aron in Sega Master System version) Christian, a red-haired adventurer and expert swordsman. One day you encounter a fortuneteller who sends you on a quest to find information about the six books of Ys. It appears that there was once an ancient land called Ys, whose secret was sealed in those six books. Before long you learn that the six books were all stolen by the evil wizard Dark Fact (Dulk Dekt in Sega Master System version, Malificus in PC version). It is your task to defeat the villain and to discover the secret of Ys!

Ys is an action RPG with original combat: instead of pressing the "attack" button, you simply run into the enemies you encounter. You do more damage if you run into them from the back or from the sides - a head-to-head collision might result in Adol's death if the monster is stronger than him. You gain gold and experience points for defeating your foes; once you have gained enough experience, you level up and become stronger. You can buy and equip swords, armor, shields, and other accessories.
</desc>
	<path>./Ys II - Ancient Ys Vanished - The Final Chapter (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc>This is the second game in the long-running Ys action RPG series. A bright light shot up from Dahm Tower in the end of the first game, and our hero Adol Christian is awakened by a young girl who finds him lying on the ground. She introduces herself as Lilia and tells Adol he is in the land of Ys. Finally he was able to establish a connection between his world and this mysterious land! But finding the gateway to Ys is not enough: Adol must stop the evil entity that his archenemy Dark Fact served. And his foes already know where he is...

This game is a direct sequel to what PC players know as Ancient Land of Ys (of which the original NES version was simply called Ys), and is also the same game (story-wise) as the second part of Ys: Book I &amp; II for TurboGrafx CD. The gameplay utilizes an unusual action RPG combat style, where you don't press any attack button, but run into your enemies in order to cause damage. You should choose the angles and the measure of contact with the enemy carefully, otherwise you'll be dead. You can (and should) level up, perform quests for village people, gather money, and upgrade your weapons and inventory, like in any other RPG.
</desc>
	<path>./Ys III - Wanderers from Ys (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc>Adol's long time friend, Dogi wishes to return to his home town of Redmont after hearing about strange disturbances that are happening there.  Always looking for an adventure, Adol joins him and soon finds out the cause of this new evil.

Ys III breaks away from the "bumping into enemies" battle system of the first two games and allows Adol to control his sword in a variety of directions. As well as changing the battle system, the game is now side scrolling instead of the previous games top-down view. Adol also now has the ability to jump. Not new to the series is the use of magical rings which give Adol different powering up abilities such as healing and shielding. The game also uses various key items found along the way to solve minor puzzles and progress the story.
</desc>
	<path>./Yume Penguin Monogatari (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Zippy Race (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc>In a game reminiscent of both Road Fighter and Rally Bike, the player takes control of a motorcyclist who's in a race to be the first to traverse the United States from the west to the east coast, starting in Los Angeles and ending up in New York City.

Gameplay consists of the player dodging cars and other roadway hazards on their way to the next checkpoint. Players can either accelerate or hit the brakes on their motorcycle so they can avoid getting into an accident. Accidents cause the player to lose fuel and running out of fuel can end the game. So players must keep an eye out on the fuel gauge, which can be refilled by fuel barrels littered throughout each stage. Each car the player passes betters their ranks which increases their score.</desc>
	<path>./Zoids - Mokushiroku (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc/>
	<path>./Zombie Hunter (Japan) (Translated En).nes</path>
	<desc>The city of Palma has always been protected by the spirits of the four elements. However, Dolgo, the spirit of the earth, revolts and makes off with the Life Seeker, the controller of the world's life energies, to his underground lair. In doing so, the people of Palma begin to lose their very souls. The spirit of the air has ordered that a champion needs to be found, to retrieve the Life Seeker from the clutches of Dolgo. You are that champion.

Zombie Hunter is an action-adventure RPG that plays similar to Zelda II with its side-scrolling battles. You receive experience from defeating your enemies and you have an inventory complete with armor and weapons.</desc>
	<path>./Zunou Senkan Galg (Japan).nes</path>
	<desc>The Zystasians are at war with Dragg and his forces and need help from the artificial intelligence battleship Galg. The player is given the mission to collect 100 enemy parts in order to have a final showdown with Dragg.The game is a vertical scrolling sh</desc>
